"Netflix
Series" [Tense music]
[Group 4 members' strenuous groans]
(Beauty) Hey, do something, you fucker!
[Group 4 members' groans of effort]
(Sang-woo) Everyone,
wake up and listen to me!
When I give the signal, we move
exactly three steps
forward. Move forward?
Are you crazy!
We have to knock them over!
Don't talk nonsense!
Let's do it!
(Beauty) No way, I can't do it!
(Sang-woo) If you can't, you die!
It's three steps.
One, two, three!
[Group 4 members' groans of effort]
[Group 5 members' strenuous groans]
[Gi-hun's startled groan]
[Anxious breathing]
[Group 5 members' groans of effort]
Pull! [Group 4
members' groans of effort]
[People's groans of effort]
[Group 5 members' strenuous groans]
[Group 5 members' urgent groans]
(Male 1) No!
[Group 5 members' screams]
[Group 4 members' urgent groans]
[Group 4 members' strenuous
groans] [Group 5 members' screams]
‎[Group 5 members fall with a thud]
‎[Group 4 members' rough breathing]
‎[Heavy Music]
‎[Forklift Warning Sound]
‎[Gi-hun's Rough Breathing]
‎(Man 2) Our Father who art in heaven...
‎[Man 2 mutters]
‎(Ji-young) Uncle
‎Who are you praying to right now?
‎Lord?
‎[Continues muttering]
‎Do you think that you being alive right now
‎is thanks to the Lord?
‎[Bitter Laughter]
‎Ha, the fact that you're alive now
‎and moving your tongue
‎is because of that old man
‎who pulled off an incredible scheme at the end.
It's thanks to that uncle.
So if you're going to pray in gratitude,
‎do it to those people.
‎You lost little lamb,
‎can't you hear the wailing of those who were crucified today?
‎We've survived another day
‎thanks to their sacrifice and blood.
‎On behalf of all of us sinners,
‎(man 2) I give thanks for their sacrifice and
‎the Lord's choice,
‎and I offer my prayers.
‎What a mess.
‎After killing them with your own hands,
‎[muttering]
‎Ah.
Just praying roughly
Are we all going to heaven?
Ah, fuck, then I should pray too
Our Father in heaven
We have come together today
To send many humans
To your side, Lord
So that we can send even more humans
- Please give us strength…
- (Early morning) Be quiet
[The man2 keeps muttering]
Me?
Or that guy?
Both
[The elevator jolts]
‎[Forklift Warning Sound]
‎(Jiyoung) What's your name?
‎(Saebyeok) Why would you care about my name?
‎(Jiyoung) What do you want to do with a name? Just call me
‎(Saebyeok) Don't call me
‎(Jiyoung) You're being expensive
‎(Saebyeok) I'm asking as a favor
‎Could you just leave me alone?
‎(Jiyoung) You're the one who came to me first
‎and started talking
‎[Meaningful Sound Effect]
‎(Man 3) Hey, did you guys see that?
‎That bald uncle who peed himself, huh?
Then the little bastards behind started to drag...
[The door creaks open]
[Significant music]
[A bitter laugh]
[Forklift warning sound]
[Remote control operation sound]
[The coffin falls with a thud]
[Soldier 1's strained groan]
(Soldier 1) I can't breathe
Quick, call the doctor
(Beautiful woman) I really
thought we were all going to die right away?
But when I actually lay like this
it feels like I get my strength back
“Oh my, what is this? This works?”
“Sir, how did you know that?”
[Laughter]
“Well, when I was young…”
“Did you just mimic that from a movie?”
“(Beauty) Ah, what was that movie? That one
You know, like this,
Like this, doing this, that one
“The Matrix”
“Hey
Did you just come to Korea and not work,
Just watch movies?”
“And brother
“(Beauty) ‘You just take three steps forward.’”
‎[Elastic]
‎What is it, totally awesome
‎No, how did you think of
‎all that from there?
‎You just called it nonsense
‎Did I?
‎What nonsense are you talking about?
‎(Ali) Crying like crazy
‎[Imitating the beauty] 'Crazy!
‎Don't talk nonsense!'
‎You said that
‎(Beauty) Hey
‎Which country are you from?
‎Do you have a visa?
‎Are you staying illegally? Hey
‎Hey, guys
No, foreign kids who don't even know this lineage
Can we really let them join our team? Huh?
I think I should completely reorganize the members this time, damn it.
Who's the big boss here?
A cool older brother
Is your older brother the boss?
There's none of that here
Everyone's just the same
[Gasps]
That's better
An equal society
Fuck
(Beauty) Some punk acts like he's a king completely.
They do whatever
they want, seriously.
(Gi-hun) But why were you kicked out, ma'am?
Brother
I’m not a ma'am
I
am Han Mi-nyeo
Just call me 'Mi-nyeo'
(Mi-nyeo) And I wasn't kicked out
[kicks her foot] I walked out on my own
Because I just couldn't match the level of those punks
(Sang-woo) They only threw you away
They only picked big guys
That too, right before the game
It feels like we already know what game we’re going to
play. [Deoksu's laughter]
[Notification sound]
[Guidance voice] We will turn off the
lights in 30 minutes. Please
prepare to go to sleep.
(Sangwoo) When the lights go
out,
there might be a fight again.
Let’s prepare in advance. (Man 4) How do we do that?
With the women here and that old man,
we're the weakest ones anyway.
(Man 2) Let’s choose the weaker side
and strike first. [Nervous laughter]
Those who believe in the
Lord are more fearsome.
(Man 2) We are
all already sinners.
Our hands are soaked in blood.
Attack is the best form of defense.
Let's just attack.
Yesterday, when the fight broke out at dawn,
do you know how the man in front of me died?
He got his neck snapped by someone he thought was on his side.
Do you trust me?
I don't trust you.
[Gi-hun's heavy breathing]
(Gi-hun) Yes,
first and foremost, we need to defend.
Let's set up barricades before the lights go out.
Having cover will be a source of strength.
[Nervous laugh]
(Duksu) Hey, Ssangmun-dong
You're trying hard to survive.
But
Well, is it okay to stack
something like this?
It seems like the wind
will blow in strongly.
[Deoksu's Smile]
Are you going to be okay?
Do you really trust
those trashy humans
on your team?
[The guys are joking]
[Laughter from the guys]
(Guy 5) Go ahead, fuck
Try it, try it, try it, fuck
[Laughter from Guy 3]
(Gi-hun) If it were me
When the lights go out and a fight breaks out
I’d look for a chance to kill you first
Because you’re the strongest bastard
[The guys are joking]
[Awkward breath from Guy 5]
(Male 3) Hyung-nim
Where should we start today, huh?
(Deoksoo) Let's take it easy today
Why?
We need to keep the number down a bit for tonight...
(Deoksoo) I said let's just relax
(Male 3) Ah, okay
Hey
You guys too
Just put that down and take it easy
[Deoksoo's sigh]
Where did the doctor go?
(Male 5) Just a moment ago
I think I saw him go out saying he was going to the restroom?
[Meaningful music]
[Nervous breathing]
(Gi-hoon) The lights
will go out soon.
It won't be easy to attack.
Just in case, let's take turns as
the night watchman one by one.
Pair up into groups of two.
One person might fall asleep
and might betray us by siding with the other.
(Il-nam) I'll go first.
When you get old, you can't sleep.
Sir.
Ah, how can we stretch our legs and relax
if we trust an old man from the start?
I'll go first.
(Ali) I'll join you too.
I'm not sleepy right now.
Then I'll go next.
If I get tired, wake me up right away.
Then I will do it with you
If you're okay with it
Yes, let's do that
[Timer sound starts]
[Interesting music]
[Timer sound ends]
[Waves crashing]
[Seagull cries]
[Bell notification sound]
[Guidance voice] Today's duties are over
[Meaningful music]
Workers, please return to your accommodations
Workers, please return to your accommodations immediately
(Ali) Eat this.
I didn't eat during meal time earlier
and saved it
I was going to give it to the boss
Why aren't you eating this and giving it to me?
Thanks to the boss, I survived today
I wanted to say thank you
There's nothing to be thankful for
It's something I did to live
I also gave the boss transportation fare
[Sangwoo's sigh]
If you receive it, you have to give it back
Did you get it?
You said your name was Ali, right?
How old are you?
Ali is thirty-three years old.
Then just call me hyung.
Is that okay?
Hyung.
How did you get here?
I came to Korea to make money.
Hyung.
No, not Korea, here.
This game.
I came because I don't have money, hyung.
What about your family?
In Pakistan.
I have mom, dad, and siblings.
And in Korea,
I have a wife and a baby.
You have a kid?
How old are they?
I have a one-year-old son.
You must miss him.
[Sigh]
Yes.
Why did you come, hyung?
Here
I don't have money
I'm here to make money
[Meaningful music]
[The door creaks open]
[The door creaks shut]
[The lock clicks open]
[Flashlight operation sound]
(Worker) Number 29
What happened yesterday? Why didn't you come?
(Junho) I'm sorry
(Worker) 'Sorry'?
The soldiers said they couldn't trust you and wanted to get rid of you
I stopped them
Last time you saved my life during the dive.
That's how I repaid you.
If you do this just one more time,
you're out.
[The door bangs loudly]
[The door opens with a click]
[Scanner operating sound]
(Soldier 2) Ha, number 29.
You've finally shown up, huh?
(Worker) I gave you a separate warning.
(Soldier 1) We couldn't even get the stuff delivered yesterday.
Is this something that can be resolved just by giving each other warnings?
(Worker) Then you guys should deliver it yourselves.
Do you think it's easy to find a diver like us in here?
(Soldier 1) Don't mess up the delivery today.
[The door closes with a click]
(Worker) What’s going on?
Haven't you finished a single one yet?
[Tense music]
(Soldier 2) Doctor, your hands are slower today than usual.
(Worker) Quack, hurry up.
If we miss the delivery time and the ship leaves, it's all in vain.
Every day, I can't even sleep properly
I can't even eat properly
While passing through the brink of death
Try doing this once
(Worker) So you don't die
They teach you the game
They even prepare food for you separately
[Weapon's sigh]
[Surprised breath]
Hyung
Uh, Sangwoo
I'm about to switch shifts
(Gi-hun) Uh
Uh, yeah
(Sangwoo) Are you okay?
(Gi-hun) Huh?
(Sangwoo) It feels like you had a bad dream or something
‎(Gi-hun) No, no
‎I'm okay
‎(Deok-soo) Hey
‎(Man 6) Hyung, why aren't you sleeping?
‎[Deok-soo's sigh]
‎(Deok-soo) Strangely, I can't sleep
‎(Man 6) I'm keeping watch well
‎Don't worry and sleep comfortably
‎[Deok-soo chuckles]
‎(Deok-soo) I trust you, you little bastard
‎[Man 6 coughs]*
‎Hasn't the doctor arrived yet?
‎(Man 6) Yes, it's strange?
‎How long has it been since he went to the bathroom?
‎(Soldier) Catch it
‎(Soldier 2) It's urgent
‎Should I try what's left over there?
‎If you just tell me the tips
‎I think I could do it too?
‎Do you think it looks easy
‎because I'm just here doing this?
‎(Soldier 1) These days, when I watch the news
‎nurse aides and office managers
‎are even performing surgeries instead
‎[Soldier 1's laughter]
‎They say they're actually better than doctors?
‎If you're so confident, you should do it yourself
‎(Soldier 1) That quack who killed a person
‎due to a medical accident
Still, only pride remains.
You were doing so well,
did you ruin your eyesight last time?
You only got cursed out by the buyers.
Back then, you guys put a living human
on the operating table.
That (weapon) woke up,
and because it was thrashing around, everything turned into a mess!
(Worker) There's no time for this.
The ship is about to arrive.
[Sigh]
[Tense music]
[A booming sound is heard]
[People gasp in surprise]
[People are in an uproar]
(Guy 7) Gi-hun.
‎[The Sound of Suffering]
‎[People Are Noisy]
‎(Il-nam) [Grabbing Gi-hoon's arm] Hey
‎[Flustered Breath]
‎What are you thinking so much about?
‎I thought you were sleeping with your eyes open
‎[Awkward Moan]
‎It reminds me of the past
‎The past?
‎At the company I used to work for
‎we went on strike
‎We set up barricades like this
‎What kind of company did you work for?
‎It was an automobile company
‎(Il-nam) Hmm…
‎Yeah
Why the strike?
They say everyone should leave because the company is struggling.
[Il-nam responds]
It’s a company I've worked at for over 10 years.
(Il-nam) That must have been tough.
[Il-nam clicks his tongue]
[Gi-hoon's sigh]
(Gi-hoon) A baby is about to be born,
And expenses keep piling up,
But suddenly they tell us to leave with no plan,
The company messed things up,
And now they want us to take responsibility.
[sigh]
I’m angry,
And just like now back then.
We took turns keeping watch
I guarded the factory with my colleagues
[Il-nam responds]
I wonder when the police will come in
I’m trembling
(Il-nam) Right, about 10 years ago
There was a big strike at the car company
I think it made big news back then
Someone died there, I guess?
Hmm…
Oh dear
I'm sorry
I, this
‎[heavy music]
It's unnecessary talk, right?
[Il-nam’s awkward breath]
‎[Awkward Moan]
‎[Difficult Groan]
‎[Gi-hun's Sigh]
‎[Il-nam's Shaking Breaths]
‎(Gi-hun) Sir, ‎[Il-nam's
Difficult Groan]
‎Are you okay?
‎Huh?
‎Ah, you're burning
up. ‎[Il-nam agrees]
‎(Soldier 2) At that time, ‎I really
thought I was peeing my pants.
I thought it was a
corpse, ‎but suddenly it sat
up like a zombie, ‎with one eyeball
popping out, ‎and it glared at me.
Ha, that showed up in my
dream last night, you know?
‎(Soldier 1) The 'Mugunghwa Flower' game is
‎all about the guys who got shot with sniper rifles.
There wasn't much
to gain anyway.
That zombie looked somewhat fine on the surface.
I almost died delivering that.
I only have one kidney, so I couldn’t even get paid properly.
Is it my fault that that zombie only has one kidney?
Is this guy’s organs fine?
[Dark music]
Half of the people that come in here are either signing a body release or are terminal patients.
It’s really unsettling.
[Il-nam coughs]
Please lie down here.
[Strenuous Moan]
Ha, just wait a moment, yeah
I need to lower my pants, damn it
[Strained groan]
[Grabs the water bottle]
[Urgent breathing]
Damn it
(Dawn) Use this
[Urgent breathing]
(Junho) That zombie
What happened?
(Worker) What do you mean what happened?
I smashed it to death with that in a hurry
(Soldier 2) But why are you asking about that?
You saw it all too
(Soldier 1) What about you?
Don't you remember?
‎(Jun-ho) Ah, back then
‎I was so out of it
‎(Soldier 1) Out of it?
‎You cleaned up the corpses
‎with your own hands
‎Number 29
‎You…
‎(Soldier) This is my operating room!
‎[The soldier's trembling breath]
‎Please stop the nonsense and
‎focus on this properly!
‎[Angry breath]
‎Let's concentrate on the work!
‎Or else I'll just cut everything
‎including your liver and kidneys! Damn it!
‎[The rough breathing of the weapon]
‎[Rough breathing]
‎Thank you
‎[A sigh]
‎Take a rest
‎Gather your strength
‎You have to play together again tomorrow
‎[Gi-hun's sigh]
‎(Gi-hun) You should sleep more
‎I can do it alone
‎(Sae-byeok) But we’re a team of two?
‎Anyway, I'm already wide awake
‎Thank you
‎[Gi-hun's strained groan]
‎(Gi-hun) Water
‎(Sae-byeok) I didn't just give it to you
‎You owe me when you get water tomorrow
‎[A sigh]
‎[Gi-hun's hollow laugh]
‎[Jun-ho's strained breath]
‎(Soldier 2) Hurry up.
‎[Significant music]
‎(Soldier 1) This time, I'm in good condition.
‎Make sure to get the full price.
‎(Worker) Hurry, the boat has already arrived.
‎[The door shuts with a click]
‎(Weapon) Now tell me.
‎What's the next game?
‎(Soldier 1) We still don't know.
‎What do you mean?
‎[Tense music]
‎I don't know.
(Soldier 1) It hasn't been
delivered to us yet either.
‎(Soldier) Then ask your upper-ups.
‎There must be someone watching your backs.
‎(Soldier 2) If they knew, they would have already contacted us.
‎There must be some circumstances.
‎That's your situation,
‎you've done everything they've told you to.
‎(Soldier) Find out right now!
‎(Soldier 2) Go back and wait!
‎I'll let you know before the game,
‎(Soldier) Don't talk shit, damn it.
‎[The door slams shut]
‎(Worker) What are you doing?
Pull
[Significant sound effect]
(Soldier 1) Calm down
If you can't figure out the game
the ones inside
will kill me tonight
(Soldier 1) If you keep this up
you won't figure anything out
Give me some time
(Weapon) You think I'm going to believe the trash you guys say! Damn
(Soldier 1) So what do you want me to do?
You go out and find out
[Weapon's strained grunt]
(Weapon) And you
That guy is supposed to be with me here until he comes back.
(Soldier 1) If we keep doing this, it'll get even more dangerous.
We have to get back before morning roll call.
That's fucking up to you guys to figure out!
I absolutely won't go back to the barracks until I understand the game!
[Heavy breathing of the weapon]
(Soldier 2) Okay, got it, calm down.
Go up and find out about the game.
(Soldier 1) Got it.
[Tense music]
(Soldier 2) Wait!
You need to take the key
There's a key for upstairs in my right pocket
[The trembling breath of the weapon]
Don't mess around
(Soldier 2) It's true
You definitely need this to go to the control room
If you don't believe me, take it out and throw it yourself
[Rising music]
[Soldier 2's strained groan]
[The weapon's strained groan]
[Soldier 2's urgent breath]
[Gunshot]
[Soldier 2's pained groan]
‎[The moaning of the weapon's power]
‎[The moaning of the soldier in pain]
‎[The shout of soldier 1]
‎[The moaning in pain]
‎[Fighting loudly]
‎(Worker) Don't touch it, it's a bomb
‎(Jun-ho) A bomb?
‎(Worker) This passage was created to evacuate
‎the VIPs in an emergency
‎Once everyone gets out
‎we'll blow it up
‎and bury this place
‎(Jun-ho) Who are the VIPs?
‎(Worker) Mind your own business
‎[Tense music]
(Worker) Number 29
[Weapon's labored breathing]
[Radio signal tone]
(Soldier 1) Emergency, the doctor is escaping!
[Button operation sound]
(Manager 1) Geez, what is this...
[Weapon's urgent breathing]
(Weapon) Damn it!
[Weapon's urgent groan]
[Weapon's urgent breathing]
[Weapon's strained groan]
[Weapon's rough groan]
(Worker) Why are you curious about who the VIP is?
(Junho) Thank you.
Diving equipment and even a secret passage
Seems like everything has been prepared for us
(Worker) You're not just curious, are you?
Your voice seems different too?
Can I see your face?
(Junho) Do we really have to do this?
[Tense music]
(Worker) Should I kill you to confirm?
Who are you?
[Junho clicks the gun]
[A knife clatters to the ground]
Can I see your face?
Should I kill you to confirm?
[The rough grunt of a weapon]
‎[The door suddenly opens]
‎Don't come any closer! Lee
‎[The rough breathing of a soldier]
‎(Soldier 1) Calm down, we can still handle this
‎How can we handle it?
‎By killing me?
‎(Soldier 1) Think about it
‎Why would I kill you?
‎Then it would just get worse
‎The situation has already escalated
‎Your friend is dead
‎(Soldier 1) That guy was not my friend
‎The body of the guy you killed
‎I'll throw it in the incinerator and burn it.
Just burn it cleanly.
If a participant disappears
here, it becomes a problem.
One missing soldier
is no problem at all.
Who am I?
What matters now
is not who I am.
What's important right now is
Who is the person
that made you like this?
The people you call zombies.
A person who woke up during
surgery and is missing a kidney.
Do you know where
that one kidney is?
Here
It's inside this.
You gave it to me.
That person is my brother!
(Not a worker)!
[Trembling breath]
You're a woman.
I was a girl.
It's not a man.
(I soldier 1) I will definitely
figure out the game.
If we make more noise
here and get caught,
You and I are both
dying a dog's death.
Believe me.
There is still an opportunity.
How can I believe the
words of trash like you?
[The rough breathing
of the weapon]
[The surprised
breath of the weapon]
[Soldier 1 quickly
removes the mask]
[Breath Sounds of Effort]
(Guard 1) Look
I'm just like you.
[The tense breathing
of the weapon]
Yeah.
(Guard 1) Now ‎All you
have to do is quietly go back.
If you only come
back before bedtime,
We can both live.
[Shaky Breaths]
(Weapon) Then what should I do?
(Soldier 1) Doctor先生
[ tense music ]
Let's go wash that face first.
‎[Gunfire] ‎[Screams of Soldier 1]
Really.
It was a woman.
How can I trust what you say?
‎(Worker) Before that
year divided the sea.
We even did that while
we were taking turns.
You don't think I would
do that to a man, do you?
If you don't believe
me, check the list.
- List?
- I have the participant list (workers).
personal information
is written on
Even the hospital records.
Where?
[Shivering breath]
On the ladder passage
There's a commander room.
Captain?
(Worker) Did you see it too?
A person wearing
a different mask
[The Worker’s Laughter]
Here
I'll help you find
your brother, okay?
Long-term gambling money
I'll give you all
of this, I swear!
When we become one team...
[Gunshot]
[sigh]
[The soldier's painful groans]
‎(Captain) Whether you take
organs out of corpses and sell them
Whether to chew the whole bag.
I'm not interested.
But you all
You've messed up the
most important thing here.
[The soldier's
labored breathing]
[Breath of Fear]
It's equality.
In this game, everyone is equal.
All participants compete fairly
under the same conditions.
To those who have suffered from inequality
and discrimination in the outside world.
It's giving us one last chance
to fight equally and win.
You broke that principle.
[Breath of Fear]
I'm sorry.
‎[Gunshot] ‎[Soldier
1's Strained Moan]
[Dark Music]
[The weapon's bewildered breath]
‎[Gunshot]
[ sigh ]
[Sound of strained breathing]
(Administrator 2) Captain
I found one more guy.
[tense music]
[scanner operating sound]
[Quivering breath]
[Moan of exertion]
[Harsh breathing]
[Scanner operating sound]
(Administrator
2) It's number 28.
There's one more guy (the boss).
The one who killed this bastard.
(It seems that the person
has already gone out to sea.)
(The Captain) The number
of dive holes is the same.
Still inside.
Find
[ tense music ]
[The siren is sounding]
[Man 3's tired groan]
[Meaningful music]
[Flashlight operation sound]
Squid Game Record
[The siren is ringing]
‎[Walkie-talkie signal sound]
(Administrator 3) Number
29 has also disappeared.
‎(Captain) locate
‎[radio operation sound]
(It cannot be seen on CCTV.)
‎(Captain) It must
be inside here.
[Announcement Voice] Participants,
please line up in the center immediately.
I say this once again.
(Soldier 3) Everyone,
come to the center.
[Guidance Voice] Participants are requested
to line up in the center immediately.
(Hyunseong 4) Move quickly.
(A guy 3) Hey, you bastards Why
are you making a fuss again, shit
[Man 3's cough]
(Brother 6) Brother, it
seems that guy the doctor...
(Soldier 3) Wake up
Wake up
Hurry up
‎(Gi-hun) The old
man isn’t feeling well.
[Significant music]
‎[The drawer creaks open]
6th round winner list
(Junho) 'Hwang In-ho'
[Junho's surprised breath]
2015년
[Joon-ho's surprised breath]
No. 132
Brother
[Dark music]
Subtitles: Ahn Hyun-jung