Netflix series
[Dark music]
[Walkie-talkie signal sound]
(Chief) Who is the intruder?
(Administrator 1) I
still haven't found it.
(Chief) Must find it.
VIPs will arrive soon.
[Snicker]
Mr. Deoksoo
Are you here now?
You
How…
Why?
Do you really think your dead mother
has come back to life?
[snickers]
The guys wearing masks call me a “kkakdugi”
They say that someone left alone
is a “kkakdugi”!
Hey, you’ve heard of that too, right?
“Kkakdugi!”
[the beauty laughs]
(Beauty) And then they nicely
took me back to the accommodation?
[laughs]
What
Not abandoning the marginalized is
what the kids from back in the day
When playing, a beautiful rule was kept?
Ha, fuck
Isn't it so cool?
[Laughter]
[Phone ringing]
[Approaching footsteps]
(Leader) [In English] I am the Frontman.
I’m glad you enjoyed the game.
Yes, the host is
waiting for the arrival of the VIPs.
[Tense music]
[The leader shakes a gun]
(Leader) [In Korean] Are you in here now?
You made one mistake.
I always put the receiver down the other way around.
The bullet you fired,
is from a Smith & Wesson M60 revolver.
It's the gun used by the Korean police.
What is the police doing here?
All alone, without a partner,
you seem to have a lot of questions,
come out and talk to me.
I don't know how you got in,
but you can't leave here
without my permission.
[The door clicks open]
[Switch operation sound]
[The captain's tense breathing]
‎[The captain's tense breathing]
‎[Radio signal sound]
‎(Administrator 1) A body has been found.
‎(Captain) Where?
‎(Administrator 1) On the northern coast of the island.
‎[The captain's sigh]
‎[Displeased breathing]
‎[Sniffling]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎(Sang-woo) Don't be so dramatic.
‎It was just an old man we met for the first time here.
‎[Sang-woo's sigh]
‎That person was
‎his wife.
‎[Dark music]
‎[Scanner operating sound]
(Administrator 2) The police ID has come out.
[Flashlight operating sound]
[Walkie-talkie signal sound]
(Administrator 3) The VIPs have arrived.
(Leader) Burn the body.
[Slams the wallet shut]
[Sobbing]
Oh, let's stop now.
I can't do this anymore.
[Crying]
They say if more than half agree,
we can stop.
If just nine people agree,
we can leave here.
Hey, does anyone want to go outside?
Is there anyone who wants to go out with me?
Please get up from your seat.
[Embarrassed groan]
(Man 1) Ah! Are you guys human?
[Dark music]
Are you really going to keep doing this insane thing?
Because of that money!
You guys killed the people you were closest to
inside here.
Because of that money
[Sobbing]
(Sangwoo) If you get out of here
If you get out of here,
will your wife come back alive?
Will you even get forgiveness for killing your wife?
If you're in such pain, why have you lived?
You should have died instead of your wife
That
is not just your wife's life
but the value of all the lives of those who died here
You want to just leave that?
Go out and start again from the bottom
to live with this ridiculous life
and this ridiculous guilt?
[Man 1 continues to sob]
Do you really have the confidence to live like that?
If you can live like that, everyone get up right now.
Get up and go outside!
‎[Heavy breathing]
‎[Knocking sound is heard]
‎(Captain) The VIPs have arrived.
‎[Elevator arrival sound]
‎(Captain) [In English] Nice to meet you.
‎Thank you for your long journey.
‎I am responsible for the operation of this place, assisting the host.
‎It is an honor to have you here.
‎(VIP1) Where is the host?
‎(Captain) I apologize, but...
The host is unable to be here due to unavoidable circumstances.
(VIP2) What?
I can't believe they are missing on a day like this.
(Captain) They asked me to
convey their apologies on their behalf.
(VIP3) Is there a problem
with the remaining schedule?
(Captain) No, this issue is just a
personal matter of the host.
The remaining games will proceed
without any problems.
You will not be disappointed.
(VIP4) I hope that's true.
I don’t want to act picky either
‎[VIP4's laughter]
‎But my expectations for this game are really high
‎It would be better if you don’t disappoint me
‎(Captain) Let’s go
‎[Button clicking sound]
‎[Man 2 prays]
‎[Elegant music starts playing]
‎(VIP1) I can’t help but wonder what the next game is
‎Why don’t you give me a little hint?
‎(Captain) I wish I could, but
‎If you know in advance
‎It might actually diminish your interest
‎(VIP2) This tournament has been
‎really exciting so far
‎(VIP3) Right, I think this
‎Korean tournament is the best so far
‎(Captain) Thank you
‎You will find the next game
‎even more enjoyable
‎[The door slams shut]
‎(VIP1) So that’s why we came this far
‎No matter how well the broadcast is done
‎Nothing can beat the thrill of watching it live
‎(VIP4) No way!
‎Stop, you bastard!
‎You idiot!
‎(VIP1) Why are you so distressed?
‎(VIP4) I bet that guy
‎will win the final championship
‎[Laughter of VIPs]
‎(VIP2) How much did you bet?
‎(VIP4) A million dollars!
‎[Sigh from VIP2]
‎(VIP3) What did you see in 69
‎that made you bet that much?
‎(VIP4) Ah, the number is good, 69!
‎[Laughter of VIPs]
‎(VIP1) You really revealed it
‎[Laughter of VIP1]
‎(Captain) You can bet again
‎before the next game starts.
Please rest in your room for a moment.
I will see you shortly when the game is ready.
(VIP1) I bet you’re looking forward to it.
(VIP5) Who are you going to bet on?
. Smart guy? Strong guy?
- (VIP2) Who are you betting on this time?
- (VIP6) I’m going with the strong guy.
- (VIP1) I haven’t decided yet.
- (VIP6) Number 101, how about you?
(VIP1) I’m still considering.
[Tense music]
[It’s shift change time]
[Bright music starts playing]
‎[The buzzer sounds]
‎[The door opens with a rattle]
‎[Meaningful music]
‎[Guidance voice] 69th eliminated
‎[Snicker]
‎[The sound of a piggy bank working]
‎[Elegant music starts to play]
‎[Guidance voice] In a moment
‎the fifth game will begin
‎Participants, please move
‎according to the guidance of the staff
‎(VIP2) [In English] How did you do this time?
‎Did you get a lot right?
‎(VIP1) [Sighing] No
Everything is dropping as we choose.
‎(VIP2) The real competition starts now.
‎Big bets begin from here.
‎How long will it take?
‎(VIP1) Let's double it this time.
‎(VIP2) Is that okay?
‎I don't even know what game it is.
‎(VIP1) It doesn't matter what it is.
‎We're going for it with guts.
‎(VIP4) What's the next game?
‎Enough with the reveals now.
‎(VIP2) It seems like you're getting anxious because of number 69.
‎Shall we let you know now?
‎(Captain) Then.
Now I will reveal the next game.
‎[Meaningful sound
effect] ‎(VIP4) What is that?
(VIP1) What kind of bridge is that?
(VIP2) It looks fun.
(VIP4) What the hell is that?
[Sangwoo's sigh]
[Guidance voice] [Korean] Welcome to the fifth
game.
Before starting the game,
please select one number tag
from 1 to 16 hanging on the mannequin in front of you.
Once again, I will inform you
before starting the game,
the number tags hanging on the mannequin in front of you.
Please select one
number ticket from 1 to 16.
[Elegant music flows out]
(VIP1) It's interesting
Actually, the outcome of this game
will be decided here
(VIP2) There will be variables, but
the number is still the most important, right?
(VIP3) What number did you choose this time?
(VIP4) 96
(VIP3) Any reason for that?
(VIP4) If you flip 69
it becomes 96, doesn't it?
[Laughter from the VIPs]
(VIP1) I wish you good luck
(VIP2) Where did you meet someone like this?
‎(VIP1) I'm a stranger
‎I thought you brought me here
‎(VIP2) No way
‎[Laughter from VIPs]
‎(VIP1) You're an interesting person
‎(Gi-hun) [Korean] The remaining person is sixteen
‎The number is also 16
‎[Sang-woo's tense breathing]
‎The day God created humans on this earth
‎was the sixth day
‎God
‎created innocent and pure humans
‎It's about going back to that day
‎[Tense breathing]
‎[Man 3's sigh]
‎Yeah
‎Lucky number 7
‎[Deoksoo's urgent breathing]
‎[Deoksoo's strained groan]
‎[The beauty's flustered breathing]
‎[Mintae's urgent breathing]
‎[Elegant music flows out]
‎(VIP2) [English] Indeed
‎the middle numbers come out first
‎(VIP1) It's the nature of animals
‎When they feel fear
‎they want to hide among the groups
‎(Gihoon) [Korean] Ah, what should I do?
The middle part has completely fallen out.
[Elegant music is playing]
(VIP3) [English] Now the choice is left.
In front or behind.
[VIP2 clicks their tongue]
(VIP2) It would be hard for me to choose too.
(Captain) Then, may I help with your choice?
(VIP1) Yeah, give us a hint.
(VIP5) Have mercy on the desperate!
(VIP6) Hurry up.
[Button pressing sound]
[Guide voice] [Korean] I would like to inform you.
The number in front
of you right now is
The order of starting the next game is as follows
Please choose carefully
‎(Gi-hun) Order?
Order, you say?
[Significant music]
Yeah
If it's the order of playing the game
the earlier number has an advantage
There’s a high possibility that this game, like 'Mugunghwa's flower' or a lottery
will have a time limit
It’s better to start first
No
Wait a minute
I don't even know what kind of game it is
It’s risky to go first
If it’s a later number like in tug-of-war
You can plan the operation by looking at the situation in front of you.
[Nervous breathing]
(Gi-hun) Number 16?
Number 16 can't be done.
[Running footsteps]
I don't want to do it at the end.
[Hasty breathing]
[Gi-hun's urgent moan]
(Gi-hun) Number 1?
Shall we start the game first?
Ah, then at the end?
Ah, that doesn't seem right either.
Ah, Seong Gi-hun!
‎(VIP1) [English] In the end, ‎the two numbers
at both ends are left. ‎[Elegant music plays]
‎(VIP2) Hmm, it's an
order that I'd like to
avoid both the
beginning and the end.
‎(VIP3) It must
be quite frightening
to start the game
where your life is at stake
‎first, right?
‎(VIP1) But thinking about how most of the people who started last in the first game ‎died due to time
over, it must be terrifying to draw number 16. ‎(VIP3) You said you were with number 96, right? ‎[Responds]
‎(VIP4) Pick well, please.
[Suspicious Moan]
What are you doing?
(Man 4) Excuse me
[Nervous Breathing]
[Trembling Voice] Can I
‎do number 1?
I’ve spent my whole life hiding behind
and just watching others.
I’ve never lived my life
as the main character, not even once.
Even when I tell myself
not to be that way, I always get scared.
Today, in the end, I just watched
others again
and ended up at the back.
I want to experience
life properly, at least just once.
[Choking up] Please
stand up front with confidence.
[Requesting]
[Gi-hun's Sigh]
[Elegant Music Plays]
‎(Man 4 in the video) Thank you, thank you!
[Man 4 in the video expresses gratitude]
‎(VIP 4) Fuck!
Damn it!
.[Laughter from the VIPs]
‎(VIP 1) What do we do?
‎(VIP 2) 69, 96 all failed
[Laughter from the VIPs]
‎(VIP 4) Damned guy
You son of a bitch!
(The Leader) Now, we will start the game.
[Exciting music]
‎(VIP2) Isn't it longer?
‎(VIP1) Much longer.
‎[Guide voice] [Korean] Welcome to the fifth
game.
‎Participants, we welcome you.
‎The fifth game is
‎Crossing the Stepping Stones.
‎In front of you, there is a pair of glasses.
‎They consist of two types of glass.
‎Tempered glass and regular glass.
‎Tempered glass is strong enough to support the weight of two people, but
Ordinary glass
breaks even if one person steps on it
Participants
must determine which of the pair of glasses in front of them
is tempered glass
They step on them
and pass through eighteen pairs of legs
If they safely cross to the other side
it’s a pass
So this number is…
(Admin 4) The order of crossing the bridge
[nervous breathing]
How do you distinguish which is tempered glass?
[VIP 4's discontented groan]
(VIP4) [English] Stupid bastard
(VIP4 exhales)
Bring the whiskey here
Hey, you!
(VIP4) It's annoying to call again
Sit here
(Junho) I have to serve others too
(VIP4) I want to leave this here
Is there anyone against it?
(VIP1) Not at all, leave it there
(VIP5) Do whatever you want
[Guidance Voice] [Korean] The time limit is
16 minutes
You have to cross the bridge in 16 minutes.
Then I will start the game.
Take off your shoes in order and
go up on the bridge.
[Tense music]
[Man 4's trembling breath]
(Man 5) What are you doing? There's no time!
- (Man 6) Hurry up and get up!
- (Min-tae) Run fast!
- (Man 5) Are you just going to stand there?
- (Deok-su) Hey.
If you don't go out, I will push you.
Um, I, I will go.
You can go, right?
‎(Woman 1) Please choose well, okay?
‎[Man 4's trembling breath]
‎[People's surprised gasps]
‎[Tense sound effect]
‎(Man 3) Great job! Yeah, keep going, okay?
‎Good, good
‎[Woman 1's surprised breath]
‎(Woman 1) That, that's right, yeah
‎[Trembling breath]
‎You can go like that, one by one
‎Oh, great job
‎[People speak one after another]
‎Great job, great job
‎[Nervous breathing]
‎[People's astonished moans]
‎[The glass shatters]
‎- (VIP5) It's a fail
‎- (VIP1) Oh dear
‎(VIP1) Number 96 is gone too
‎(VIP2) Ah, that's unfortunate
‎[VIP2's exclamation]
‎You've already found another fun
‎[VIP2's laughter]
‎(VIP4) Your eyes are pretty
‎[Tense music]
‎[Woman 1's trembling breath]
‎[Frightened moan]
‎[Woman 1's pondering moan]
‎[Woman 1's trembling breath]
‎[In Korean] First on the left
‎The second on the right
‎[Glass shatters loudly]
‎[Woman 1's scream]
‎- (Man 2) You can do it, yeah
‎- (Man 3) You can do it
‎- (Min-tae) Hurry up!
‎The glass in front
‎- (Min-tae) Hurry up already!
‎- (Man 7) Fifteen lines
‎(Man 6) What are you doing? Run!
- (Beauty) We don't have time for this!
- (Man 7) If I get all of these right
- The probability of going all the way is
- (Woman 2) We can do it
- (Man 8) We can do it!
- 2 to the power of 15
[Nervous breathing]
- 1 in 32,768
[Forced laughter]
- Fuck
[Tense breathing]
[People's surprised groans]
[Man 7's scream]
[People's shocked gasps]
[Tense music]
[Tense breathing]
- (Man 8) Ma'am
Maybe
Do you remember which side that person stepped on earlier?
I suddenly can't remember
[Woman 2's flustered moan]
It was so quick that...
Think carefully
If I guess right, you’ll live too
That...
It seems like it was the left
(Man 2) No, he went to the right first
then went to the left!
(Man 3) Ah, no, no, no
he went straight to the left
(Man 9) No, it was right from there
‎[Trembling breath]
‎Outside, left
‎Are you sure?
‎(Woman 2) Yes
‎[Nervous breath]
‎[Takes a deep breath]
‎[Glass shatters]
‎[Man 8's scream]
‎[Man 8 falls with a thud]
‎[Flustered groan]
‎It was the right side, huh?
‎(VIP 2) [In English] Number 5 was wrong
‎(VIP 1) You've lost credibility
‎(VIP 4) Take off your mask
‎[Laughter from the VIPs]
‎I said take off your mask
‎I want to see your face
‎[Meaningful Music]
‎[VIPs' Excited Gasps]
‎(Gi-hun) [Korean] The remaining legs are ten lines
‎The remaining people are eleven
‎If just one or two clear the way in front
‎We can all cross to one side
‎(Sang-woo) Not necessarily
‎If the scared people at the front
‎Start to stall for time
‎We in the back will be in danger too
‎[Nervous Breathing]
‎[Trembling Breathing]
‎(Man 2) Our Father in Heaven
What are you doing right now?
‎[Man 2 is praying]
‎(Man 3) Are you praying there?
‎(Man 9) What are you doing in front?
‎(Min-tae) There's no time, hurry up!
‎(Man 3) Hey, don't mess around and get up quickly
‎It's your turn, you bastard!
‎[Tense music]
‎I said hurry up
‎Because of you, everyone is dying!
‎In God's calling,
‎there's no turn
‎The day of judgment is approaching.
We're all the same anyway.
You're going to hell.
Send that person
forward somehow.
(Man 9) If not, I might
have to push you.
[Trembling breath]
(Deoksoo) If you don't want to
die first, send that praying
bastard forward. [Trembling breath]
(Man 3) Get up, you bastard.
[Man 2's strained groan]
I said move forward, you crazy bastard!
[Man 3's scream]
[Rough breathing]
[Significant sound effect]
[Laughter]
[Tense breath]
Thank
you, Lord.
‎[Man 2's scream]
‎[Man 2 thuds down]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Deoksoo's rough breathing]
‎[Man 9's scared breathing]
Don't push me
‎I'll go
‎Don't worry
‎Why would I kill you?
‎You have to cross for me to live, okay?
‎[Scared groan]
‎[Nervous breathing]
‎[People's moving footsteps]
‎[Uneasy breathing]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Flustered breath]
‎(Dawn) It's to the left
‎[Surprised groan]
‎I said it's to the left
‎Pull yourself together
‎Uh, uh
‎[Gi-hoon's straining groan]
‎[Gi-hoon's trembling groan]
‎Thank you
‎[Gi-hoon's rough breathing]
‎[Straining groan]
‎[Scared breathing]
‎(Deoksoo) You did well
‎Just keep doing that
‎[Man 9 taps the glass]
‎I think I can tell what tempered glass is
‎Really?
‎Is it really distinguishable?
I have a feeling.
The color is different.
[Man 9's trembling breath]
[Man 9's scream]
[Man 9 falls down]
[Nervous breathing]
(Deoksu) Crazy bastard
What do you even know?
[Trembling breath]
Hey, you fucking guys!
[Tense music]
[Rough breathing]
I’m not going any further here!
If you want to go, you go first!
Ah, shit
(VIP2) [English] Ah, this is getting fun.
(Junho) We must not have
our faces revealed in here.
(VIP4) Right now, you're mine here
(Junho) After you leave
I will kill me
[VIP4's laughter]
(VIP4) If you don't do what I say right now
I'll kill you before I leave
(Junho) Please
Take me
To a place where just the two of us can be
(VIP6) It's so much fun, where are you going?
(VIP4) Enjoy the fun
I need to find a different kind of fun
(VIP2) Ah, are you really going to do 69 now?
[Laughter from VIPs]
(VIP6) [French] Enjoy your meal!
(VIP5) [English] Have a good time
[Min-tae's embarrassed groan]
[Korean] What the hell are you doing?
Can't you understand Korean?
I'm not going anymore
Don't be stubborn
Going in order is the rule
[Laughter]
Fuck off, you bastard.
This place is hell
Where are the rules in hell?
If you want to go, you can either go first
You fucker!
If you don't go, I'll push you out
Yeah
Okay, fuck
Everyone come in!
(Deoksu) We all die together!
Hey, you fuckers!
I don't want to die instead of you
So come at me! Shit
[Deoksu's rough breathing sounds]
You can either go first
Or die together here
Choose one of the two
Don't be pretentious,
you son of a bitch.
Time passes, but you don't go, huh?
Then you can try waiting until you die
[Laughter]
[Deoksu's laughter]
(Mintae) Fuck
[Sigh]
[VIP4's rough breaths]
[VIP4's exclamation]
[The mask suddenly drops]
[VIP4's rough breaths]
(VIP4) [English] It's a waste of a beautiful face to hide inside a mask
(VIP4) If you
satisfy me
within 5 minutes
Your life could change
‎[VIP4's trembling breath]
‎[VIP4's scream]
‎Are you satisfied?
‎[VIP4's painful moan]
‎[VIP4's frightened moan]
‎(Junho) If you satisfy me in 5 minutes
‎I might spare your life
‎[responding]
‎[trembling breath]
‎[recording notification sound]
‎Tell me everything you know about this game
‎[meaningful music]
‎[Deok-soo's trembling breath]
(민태) Fuck, aren't you going soon?
Hurry up and go!
‎(미녀) You go instead.
‎[민태's embarrassed moan]
‎[민태's scream]
‎[민태 falls with a thud]
‎[rough breathing]
‎[snort]
‎Fucking idiots
‎[trembling breath]
‎Just because you have two balls
‎you act all high and mighty
‎Going, not going
‎Ha, fuck, what a shame
‎Fuck off, you fucking bitch.
No matter how much
you whine, I'm not going.
[LOL]
(Beauty) Deoksu
I feel so ashamed for having been with a piece of trash like you
I really want to die from embarrassment
Then go die first
Get out of the way
Really?
Ha, you’re saying you’ll go first?
(Beauty) Yeah
I’m a beauty
I’m not going to die
living like a pathetic piece of trash like you
[LOL]
Then I’m thankful
(Deoksu) Choose wisely
[Tense music]
‎[The Beautiful One's Trembling
Breath] ‎[A Flustered Moan]
What are you doing?
Naive bastard
Did you really think I
would die in your place?
[Half-laugh]
(Duksoo) Solve this.
(Beauty) Don't you remember?
I told you to go all
the way together.
This crazy bitch, fuck!
Let go of this,
you fucking bitch!
[The Strengthening Moans
of Deoksu and the Beauty]
Dog shit
If you betray me
You said you would die, right?
Don't do this.
I'll go first, okay?
[The Beautiful Woman's
Hollow Laughter]
Please solve this,
I'm begging you.
Let it go!
‎(Beautiful) coward brat
Deoksu, hey.
Do you know that?
You're really small as hell.
This fucking!
‎[Deoksu's urgent
moan] ‎[Laughter]
[Duksu's Scream]
(VIP1) [English] It's a
very dramatic ending.
(VIP2) 'When a woman harbors resentment,
even in May and June, frost falls.'
(VIP1) Shakespeare I
didn't know you liked him.
(VIP6) Actually, it's not
Shakespeare. It's William Congreve.
I preferred it when you
kept your mouth shut.
[VIP1's Sigh]
‎(Captain) Check the VIP room.
[Meaningful music]
[There are screams]
‎[The Sigh of VIP2]
[VIPs' Laughter]
[Quivering Breath]
‎[Rough breathing]
‎[The timer ticks]
What are you doing?
(Sangwoo) Don't waste time.
(Man 5) Okay, okay,
okay, wait a minute.
I know how to distinguish.
How?
I worked at a glass
factory for 30 years.
I can't see other people, but
(Man5) Tempered glass If you look at it
at an oblique angle, it reflects the light.
I see something
like a faint stain.
[Man 5's strained
breathing] [Significant music]
[Shaking breath]
[Nervous breathing]
[The trembling
breath of Sangwoo]
Another thing is sound.
Tempered glass is
Because it is made at a high
temperature of over 700 degrees.
When you hit it with something like a hammer,
the sound is clearer than regular glass.
Why are you saying that now?
(Gihun) If you had taken
the lead from the beginning...
(Man 5) Why me?
They are the people who wanted to
kill me whenever they had the chance.
[VIP1's lament]
(VIP1) [English] Can you
really tell the difference?
It seems like that.
According to the
(captain) records
I am a participant with
experience as a glass technician.
(VIP1) Was there such
content? Why didn't I know?
(VIP2) I couldn't see it either.
(VIP3) The game is
going to get boring.
(VIP1) Number 13 definitely seems to
be moving as if it's seeing something.
It seems to be
utilizing light reflection.
I will try changing
the settings.
Power off
It seems like it has an effect?
(VIP2) Yes, now you
seem to lack self-confidence.
[Male 5's embarrassed breathing]
(Sangwoo) [Korean] What's wrong?
What's the problem?
[The Awkward Breathing of Man 5]
(I can't see well
because it's dark.)
[Man 5's trembling breath]
‎[A knocking sound is heard]
(Administrator 5)
[English] Excuse me
[Walkie-talkie signal tone]
‎(Manager 5) [Korean]
The VIP has collapsed.
(Is the captain) alive?
‎(Administrator 5) You are safe.
Who is the (leader) intruder?
(Manager 5) We are searching.
[The Captain's Sigh]
‎[Sangwoo's frantic breathing]
‎(Sangwoo) Which side is
it? Make a decision now!
You need to listen to the sound.
Is there nothing
you want to throw?
(Sangwoo) What,
isn't there anything?
[Trembling breath]
[Man 5's tense breathing]
[Man 5's strained breathing]
Give me one more.
Oh, you have to listen
to the right sound too.
[Changwoo's Sigh]
[The Captain's Sigh]
[The Awkward Breathing of Man 5]
(Man 5) Uh, I don't know.
(Sang-woo) Then just go.
[Man 5's embarrassed moan]
[The scream of man 5]
[Surprised breath]
‎[Surprised breath]
‎[Man 5 falls with a thud]
[Intense breathing]
[Chang-woo's sigh of relief]
[Surprised breath]
‎[Tense music] ‎[Urgent
breaths of dawn]
[The Breath of Dawn
and Ki-hoon's Strength]
‎[Timer end sound]
[The rough breaths of people]
‎[A crashing sound is heard]
‎[People's astonished breaths]
[Exciting music]
[Seongwoo's Painful Moan]
[Heavy breathing]
[Strenuous Groan]
[Surprised breath]
The door bangs.
[Radio signal sound]
‎(Admin 5) One piece of diving
equipment has disappeared.
‎[VIPs are making a fuss] ‎It seems
they have gone into an underwater cave.
(Scout) Track the location and keep
the boat on standby [Tense music]
(VIP2) [English] It
was the best game.
‎(VIP1) That was great!
‎[Cheers from the VIPs]
[Machine operating sound]
[Groaning with effort]
[Heavy breathing]
Subtitle: Ahn Hyun-jeong