Netflix series
‎[Calm music]
‎(Administrator) 218 and 456
‎Welcome to the final game
‎Before the game
‎We will conduct a coin toss
‎Choose between triangle and square
‎Triangle
‎(Administrator) It's triangle
‎Choose between attack and defense
‎[Inhale]
‎Attack
‎(Administrator) 456 attacks
‎[Sigh]
‎218 defends
‎(Administrator) The final sixth game is
‎[The door slams shut]
It's Squid Game.
‎(VIP1) [English] 'Squid Game'
‎That's a fun name.
‎(Captain) A long time ago in Korea,
‎it was a game that children played a lot.
‎[VIP1 reacts]
‎(Manager) [Korean] Let me explain the
‎rules of Squid Game.
‎First, the attacker
‎enters the drawing of the squid
‎and must break through the defenders
‎and step on the head of the squid drawing
‎with their foot to win.
‎Second, the defender must...
If you push out of
the picture, you win.
Thirdly, either the
attacker or the defender
If the game cannot be continued
the other side wins
The state in which the game cannot be continued
What kind of state is it?
(Administrator) It refers to the state in which a participant
is deceased
Now we will start the game
[Heavy music]
(Captain) [English] Among the children's games
it was the most physical and violent game
(VIP2) In this game,
is any kind of violence allowed?
(Captain) Yes, there are no restrictions at all
‎[Heavy Breathing]
‎[Taking Deep Breaths]
‎(VIP1) Why are you moving on one foot?
‎(Captain) The attacker has a handicap
‎so before crossing the waist of the drawing
‎you must move on one foot
‎(VIP2) Then the defender has to block that
‎(Captain) Yes
‎That's the first point of this game
‎[Korean] Did we do this a lot when we were kids?
‎[Nervous Breathing]
‎Do you remember?
‎What did we say when we passed by here?
Don't say useless things...
‎[Tense music]
‎[Sang-woo's strained groan]
‎[Sang-woo coughs]
‎[Sang-woo's labored breathing]
‎[Rough breathing]
‎The secret inspector
‎I said I'm a secret inspector
‎[The sky rumbles]
‎[Rough breathing]
‎[VIP3 speaks in Chinese]
‎[VIP2's admiration]
‎(VIP2) [in English] It sounds romantic
‎What does it mean?
‎(VIP3) 'Good rain knows when to fall'
‎It's a line from a poem by Du Fu.
[English] It was a kid who was going to die anyway.
I just ended the pain quickly.
Don't talk carelessly.
He was alive.
He could have been saved.
So I killed him.
Because you're that kind of person.
Because you're the kind of person who could give up everything to save that kid.
Is that it?
Are you worried that I'm going to quit the game?
Yeah!
If you and that kid quit,
everything will be over.
I have to leave here with no money!
If it wasn't for that kid...
You died by this knife back then.
That money
You can never take it out of here.
[Sarcastic laugh]
[Tense music]
[Gihun is panting]
[They fight noisily]
[Sangwoo's scream]
[Sangwoo gets slashed by the knife]
[Sangwoo's strained groan]
[Sangwoo gets punched hard]
[Sangwoo's groan]
[They fight noisily]
(Sangwoo) Bastard!
[Sangwoo's shout]
[They fight noisily]
‎[Gi-hun and Sang-woo's painful moans]
‎[Gi-hun's surprised moan]
‎[Sang-woo's rough moan]
‎[Sang-woo's shout]
‎[Gi-hun's scream] ‎(Sang-woo) Die! ‎[Sang-woo's
straining moan] ‎[Gi-hun's painful moan]
‎Die!
‎[Sang-woo's straining moan]
‎[Gi-hun's painful moan]
‎[Sang-woo's painful moan]
‎[Gi-hun's scream]
‎[dark music]
‎[Sang-woo and Gi-hun fight noisily]
‎[Gi-hun's scream]
‎[painful moan]
‎[Sang-woo's rough breathing]
‎[Gi-hun's moan]
[Struggling Groan]
Do you remember this place?
Here
'The mugunghwa flower has bloomed' was played
[Struggling Breath]
‎(Sangwoo) All the people who were standing in the playground back then are dead
Everyone except me and you
[Gi-hun's Struggling Groan]
[Sangwoo's Rough Breathing]
We
Have come too far to turn back
[Sangwoo's Battle Cry]
[Gi-hun and Sangwoo's Straining Groans]
[Straining Groans]
[Screams]
[Rough Breathing]
[Spits]
[Struggling Groan]
[Sangwoo's Groan]
‎(Gi-hun) You killed them
[Gi-hun's Rough Breathing]
You were the one who killed them
You killed them
You are the one who killed them
[Gi-hun's Rough Groan]
[Groan of Pain]
[Rough Breathing]
[Struggling Groan]
‎[Gi-hun's Rough Groan]
[Battle Cry]
[Heavy Sound Effect]
[Dark Music]
[Struggling Breath]
[Gi-hun's Rough Breathing]
‎[Sniffing]
‎(VIP1) [English] The game is over.
‎(VIP2) Yes, it seems to be over.
‎[Gi-hun's strained groan]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Gi-hun's labored breathing]
‎[Korean] I won’t do it.
‎I will quit.
‎- (VIP2) [English] What are you doing?
‎- (VIP1) What…
‎(VIP3) What’s going on?
‎[Korean] 'Clause 3 of the consent form'
‎'If a majority of participants agree'
‎'The game will be suspended'
‎[Rough breathing]
If the two of us give up
It'll end here
[Rough breathing sounds]
[Radio signal sound]
(Manager) [In English] 456 says
he's going to give up
(VIP1) Are you saying you're giving up the prize?
We were just about to win?
(VIP2) Are you kidding right now?
[In Korean] Sangwoo
When we were young
[Trembling breath]
When we played like this with hyung
Mom would definitely call us to eat
But now no one calls anymore
‎[Calm music]
‎Let's go
‎Let's go home
‎[Sangwoo is choking up]
‎Hyung
‎I'm sorry
‎[Strenuous groan]
‎[Surprised groan]
‎[Gihun is choking up]
‎[Sangwoo is coughing]
‎[Sangwoo's strenuous groan]
‎S, s, Sangwoo
‎[Gihun is choking up]
‎(Gihun) S, s, Sangwoo
‎[Gihun's urgent groan]
‎(Sangwoo) Hyung
‎[Surprised breath]
(Gi-hoon) Ah, no, Sang-woo, don’t say it.
- Our mom, our mom
‎- (Gi-hoon) [sniffling] Sang-woo
‎[Gi-hoon’s trembling moan]
‎Our, our mom…
‎(Gi-hoon) Ah, no
‎Sang-woo, no
‎[sobbing] No, ah, no
‎[wailing]
‎(Gi-hoon) Sang-woo
‎No, ah…
‎Ah, Sang-woo
‎[Gi-hoon’s crying]
‎[Gi-hoon screams]
‎[The captain sets down the bottle]
Congratulations on your victory.
It was an amazing match.
(Gi-hun) Why?
Why are you doing this?
(Captain) You like horse racing, right?
You are, after all,
the horses in the racetrack.
That was unexpected.
I thought you wouldn't run for long.
Who are you?
Just think of it as a dream.
It wasn't such a bad dream for you, was it?
(Gi-hun) Who are you?
[Slams down the glass]
[Sigh]
Who are you?
‎[The gas hisses out]
‎[Rough breathing]
Who are you?
‎[Strained breathing]
‎[Gasping breath]
‎(Evangelist) Jesus heaven, disbelief hell!
‎O foolish ones who deny the Lord!
‎Repent, the day of
judgment is coming!
‎Jesus heaven, disbelief hell!
‎Only the pain of hellfire awaits
you ‎[The car door swings shut]
‎Kneel before the Lord!
‎Jesus heaven, disbelief
hell! ‎[Significant music]
‎[Strained Breathing]
‎[Surprised Breathing]
‎Believe in Jesus
‎[Strained Breathing]
‎[Gi-hun coughs]
‎[Gi-hun's labored groans]
‎[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
‎[Guide Voice] Checking the IC card information
‎Please press the button for the desired amount
‎[ATM Operating Sound]
‎[Guide Voice] Now
‎counting the cash
‎Please wait a moment
‎Please take the cash
‎(Sang-woo's Mom) Gi-hun
‎[Sang-woo's Mom's surprised breathing]
‎(Sang-woo's Mom) You, why do you look like that?
‎Did you get into a fight after drinking again?
‎[Sang-woo's Mom's sigh]
‎Wait a moment
‎(Sang-woo's Mom) Mackerel
‎Go eat with your mom
‎[Dark Music]
‎Where is your mom sick
‎Not answering the phone
‎She hasn't shown up for work since the other day
‎I should go check on her
‎But I've been so out of it that I couldn't go
‎[Sang-woo's Mom's sigh]
Ayu, it's fine, it's fine
If you have money, give it to mom
Don't spend it elsewhere
(Sangwoo's mom) Gi-hun
Um, these days
You haven't contacted
Sangwoo, have you?
No
Go inside
[A dog barks from afar]
(Gi-hun) Mom
I’m back
[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
Mom
(Gi-hun) Is mom here?
[Gi-hun rustles as he puts down the bag]
Mom, I’m back
Mom
‎[Dark Music]
‎Mom
‎Hey, open your eyes
‎(Gi-hoon) Mom, I'm here
‎I brought back some money
‎[Trembling Breaths]
‎[Gi-hoon is on the verge of tears]
‎[Subway Engine Sound]
‎Ah
‎Ah, our employee
‎has a barista certification
‎[The Door Clicks Open and Shut]
‎This is coffee brewed by them
‎I’m not sure if it will suit your taste
‎[Branch Manager's Laughter]
‎Why did you want to see me?
Ah, I'm sorry for making you come all the way here.
We were going to send you a car...
Why did you ask to meet?
Ah, that is...
You've had your money deposited in our bank for quite a while,
but you haven't said anything yet.
What do I
have to say?
Yes?
Ah, no
Oh, it's not like that.
[laughter]
Ah, that money is currently
in a regular savings account, and
well, there’s almost no interest there.
For VIPs like you,
We have started a
VIP-exclusive consulting service at our bank this time
I would like to introduce that
and also greet you
[smiling] I know you must be busy
so I asked to meet you like this
No,
I, did I do something rude…
(Gi-hun) Can I ask you for a favor?
Oh, yes, please go ahead
Could you lend me just 10,000 won?
What?
Oh, yes, sure, of course, yes
(Branch manager) Here…
‎(Old woman) Excuse me
‎Please buy some flowers
‎I beg you
‎If I can't sell this today
‎It will wither away
‎Thank you
‎(Old woman) Thank you
‎[Footsteps fading away]
‎[Gi-hun drops the flowers]
‎[Meaningful music]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Elevator arrival sound]
‎[The door shuts with a click]
‎[Medical device operating sound]
‎[Rough breathing]
‎[Sigh]
Can you give me some water?
Please
You…
Who are you?
[Il-nam's rough breathing]
(Il-nam) Over there
That man
Is he drunk?
He's been like that for hours
From the looks of him
[Trembling breath]
He looks like a homeless person
(Gi-hun) Is this all
What you did?
(Il-nam) If we leave him like that
He'll freeze to death soon
No one is here to help
Why did you do something like that?
‎[Sigh]
‎What would you do?
‎Answer me!
‎[Trembling breaths]
‎Why did you do that!
‎Stop in your tracks
‎Are you going to help
‎that smelly human trash?
‎Who are you!
‎Why did you save me!
‎(Il-nam) Let's play
‎one more game
‎until midnight
‎If that person is still here
‎I'll
‎someone
‎helps that person
‎then you win.
‎(Gi-hun) Stop talking nonsense
‎[Strained groan]
‎[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
‎I could kill you right now
‎(Il-nam) Oh, then
‎you'll never hear the answer
‎[Gi-hun's trembling breath]
‎If you play the game
‎I'll answer your question
‎[Il-nam's strained breathing]
‎[Wind blows fiercely]
‎[Clock ticks]
‎If you lose
‎I will kill you with my own hands
‎You will
What will you bet?
Whatever
If you want it anyway
you can take it all
[Struggling breath]
[The clock ticks]
You
Who are you?
(Il-nam) I'm
a person who rolls money
How could you earn money so easily
that you do this kind of thing?
(Il-nam) Money
You know it when you earn it too
Is it
easy?
You
How much is real
and how much is false?
Oil-nam
Is that your real name?
‎(Il-nam) Yes
‎That's my name
‎O Il-nam
‎It's true that
‎I have a tumor in my head
‎In the past
‎I lived in a neighborhood house
‎with my wife and son
‎[sigh]
‎Do you still
‎trust people?
‎(Il-nam) Even after going through that?
‎Why did you come looking for me?
‎I heard that
‎you didn’t even touch the prize money
‎and just lived as is
‎Is it like guilt?
Guilt?
[Quivering breath]
That doesn't seem like something you should say,
That money is
the result of your luck and
effort.
(Il-nam) You have the right to use that
Look at me
Life is
short
[The clock ticks]
[Quivering breath]
[A sigh]
(Gi-hoon) Why did you do that?
(Il-nam) You
are with someone who has no money at all.
Do you know what the common
trait of people with too much money is?
‎[Il-nam's trembling breath]
‎Living
‎isn't fun
‎If you have too much money
‎no matter what you buy, eat, or drink
‎[Il-nam's hollow laughter]
‎in the end, everything becomes trivial
‎At some point, my clients
‎started telling me one by one
‎that there’s no longer anything
‎enjoyable in life
‎So
‎everyone gathered
‎and thought about it a bit
‎'What would be'
‎'fun to do?'
‎Fun?
Doing such things for fun.
Did you say you made them do it?
‎(Il-nam) It seems you
‎have forgotten
‎I have never forced
‎anyone to play a game
‎Did you not come back on your own?
‎[The clock ticks]
‎(Il-nam) It seems your luck
‎has run out now
‎Really
‎Do you still
‎trust people?
‎(Gi-hun) Why did you
‎go inside that?
‎When I was young
‎[Calm music]
‎I had fun playing
‎whatever with my friends.
I didn't realize
time was passing.
Before I die
Must try once.
I wanted to feel it again.
Sitting in the audience
can never feel
that feeling
So
[Trembling breath]
Were you feeling good?
I asked why
I saved you?
Because it was fun
Playing with you
(Il-nam) Thanks to you
[The clock ticks]
Memories I couldn't even recall
from long ago
came flooding back
It was really
a long time
since it was that much fun
[A siren wails]
‎[Gi-hun's overwhelming breath]
‎You came
‎A person has come
‎[The clock chimes]
‎[The medical device beeps]
‎[The clock keeps ringing]
‎(Gi-hun) You saw it too, right?
‎You lost
‎[Il-nam's cough]
‎[A sigh]
‎You take care of the guests
‎(Captain) May I ask why you are doing this?
‎Seeing
‎is more fun than doing
‎[Dramatic music]
‎[A sigh]
(TV anchor) The pace of increase in household debt in our country is still
among the highest in the world. The Bank for International Settlements and the
Bank of Korea reported that as of the end of the third quarter last year, the
household debt ratio compared to Korea's GDP is... [Laughter from the hairdresser]
You've grown your hair a
lot. [News is playing on the TV]
What would you like me to do?
Would you like to cut it short?
Or if you're growing it out,
would you like me to perm it?
(TV anchor) Among 43
countries in the world,
The rise in household debt ratio in Korea is the largest after China.
The increase in the household debt ratio in Korea has become steep.
This began when the government eased loan regulations and
the Bank of Korea lowered interest rates.
[Bright music plays on TV]
[Gentle music]
[The wind blows]
(Gihoon) You're Cheol, right?
You really resemble my sister.
Uncle
Do you know my sister?
She's my sister's friend.
Then do you know where my sister is?
(Sangwoo’s mom) Is this the kid?
(Gihoon) Yes.
What's your name?
Cheol.
Kang Cheol.
Kang Cheol?
Oh my, that's a very manly name.
(Sangwoo’s mom) He looks
very brave too.
I would appreciate it.
(Sangwoo’s mom) Right.
Just add another spoon for the kid at the dinner table.
Don't worry and come back safely.
Yes.
(Sangwoo’s mom) Has Cheol eaten?
Oh my, come here and sit down.
Grandma will give you one bungeoppang.
Yes, eat it.
Oh dear, it's cold, what's this outfit?
Isn't there something warmer?
[Sang-woo's mother moans as she exerts herself]
[Sang-woo's mother opens the zipper straight]
[Sang-woo's mother's surprised breath]
[Opens the zipper straight]
[Breathes heavily as she exerts herself]
(Sang-woo's mother) Gi-hun!
Gi-hun!
[Entrance door alarm tone]
[Announcement voice] This stop is
Incheon Airport Terminal 1.
Incheon Airport
Terminal 1 Station.
(Gi-hun) Yeah, Dad, I'm
almost at the airport now.
I'm getting on the plane soon
So, I bought a gift for our Gayoung
[smiling] No, it's a secret
I'll show you in person when Dad meets you
‎[a sharp sound rings out]
‎[a man's angry groan]
Gayoung, wait a moment
Gayoung, Dad
will call again when I arrive
I love you too
‎[a sharp sound rings out]
‎[dark music]
‎(Man 1) Let's play one more game
Hurry!
‎[the approaching sound of a subway engine]
‎[Gihoon's urgent breathing]
‎[Gihoon's rough breathing]
‎(Man 1) What are you doing?
‎Give that to me!
‎(Gihoon) Hey, no!
‎[Rough breathing]
‎Absolutely not!
‎[Announcement voice] This is a final boarding
announcement from Uway Airlines.
‎Flight Uway
Airlines 202 to Los Angeles will be closing
boarding shortly.
‎Passengers departing for
Los Angeles, please proceed to gate 22 for boarding.
[The guide voice flows in English]
[Gi-hun's sigh]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Call connection sound]
(Male 2) Do you want to participate in the game?
If you wish to participate, please tell me your name and
your date of birth.
(Gi-hun) Seong Gi-hun
October 31, 1974
Listen carefully.
I'm not a thing.
I'm a person.
So I'm curious
[Gi-hun's sigh]
Who you are
how you can do
this to a person.
(Leader) Number 456
Don't think nonsense.
(Gi-hun) So I
can't forgive.
[Meaningful music]
What you are doing
(Leader) Get on that plane.
It will be good for you.
[Gi-hun's trembling breaths]
[Rising music]
Subtitle: Ahn Hyun-jeong