"Netflix series"
[Meaningful music]
[The rough breathing of weapons]
[Button operation sound]
[Elegant music flows out]
(Deoksoo) You did well.
(Sangwoo) Hyung Gi-hoon.
(Gi-hoon) Oh
No.
[Elegant music flows out]
(Il-nam) Thank you.
[Il-nam's laughter]
Yes?
I lived thanks to you.
[Il-nam and Gi-hoon's laughter]
(Ali) Bosses!
(Il-nam) Oh
[Sigh]
(Ali) Are you all alive?
I was worried.
Did you think I would die easily? Really…
I'm Seong Gi-hoon from Sangmundong.
[Il-nam's laughter]
Old boss, are you okay?
(Il-nam) Yes, I’m okay, yeah.
Thanks to this friend.
[Il-nam's laughter]
(Sangwoo) I’m sorry.
I shouldn’t have suggested tearing everything apart.
Ah, no.
It’s not like I knew that.
The umbrella was my choice too.
[Patting Sangwoo] It's okay.
Yeah, I'm glad everyone is safe
‎(Gi-hun) Uh
‎[Announcement voice] I will now inform you of the results of the second game
‎In the second game, out of 187 participants
‎[Dark music]
‎79 were eliminated
‎[Piggy bank sound]
‎[Announcement voice] The prize money accumulated from this game is
‎7.9 billion
‎The total prize money accumulated so far is
‎34.8 billion
‎[Elegant music plays]
‎[Announcement voice] It is now meal time.
Participants are requested to line up
in the center of the accommodation.
[Deoksoo's Hollow Laughter]
Is this it?
Son of a bitch
[Sigh]
You just gave me a piece of bread
And this is all you want me to eat after surviving a near-death experience?
[The Beauty Whispers]
[Man 1's Hollow Laughter]
(Man 1) Are you kidding me?
Alright, excuse me
(Man 2) Excuse me
(Man 3) Yes, thank you
(Beauty) 'Excuse me'
(Woman 1) Hey, what are you doing?
Let's eat together.
[Elevator arrival sound]
[The elevator doors close with a thud]
(Man 4) Hurry up and give me the eggs and cider.
(Woman 2) Oh, we didn't get any either.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, they say there are no five.
(Admin 1) The food is
prepared based on the number of participants.
But why isn't there any?
Hurry up and give me mine!
[A confused groan]
(Admin 1) The food is
prepared based on the number of participants.
‎(Woman 1) Excuse me
‎Those people
‎took it twice
‎I saw it
‎Hey, fuck, how unlucky, damn
‎(Deoksoo) What, are you watching someone eat
‎and making a fuss, damn
‎[Deoksoo's snicker]
‎[Man 4's trembling breath]
‎(Man 4) What are you guys?
‎Why are you stealing someone else's stuff?
‎(Deoksoo) Oh, is this yours, sir?
‎What's your name, sir?
‎Is your name written anywhere, sir?
‎[Laughter from the crowd]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎I can’t see it?
‎[Gasping]
‎[Deok-soo’s straining groan]
‎(Man 4) Give it to me, it’s mine, I said give it to me!
‎[A bottle crashes, shattering]
‎[Rough breathing]
‎This son of a bitch, damn
‎(Deok-soo) It broke because of you, you bastard
‎[People’s surprised groans]
‎[Man 4’s groan of pain]
‎Fuck, you skinny bastard
‎You’ve got a big appetite, damn it.
[People's astonished groan]
[Man 4's groan of pain]
Go
[Tense music]
We're trying to live together.
Is that so difficult?
You fucking bastard
Oh, you son of a bitch
[Deoksoo's angry groan]
[Deoksoo's rough breathing]
(Deoksoo) Ha, shit
(Sangwoo) Hey
Hey, come on…
It's dead
(Gihoon) Over here!
[Urgent breathing]
Someone died!
Can't you hear?
A person has died
That person has died
‎[dark music]
‎[Gi-hun's heavy breathing]
That person over there has died
That guy killed a person!
I can't hear!
A person has died!
Can't you hear what I'm saying?
This shouldn't be happening!
‎(Gi-hun in the video) We shouldn't be killing like this among ourselves!
‎[heavy breathing]
‎[voice-over] Number 271 has been eliminated
‎[Piggy bank operating sound]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[The buzzer rings]
‎[The door creaks open]
‎[Footsteps approaching]
‎[Heavy music]
‎[Workers thud the coffin down]
‎[The coffin creaks open]
‎[Smirking]
‎[Meaningful music]
‎[Tense music]
‎(Soldier 1) Hey
‎What are you doing not working?
‎I'm sorry
‎What brings you to the incinerator…
‎(Junho) Did you forget the rules?
'One does not speak
first until the superior asks.'
‎[Rustling]
‎[Jingle Notification Sound]
‎[Guidance Voice] We will turn off the lights in 30 minutes
‎(Soldier 2) Hurry up, it's almost bedtime
‎[Guidance Voice] Everyone please return to your accommodations
‎You absolutely must not sleep today
‎(Sang-woo) If the lights go out
‎I don't know what will happen
‎Those guys' atmosphere
‎has been strange since earlier
‎If an attack starts
‎we must fight together
‎If anything happens over there, come this way.
(Ali) I understand.
(Gi-hoon) Grandpa.
[Il-nam's sleepy groan]
Grandpa.
[Il-nam's surprised groan]
Even if the light goes out later,
you must not sleep, got it?
Why?
(Gi-hoon) Because today is a bit dangerous.
Stay wide awake.
If something happens, we'll come this way.
(Il-nam) Oh.
Right.
[Approaching footsteps]
(Gi-hoon) Hey, pickpocket.
[Sigh]
Will you be okay?
You don’t seem to have a good relationship with that punk.
So?
When the lights go out and something happens
we decided to gather towards my bed.
You come too.
I don’t trust people.
Humans who crawl into places like this
can’t be trusted even more.
Is that what you want to say to me?
(*Gi-hun) Originally, people aren’t trusted because they’re trustworthy.
It’s because there’s nowhere else to lean on that we trust.
[Gi-hun's sigh]
‎(Soldier 3) Why isn't the transport team coming?
‎[Closes the icebox with a snap]
‎[The door bangs loudly]
‎[Significant music]
‎[Scanner operating sound]
‎(Soldier 2) Number 28, why are you alone?
‎(Worker) Number 29 hasn't shown up
‎- (Soldier 3) Did something happen?
‎- (Worker) I don't know
‎[The door slams shut]
‎(Soldier 2) Then deliver it by yourself.
‎(Worker) I can't dive alone.
‎It's too dangerous.
(Weapon) Stop
talking and speak now.
Tomorrow's game, what is it?
Is it certain?
If I get eliminated,
you guys are done with this too.
(Soldier 3) Don't worry about that,
just get through tonight.
What do you mean?
(Soldier 3) There's going to be a fight inside.
They're deliberately giving us less food
to provoke a fight.
Before the next game,
we're going to weed out the weak ones in advance.
It's all part of the game.
(Soldier 2) We can't protect you in there.
Quickly go back and find a way to survive
‎A way to survive?
‎(Soldier 3) Stick to the strongest side
‎That's the way to survive
‎(Weapon) Let me join too
‎On the same side
‎[Deoksoo's snicker]
‎Why should we?
‎Mister, what can you do?
‎I'm a doctor outside
‎It will be helpful
‎So?
‎Well, if you catch a cold here
‎will you at least give me a shot?
‎[Everyone laughs]
‎When the lights go out, stay still in the corner
‎Don't even breathe
If you hear a breath
I will come to catch you
‎[Tense music]
‎(Weapon) I know
‎what the next game is
‎[Guidance voice] Two minutes until lights out
‎[Meaningful music]
‎In a moment, the special game will begin
‎Administrators, soldiers, and workers
‎please move quickly to the designated location
‎I will say it again
‎Administrators, soldiers, and workers
‎please move quickly to the designated location
‎[Guidance Voice] 30 seconds before power off
‎[Guidance Voice] 10, 9, 8
‎7, 6, 5
‎4, 3, 2, 1
‎[Timer End Sound]
‎[People's tense breathing]
‎[Tense music]
‎[Woman 1's tense breathing]
‎(Deok-soo) Did you see it?
‎[Woman 1's fearful moan]
‎[Woman 1's scream]
‎[Woman 1's strained moan]
‎[People's screams]
‎That bastard…
‎[Deok-soo's effortful groan]
‎[People are noisy]
‎(Captain) Start
‎[Screams of people in the video]
‎[People are in an uproar]
‎(Woman3) Please save me!
‎[Urgent groan of Man5]
‎[The bed crashes down]
‎[Gi-hun's urgent groan]
‎[Dawn's tense groan]
‎[Dawn and Man3's exerting groans]
‎[Dawn's exerting groan]
‎[Man3's pained groan]
‎[Dawn's heavy breathing]
‎[Dawn's strenuous groan]
‎[Dawn's exerting groan]
‎[Dawn stabs deeply with a knife]
‎[Rough breathing of dawn]
‎[Deoksu's strained moan]
‎[Dawn's painful moan]
‎[The difficult moans of dawn and
Deoksu] ‎[The bed crashes down]
‎[Dawn's difficult moan]
‎[Dawn's startled breath]
‎[Deoksu's painful moan]
‎[Dawn's urgent moan]
‎[Deoksu's difficult moan]
‎[Deoksu stabs deeply with a knife]
‎(Deoksu) Fucking bastard!
‎[Deoksu's labored breaths]
‎[Gihoon's frightened breath]
‎[Gihoon's painful moan]
‎[Gihoon's urgent moan]
‎[Man 6's shout]
‎[Gihoon's startled moan]
‎[Man 6's strained moan]
‎[Gihoon's urgent moan]
‎[Man 6's shout]
‎[Gihoon's strained moan]
‎[Man 6's strained moan]
‎[Gihoon's painful moan]
‎[Sangwoo and Man 6 fight noisily]
‎(Sangwoo) Hyung, are you okay?
‎- (Gihoon) Uh, uh, thank you ‎-
(Ali) Bosses ‎(Gihoon) Old man, huh?
‎- (Ali) Grandfather
‎- (Gihoon) Old man
‎[Gi-hun's strained moan]
‎[Gi-hun's surprised moan]
‎[Sang-woo's strained moan]
‎- (Sang-woo) He's gone
‎- (Gi-hun) Sir
‎(Gi-hun) Sir!
‎Sir, sir!
‎Sir!
‎[Man 7's urgent moan]
‎[Man 7's scream]
‎[Increasing music]
‎[People are fighting noisily]
‎[A cracking sound is heard]
‎[People's screams come out]
‎[The door bangs loudly]
‎(Woman 4) Please help me!
‎[Woman 4's urgent moan]
‎[Man 8's strained moan]
‎[Scared breathing]
‎[Dawn's labored breathing]
‎(Gi-hun) You came
‎(Dawn) You called me?
‎[Tense music]
‎[Gi-hun's urgent moan]
‎[Deok-su's strained moan]
‎[Gi-hun's scared moan]
‎[Deok-su's moan]
‎[A bottle shatters loudly]
‎[Dawn's pained moan]
[The people are fighting loudly]
(Deoksu) Hey, Ssangmun-dong, why are you butting in?
If you reduce the number of people a bit, it’d be good for you too
[Deoksu's laughter]
(Gi-hun) This guy is on our side, you know
[The rough breathing of the people]
(Deoksu) Fuck
(Il-nam) Please stop
I’m, I’m scared
If this goes on, we’ll all die!
We’re, we’re all going to die
(In the video, Il-nam) I’m so scared
Stop it!
(Captain) Game over
(영상 속 일남) If this happens, everyone will die!
[The buzzer sounds]
[Gunshot]
(병정4) Drop your weapons!
Turn back
[Nervous breathing]
[Sigh]
[Scanner operating sound]
[Announcement voice] Contestant 277 eliminated
Contestant 74 eliminated
[Scanner operating sound continues to ring]
Contestant 198 eliminated
Contestant 87 eliminated
(준호) Contestant 456
[Announcement voice] Contestant 222 eliminated
(준호) Is there anyone named Hwang In-ho among them?
‎[The guidance voice continues to flow out]
‎We don't know each other's
names ‎[Meaningful
music]
‎[Guidance voice]
Number 361 eliminated
‎Number 328 eliminated
‎Number 103 eliminated
‎Number 198 eliminated
‎Number 6 eliminated
‎Number 206 eliminated
‎Number 233 eliminated ‎Number 239 eliminated ‎[Forklift warning sound]
‎[Flames are raging]
‎[Sigh]
‎(Gi-hun) Are you okay?
‎Huh?
‎Ah, when did you get up there?
‎It was dangerous ‎I
was worried because
the old boss was gone ‎I'm glad no
one got seriously hurt ‎[Gi-hun's sigh]
‎[Gi-hun's Thoughtful Breath]
‎(Gi-hun) Uh, let's take this opportunity
‎to introduce ourselves.
‎Thinking about it,
‎we don't even really know each other's names.
‎(Ali) I know the boss's name.
‎Sangmun-dong
‎[Gi-hun's Laughter]
‎Sangmun-dong is the neighborhood I live in,
‎my name is Seong Gi-hun.
‎(Gi-hun) Seong Gi-hun from Sangmun-dong.
‎[Jokingly nudging Ali] What's your name then?
‎Ali
‎Ali Abdul.
‎(Gi-hun) Where are you from?
‎(Ali) Pakistan.
‎(Gi-hun) Pakistan?
‎Where is that located?
‎Above India.
‎(Ali) That's right.
‎(Gi-hun) I see.
‎This is Seoul National University's Business Administration...
‎Jo Sang-woo.
‎[Gi-hun chuckles]
‎Do I really have to say this?
‎If we're on the same side,
‎we should at least know each other's names
‎to build some trust, right?
‎Kang Saebyeok.
‎Saebyeok?
‎Nice name.
‎Doesn't quite match your image though.
‎(Ali) Old boss, what's your name?
(One man) Huh?
What’s your name?
Um…
[Il-nam hesitates]
My…
My
name is
Um…
So
that’s
Well
My
name is…
[Gi-hun clears his throat]
[Gi-hun's awkward laugh]
You seemed really scared earlier, sir.
I also tend to forget my home address and
my resident number when I’m under a lot of stress lately.
[Gi-hun's laughter]
(Gi-hun) If you take a little rest, everything will be alright.
‎[Deoksu's Strained Moan]
‎Hey, fuck
‎Are you really a doctor?
‎What if I don't believe you?
‎[Raspy Breathing]
‎(Weapon) I didn't stab deep, so
‎it'll be fine
‎Once we get out of here
‎I'll take care of you again at our hospital
‎[Deoksu's Strained Breathing]
‎(Beauty) You idiot, with all your bravado
‎looking like that, you've really messed up
‎I'm going to get out of here
‎(Weapon) With that
‎[Hollow Laughter]
(Man 1) These sons of bitches.
When you set the stage for killing, when
was that Why are you stopping me, damn it?
It's just a game
and nothing more.
Before that, I could have
cleaned it up properly, Mr. Lee.
(Man 3) If we completely wipe
out all the remaining humans
Just us
That.
Isn’t it the case?
[Byung-gi tears the cloth straight]
If I do well in the next game
There will be another chance
Right, Doctor?
[Deok-soo's laughter]
(Byung-gi) Got it
[Byung-gi's sigh]
(Deok-soo) That's why since ancient times
Every household should have at least one doctor, right?
[Deok-soo's laughter]
(Beauty) Still, you reduced it a lot
From 107 to 80
So, did 27 people die?
Isn't that right, oppa?
'Oppa'?
Am I really your oppa?
‎(Deoksu) [smiling] I don't think so?
Uncle
How old do I look?
Forty-nine
When you were drawing lots
You should have just left it to die
Thirty-nine?
This is the last chance
[thinking groan]
Nineteen?
Bingo
‎(Beauty) Oppa, you have good taste?
If you got it right
You should be rewarded
I'll go to the bathroom and think about it
[sigh]
Suddenly, I have to pee
‎[Deoksu's effortful groan]
‎[The beauty and Deoksu's rough groans]
‎[The beauty and Deoksu's rough breathing]
‎Oppa
‎What’s up with that quack doctor?
‎[Deoksu chuckles]
‎(Deoksu) What’s there, huh?
‎[Deoksu slams the lighter down]
‎[Deoksu exhales]
‎Oppa
‎Really
‎You're going to stick with me until the end, right?
‎[Significant music]
‎You can't deceive me.
‎[Deoksu chuckles lightly]
‎Yeah, just trust me
‎We're getting out of here, just the two of us
‎[Deoksu's rough breathing]
‎What's your name, oppa?
‎Why do you want to know my name?
‎Because I want to know
‎[Deoksu's hollow laugh]
‎(Deoksu) Deoksu
‎Jang Deoksu
‎[Deoksu exhales]
‎[The beautiful woman exhales]
‎Deoksu-ssi
‎If you betray me
‎I'll kill you
‎I feel like I'm going to die today?
‎Because of you
[The beautiful woman's lewd moans]
[Deoksoo's strained moans]
[Bell ringing notification]
[Guidance voice] Everyone
Now it’s time to go to bed
You worked hard today
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Coughing sound is heard]
[Meaningful music]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
(Joonho) Morse code?
[Bright music begins to play]
[Gi-hun's sigh]
Hey, old man
‎(Il-nam) Uh
‎Ah, you've been like this all this time?
‎[Il-nam's awkward laugh]
‎(Il-nam) Yeah, I was worried you might come back again
‎Ah, you must be really tired too, old man
‎[laughter]
‎It's okay
‎When you get old, you lose sleep too
‎Hey, I may not be much help
‎But at least I should keep watch
‎[Elegant music begins to play]
‎[Gi-hoon's sigh]
[Announcement Voice] The
third game will start shortly.
Participants are requested to move according
to the instructions of the progress staff.
I will inform you once again
‎[Meaningful music]
‎The third game will begin
‎[Guidance voice] We are checking the participants
‎Please wait right in front of the door
‎[A worker coughs]
‎Completed
‎[Junho's trembling breath]
‎[Elegant music flows out]
‎[Guidance voice] Welcome to the third game,
‎everyone
‎This game is a team event
‎Participants, please divide into teams of ten
The time limit is 10 minutes, 10 minutes.
I will guide you once again.
This game is a team competition.
Participants should divide into teams of ten.
The time limit is 10 minutes, 10 minutes.
(Deoksu) Absolutely gather only those who look strong.
(Man 1) Ah, yes.
Oh, then what about him?
If it's going to be teams of ten,
(Gihun) Are they going to make us do something like tag or
'Why did you come to my house'?
What, something like this?
[Thinking Moan]
If it's tag, you have to be quick
"Why did you come to our house?"
You just have to play rock-paper-scissors well
What will you do?
We already have an old man and a woman
The rest has to be chosen from the men
(Gi-hun) Then what if we make them play things like rubber band or game of air?
Women are better at those kinds of things
That might be true, but statistically
there are more games that favor men.
(Sang-woo) Right now
‎we're betting our lives
‎Which side will you bet on?
‎[sigh]
‎We only need to pick five
‎So let's spread out
‎and each bring one person back
‎Okay?
‎[Il-nam's cough]
‎Hide this hand
‎(Sang-woo) It looks weak
‎[People are talking among themselves]
‎(Man 1) Yes, brother
‎I think you can do it with this guy over here
‎Hey, you, go look over there for a bit, over there.
‎[Gi-hun's Sigh]
‎[The Sound of Contemplation]
‎(Sang-woo) Teacher
‎Have you decided on a team?
‎Ah, no
‎Then let’s team up
‎I have a team
‎(Man 9) Ah, yes, but I
‎really have to be with my wife
‎Is that okay?
‎I’m sorry
‎We already have a lot of women on our team
‎(Man 10) Hey, if you’re looking for a team
‎let’s team up, okay?
‎(Gi-hun) Excuse me
If you still don't have a team
Would you like to join us?
‎(In the video, Deok-soo) Let's just meet next time
‎(In the video, the beauty) Oppa
No, right?
You're just messing around, right?
There's so many people
Can't you see?
‎(Deok-soo) We're exactly ten people now
[Awkward laughter]
Oppa
Ah, what's wrong?
[Deok-soo's sigh]
‎(Beauty) I'm sorry
I'll do better
Oppa, just tell me anything to do
I can do it all, you know, oppa.
So
This time, let's just take a break for a bit
and we can meet again next time, right?
[The urgent moan of a beauty]
(Beauty) Oppa
Why are we breaking up?
You said we would stick together till the end
Oppa
Are you really okay without me?
I
can't be without you, oppa.
(Deoksoo) Damn it!
Ah, fuck
it's so disgustingly sticky, really, damn it.
Coming out of nowhere, calling me 'oppa, oppa,' huh?
If you call me brother one more time
I’ll split that mouth open
‎[The beautiful one's trembling breath]
‎You bastard
‎So this is your true self?
‎(Beauty) Jang Deok-soo
‎You fucking bastard
‎I said I would kill you if you betrayed me
‎Oh dear, I'm so scared
‎Our Han Mi-nyeo
‎Hope you do well in the game today, okay?
‎[Laughter from the crowd]
‎(Man 1) [smiling] 'Beauty'
‎Such a waste of a name, damn
‎What is it?
‎Let’s do it together
‎(Gi-hun) One
Two, three
Four
Five
Six, seven
Eight
Nine?
No…
[Sigh]
Who is the person who couldn't bring anyone?
I'm sorry
Who called you to come?
Here
I said to gather only men, right?
(Ji-young) The atmosphere is cold
Did I come to the wrong place?
Then get up
[Gi-hoon's flustered groan]
Oh, just sit here
(Gi-hoon) No, we still don't know what to do
There's not much time left.
Let's hurry and find one more person
to fill the spots for ten people.
Who would voluntarily join a team that looks weak at a glance?
Once the teams are all set,
someone who's been pushed out with nowhere to go will show up.
Who’s been pushed out, huh? (Beauty)
Brothers, I’ll specially join you.
You guys should know you’re lucky today, oh my.
I’ll be much more useful than those scrawny kids.
And I can do everything except what I'm not good at
I do well
‎[beauty's laughter]
‎[chuckle]
‎[timer end sound]
Sigh…
‎[announcement voice] The team selection
time has
‎ended. All teams, please line
up
‎in a single file at the game entrance.
(Gi-hoon) No, weren’t we supposed to do this here?
‎[interesting music]
‎[sigh]
‎[the door slams shut]
‎(Manager 2) Welcome everyone to
the third game. This game is tug of war.
In the tower above, pull the rope.
If you drop your opponent down,
you'll win.
‎[Sangwoo's discontented breathing]
‎[Man 2's laughter]
‎[Man 10's sigh]
‎(Administrator 2) Then from now on,
we will draw the teams you will face.
Please take your seats.
We will draw the teams that will climb the left tower.
Group 1
Please stand up.
‎[Deoksoo's tense breathing]
Next, we will draw the team that will climb the right tower.
Group 7
Please stand up.
‎[Trembling breathing]
‎[Tense music]
‎(Administrator 2) Groups 1 and 7 will
compete first.
Groups 1 and 7, please enter.
‎[People's trembling breathing]
‎[Interesting music]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[People's straining groans]
‎(Deoksoo) Die!
‎[Woman 5's scream]
‎[Group 7 members' strenuous groans]
‎(Deoksu) Die! ‎[Group 1
members' strained groans]
‎[Group 7 members' screams]
‎[People's astonished groans]
‎[Group 1 members' strained groans]
‎[Group 7 members' screams]
‎[Group 1 members' rough breathing]
‎[Deoksu's laughter]
‎[Intriguing music]
‎[Group 1 members' rough breathing]
‎[Deoksu's laughter]
‎[Voice announcement]
Eliminated are 245, 120,
37, 408, 27, 273, 58
‎[Dark music]
‎243, 327, 241.
[The苦しみのうめき声 of a man 11]
(Administrator 2) I will draw the next opponent
Group 4
Group 5
Ah, shit
It's the men's bath
(Administrator 2) Groups 4 and 5,
please enter
[Deoksu's laughter]
(Deoksu) That's a shame
I wanted to kill you with my own hands
[Laughter from Group 1 members]
[Forklift warning sound]
[Elevator operating sound]
[Il-nam's cough]
(Il-nam) Don't be too demoralized
Tug of war isn’t just about strength.
‎(Man 10) If it's not by strength, what
‎Are you talking about tug-of-war?
‎Tug-of-war requires good strategy
‎And if we just come together well
‎Even if we're lacking in strength, we can win
‎(Man 12) The only one who can save us
‎Is the Lord alone
‎(Man 10) Hah, the old man
‎Looks like he doesn't even have the strength to stand, tsk, tsk
‎Stop saying useless things and conserve your strength!
‎[Il-nam's sigh]
‎(Gi-hun) Let's hear what you have to say.
When I was young, I used to participate in
tug-of-war quite a bit back in my hometown.
I had barely ever lost.
Even (Il-nam)
when there was a wrestler on the other side
and our side was at a significant disadvantage.
[The elevator rattles]
Listen carefully
From now on, I'll tell you how I won back then.
[Tense music]
I'll let you know that.
First of all, the person standing at the very front is important.
That person is the one who faces the opponent’s face
the closest.
The remaining team members are all
the ones looking at his back.
If that person looks weak
or seems discouraged,
then the competition is already over.
And at the very back,
someone sturdy needs to take charge,
like an anchor on a ship.
And it's important to place people well
by standing in a line.
One by one, divide them to the right and left
and line up.
Keep your feet straight in an "11" position.
Place the line between your armpits.
To receive power properly
[Group 4 members' tense breathing]
Finally, this is the most important thing,
the signal rings and for the first 10
seconds, [gunshot] [Group
4 members' straining groans]
You just have to
endure it. At this time, the
position is a lying
position. Push your lower
abdomen up towards
the sky and tilt your head
back enough to see the
groin of the person behind you.
Then you won’t
get pulled away as
long as you endure for 10 seconds, you'll
think, 'Huh, this is strange,
why am I not getting pulled over?'
The other side is going to be confused.
They must have believed that they were stronger.
If we hold on like this,
the moment their breathing breaks
will definitely come.
Pull!
[Group 4 members' straining groans]
[Rising music]
[Group 5 members' struggling groans]
(Male 13) Get a grip!
[Group 5 members' straining groans]
[People's straining groans]
[Group 4 members' struggling groans]
Hey, do something, you fucker!
[Group 4 members' straining groans]
(Sangwoo) Everyone, get a grip and listen to me!
When I give the signal,
just move three steps forward.
Move forward?
Are you crazy!
We need to knock them down!
Don't talk nonsense!
Let's do it!
(Beauty) No, I can't do it!
(Sangwoo) If you can't, you'll die!
We're going on three.
One, two, three!
[Group 4 members' straining groans]
[Heavy music]