"Netflix series"
[Significant music]
[A clattering sound is heard]
[A faint moan escapes]
[A nail is slammed in]
(Gi-hun) Sang-woo
Thank you
I survived because of you two
(Ali) I'm glad to be alive
[A buzzer sounds]
[People murmur]
(Manager) To the participants who passed the first game
Congratulations from the bottom of my heart
I will announce the results of the first game
[Sang-woo's tense breathing]
(Manager) Out of 456 people
255 have been eliminated
The number of participants who finished the first game
is 201
[People's astonished breaths]
[People murmur]
[A sigh]
(Beauty) [Choking up] Teacher
I made a mistake
I will definitely pay you back
[Sobbing] I will definitely pay you back
Teacher
It's me
The child is with me
I haven't even named
it yet, so I can't
report the birth. [Sniffles]
Please let me out. [Sangwoo's sigh]
(Woman 1) [Sobbing]
Teacher, I was wrong.
Please, please save me.
I will somehow repay the money.
Please save me. (Woman
2) Me too, I want to stop
too - please let me out.
- (Woman 1) Please save me.
[People are pleading in their own ways]
(Administrator) It seems
there is a misunderstanding.
We have no intention of harming
you or trying to take your money.
I'm saying this again
I’m giving you a chance
‎(Sang-hoon) A chance?
‎Is this supposed to be a chance?
‎Making kids play
‎and killing people
‎Is this a chance?
‎We owe money
‎but we haven't committed a mortal sin
‎[people murmur]
‎(Administrator) This is just a game
‎(Joo-eun) Killing people like that
‎and you call it a game?
‎(Administrator) They simply broke the rules of the game
‎and got eliminated.
If you just follow the rules of the game
With the promised prize
You can safely leave this place
[The beauty weeps]
(Man 1) I don't need the prize or anything
Please just let me go!
[People are all speaking]
(Administrator) 'Article 1 of the consent form'
'Participants may not arbitrarily suspend the game'
Do you really think you can get away with doing something like this?
(Sang-hun) The police are here to find the missing people
They’ll find this place soon, probably?
‎[People murmur]
Yeah
If we don’t let them go!
They’ll track our phones
and come here!
- (Man 1) Then it’s the end for you too!
- (Min-tae) Yeah, it’s the end!
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Screams of people]
‎(Administrator) 'Article 2 of the Consent Form'
'Participants who refuse the game
will be disqualified'
‎(Sang-woo) 'Article 3 of the Consent Form!'
‎[Gasp of shock]
'If the majority of participants agree'
'The game will be suspended'
Is that correct?
(Administrator) That's correct
Then let's proceed with the voting
(Sang-woo) If there are more people who want to stop
then we will be let out from here
(Administrator) Depending on your will
I will conduct a vote on whether to suspend the game
‎[People murmur]
Then, before the vote
I will reveal the prize accumulated from the first game
[Remote control operation sound]
‎[Piggy Bank Operating Sound]
‎[Significant Music]
‎(Administrator) The number of participants eliminated in the first game
‎is 255.
‎The prize amount at stake for each participant
‎is 100 million won.
‎Thus, 25.5 billion won in prize money
‎has been accumulated in the piggy bank.
‎If you give up the game now,
‎that 25.5 billion won
‎will be distributed to the families of the eliminated participants,
‎each receiving 100 million won,
‎and you will
‎go home empty-handed.
‎Excuse me
‎But
If you pass all six games
How much will you give?
(Admin) 456 participants
Therefore, the total prize money is 45.6 billion
Then we will start the voting from now
If you look in front of you
There are two buttons
If you want to continue the game
Press the green circle button
If you want to stop
Just press the red X button
Those who have finished voting
Please stand on the opposite side of the white line in the middle.
The voting will be done in reverse
order of the numbers in your heart.
Please vote for number 456
‎[Gi-hun's tense breathing]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Button operation sound]
‎(Administrator) Please vote for number 453
‎[Significant music]
‎[Button operation sound]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Button operation sound rings incessantly]
‎[Button operation sound]
‎(Administrator) Number 218
‎[Sangwoo's Sigh]
‎[Button Sounds]
‎[Startled Breathing]
‎[Sangwoo's Sigh]
‎[Button Sounds]
‎(Sanghoon) Are you crazy?
‎Are you saying everyone wants to keep doing this, right now?
‎(Beauty) Of course!
‎What's going to change if we go out?
‎It's hell on earth anyway, fuck.
‎Tsk
‎(Mintaek) That's right!
‎If we stop now
‎only the ones who got eliminated benefit.
‎They say those guys are getting 100 million each.
We won the game, but
Does that make sense?
(Joo-eun) Please
‎Ah, please don’t do this!
We have to go home!
‎(Min-tae) I don’t have a home anyway
At least there’s hope here, but when I go out…
If I go out, there’s nothing, damn it
[Min-tae's trembling breath]
Let’s stay and see it through to the end!
Instead of going out and dying like a dog,
I’d rather die trying to do something here
‎[approaching footsteps]
‎(Sang-hoon) Hey, you bastard!
If you're going to die,
die alone, you bastard!
Don't draw everyone in, you son
of a bitch. ‎[Approaching footsteps]
- Why the hell...
- (Sang-hoon) Hey, this...
[People's shocked groans]
[Sang-hoon's trembling breath]
(Administrator) From now on
I will not tolerate
any act that disrupts
the democratic voting process
Then I will resume the voting
[Tense music]
[The sound of button presses continues to ring]
[Button press sound]
(Administrator) Now
is the last voter.
Number 1
[Breath of tension]
The doctor says.
In my head
They say I have a mass
Brain tumor
(Administrator) If you want to continue the game
‎Circle
If you want to stop
Please press the X button
‎[Sigh]
‎[Male contestant's worried breath]
‎[Strained groan]
‎[Button operation sound]
‎[Cheers from the crowd]
‎[Sigh]
‎(Man 2) Hey, I'm alive, ah!
‎(Administrator) Since the majority of participants
‎agreed to pause the game,
‎I will stop this game here.
(Min-tae) No, let the people who want to leave go out,
and let the ones who remain continue!
(Video Min-tae) Half of them are already
dead on the floor, so we can't just stop here!
(Video Beauty) Yeah!
Let us at least continue!
(Video Min-tae) Yeah,
let us continue!
[People are noisy] (Administrator) It is unfortunate
for us as well to have to part with all of you like this.
But we will not completely close
the door of opportunity for you.
If many of you want the game to resume,
I will start the game again at any time.
Then, please go back safely.
[Cicada sounds]
[Gi-hun's painful moans]
[Gi-hun's frightened breaths]
(Gi-hun) Please, save me!
Someone, help!
Is no one here? There is someone here!
(Dawn) Be quiet.
(Gi-hun) Yes? Yes.
[Gi-hun's struggling groans]
[Rough breathing]
[Surprised] Ah, who are you?
‎[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
‎Pickpocket, pickpocket?
‎Are you the pickpocket?
‎You’re not going to lie
here all night, are you?
‎So untie this a bit,
okay? ‎[Suffocating groan]
‎[Gi-hun's straining groan]
‎[Dawn's straining groan]
‎[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
‎(Gi-hun) Damn, where am I?
Damn ‎[Gi-hun's straining groan]
‎Come on, I need to hurry
up too, come on, okay?
‎Ah, you, ah, yeah, put yours
on quickly, yeah, isn’t it cold?
‎Ah, I’m cold too, seriously
Oh, dear, oh my, oh no.
Ah, okay, hurry and put it on, oh
[groaning in pain]
Oh my, my
leg, ugh hey
hey, now let
me go quickly, huh?
Hey hey, hey!
What are you doing?
You have to let me go!
[Gi-hun's urgent breathing]
(early morning) Why should
I? [Gi-hun's flustered breathing]
Ah, because I let you go!
Are you naive or stupid at that age?
When you let me go, you'll tell me
to give you money,
You'll say
something to me, right? Ah, that's that!
(Gihun) I got it, I got it
I won't ask for money
Just hurry up and let this go
[Gihun's rough breathing]
Is it for real?
Yeah
I swear I'll never ask for money
How can I trust you?
Ah, I swear on my mom
My mom's name
Hurry up and let this go
(Gihun) [in pain] Ah, fuck
Oh, oh, oh, that hurts
[sigh]
[Gihun is mumbling]
[Gihun's pained groan]
[Gihun's straining groan]
[early morning straining groan]
(Gihun) Hey, you, hey, you come here
My money, give me my money
Give me my money, huh? Give me my money
Ah, damn
Aren't you going to give me my money? Give me my money, damn it
[Gihun's pained groan]
Fuck, give me my money, fuck
[Gihun's pained breath]
Mr. A is so pitiful
(Gihun) You, damn
You just stay there for a moment
You, you!
Don’t stand there!
‎[Gi-hun's painful groan]
‎(Ali) Manager
‎[rough breathing]
Where is this place?
‎(Sang-woo) Yeouido
‎(Ali) Where is Yeouido?
‎[Sang-woo rustles his clothes]
It’s in the middle of Seoul
‎(Ali) M-M-M-Mr. Manager
Is there a phone?
‎I just want to make one call
Just one time
‎(Convenience store employee) It’s 2,000 won
‎[register beeping]
‎[mobile phone vibration sound]
‎[The cellphone vibrates continuously]
‎[Sigh]
‎(Ali) Thank you
‎[Urdu] Hello?
‎Yes, dear
‎I have something to take care of
‎Sorry
‎[Snapping a lighter]
‎(Ali) [Korean] Thank you, boss
‎Goodbye
‎(Sangwoo) Excuse me
‎Do you have money for the fare?
‎What?
‎I heard your home is in Ansan
‎You don’t even have money for instant noodles
‎So do you have money to go home?
‎Money
‎(Ali) I don't have any money
I'm walking
Are you walking from here to Ansan?
I'll wait and take the bus
No
I don't have money, I can't pay you back
I won't make you pay it back
Just take it with you
Thank you, (Ali)
Thank you, boss
I'm not your boss
Quit calling me boss
I'm sorry, (Ali)
Thank you
Thank you!
[A bird chirps]
(Gi-hun) Officer
It seems like you still don't fully understand the
seriousness of the current
situation. (Police Officer 1) Yes, sir.
So, you're saying
that 'strange people
gathered hundreds of unknown individuals in a
playground' and 'told them to play a game and then shot them dead with guns'?
[Slams the table] Yes, it's not
just one or two people; over 200
people were just shot dead, you know?
What was that game?
'Mugunghwa Flower Has Bloomed.'
(Officer 1) That, the kids are playing
'The Mugunghwa Flower Has Blossomed'?
(Gihun) Yes, so you're saying
that the adults made them do that?
[Clapping the table] Ah
That's what I'm saying.
(Police Officer 1) So if they got
caught, they shot them dead with guns?
Ah, how many times do I have to say it?
(Police Officer 2) Sir,
so where is that place?
The place where those
people were killed, I was anesthetized
and taken away, so I
don’t know where it is.
Then what about the
people who ordered it?
They all wore masks
and disguises...
(Police Officer 2) Then how
did you get out of there, sir?
This was a vote among people playing the game
to see
.(Gi-hun) There were
more people wanting to leave…
.(Police Officer 2) So
the victims
said, ‘We want to leave’, and then
the murderers
said, ‘Sure, go ahead’?
.(Gi-hun) Yes
[laughter of Police Officer 2]
Why did you initially go there?
Well,
they said if you play the game
they’d give you money…
.(Police Officer 2) Money?
Yes
They said they’d give hundreds of billions.
[Chuckles]
So
‎(Officer 1) [Clapping hands] So, to summarize what you said,
Someone suddenly said that if you play a game, they'll give you hundreds of billions, so you followed them,
And then they made you play 'Mugunghwa Flower Has Bloomed',
And if you got caught, they would shoot you dead.
But you said you wanted to get out, so you managed to come out,
And you don't even know what those people's faces look like,
Or where that place even is.
Is that right?
Yes
So, what is your name?
I'm Sung Gi-hoon, a resident of Ssangmun-dong.
Mr. Sung Gi-hoon.
Do you, by any chance, have a guardian?
(Police Officer 1) If you need help,
we can contact a medical institution for you.
[Slamming the table] I'm a resident of Ssangmun-dong who pays taxes here!
(Gi-hoon) How do you see people?
This is the business card they gave me,
so you can just call this number! Sir.
[Gi-hoon snorts]
[Button press sound]
[Call connection tone]
[Heavy breathing]
[There is a clattering sound]
(Woman 3) [In a sleepy voice] Hello?
[The confused groan of Officer 1]
(Officer 1) Ah, yes
Well, um, excuse me
from the morning Um,
may I ask you something?
(Woman 3) Who is this?
(Officer 1) Ah, yes Ah.
..
Ah, yes, I'm sorry but um, is it
possible to play
some kind of game?
(Woman 3) A game?
Ah, yes, I do play games a bit.
Just tell me
whatever, and I will do my best...
(Woman 3) Excuse me
What kind of person are you
talking nonsense on the phone since the morning?
If you want to play games,
go to the PC room alone, you pervert!
[Sniffing]
(Gi-hun) I just pressed the wrong button!
Come on, don’t push, don’t push, let go of this
(Police Officer 2) Yes, sir, I’m sorry.
Please come back later!
Did you really call the right number?
Did you dial the wrong number?
Just wait a second
I’ll walk over and switch you over
The number you called last time
is still saved on my phone
[Gi-hun is panting]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Dial tone]
[Automated voice] The number you are dialing
is not a valid number.
Please check and try again.
[Automated voice switches to English]
[Sigh]
(Jun-ho) What’s going on? Are you a drunk?
He’s just a crazy person
Today is just so chaotic
I’m going crazy, seriously.
(Police Officer 1) Get a grip
Are you going to keep coming here? Tsk
(Junho) I'm going in, take care
(Police Officer 2) Yes, take care
Mom!
I'm here
(Gi-hun) Mom!
What's this?
[Dial tone]
[Automated voice] The power is turned off
Connecting to voicemail…
Oh?
[Automated voice is playing]
Ah, where did this old man go?
[Call disconnect tone]
Leaving the door wide open, jeez
[Sigh]
(Sang-woo) Gi-hun.
What are you doing here?
‎[Sangwoo's awkward groan]
‎[Sangwoo and Gi-hun's sigh]
‎(Gi-hun) Is it because of your debt?
‎Damn, hey
‎The pride of Sangmundong
‎The genius born and raised in Sangmundong
‎Top admission to Seoul National University's Business School
‎What does Jo Sang-woo have to worry about?
‎You can just earn it back
‎Go tell your mom everything
‎and start anew
‎Earn it back?
‎60 billion?
‎Oh, you said 6 billion?
‎There’s something those guys don't know.
No, you said you work at a securities company.
Did you invest in stocks?
The stocks aren't that big,
I traded futures.
Futures?
Are you spending that money on futures?
(Gi-hoon) Ah, whose futures
did you buy that are so expensive?
Did you get a girlfriend?
It's not that kind of futures,
[makes a smacking sound]
[sighs] There's something like that.
(Gi-hoon) Ha, really
Come on, can't I just apply for personal bankruptcy or something?
Isn't that okay?
It seems that if you do that
you don’t have to pay back the money
Everything has gone in, even my mother’s
(Sangwoo) house
even mom’s store
[Flustered breath]
[Mobile phone ringtone]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
Hello?
Yes, it’s me?
What?
[A siren is heard from a distance]
[Gi-hun's shocked breath]
.(Doctor) It’s diabetes
It has been neglected for a long time and complications have arisen
[Trembling breath]
It must have been quite painful.
Didn’t you know?
We just need to treat it, right?
In the worst case,
we might have to amputate the foot
.(Doctor) First, please get hospitalized
and let's observe the progress while treating it.
.(Gi-hoon) Mom!
Mom!
Ah, Mom, where are you going?
They said to get hospitalized!
.(Gi-hoon’s mom) Ah, I’m fine
.(Gi-hoon) What do you mean you’re fine!
Ah, you can’t even walk properly!
(Gi-hun's mom) Ayi,
Chiara, thank you.
You don't even come home, just
wandering around, and now you
show up acting like a good son?
(Gi-hun) Mom, why are you being so foolish?
They say if you don't get treatment, it's going
to be a big deal. (Gi-hun's mom) Is that so?
If I just lie here like this,
who's going to pay the rent?
And do you know how much
a day in the hospital
and the medication costs?
Ah, we have
insurance, right?
What do you mean?
Insurance?
Don't you remember? (Gi-hun's mom) That
was already canceled, it's all used up.
Please get a grip.
Oh my.
Gi-hun.
Oh, Mom is tired.
I’m struggling.
I want to be thankful now.
Thank you.
[Gi-hun's mother's sigh]
Damn it.
I’ll bring the money!
If I bring the money, that should be enough! Damn.
Yes, mother.
Ah, I’m on my way to the goshiwon.
Oh, nothing will happen.
Hyung sometimes does that.
He doesn’t respond to messages well.
Yes, I’ll call people around where my brother is.
Hmm, if I can’t reach him,
I’ll report him missing in person tomorrow.
Ah, I’m with the Korean police.
Hyung, I’ll find you.
(Jun-ho) Yes, mother.
Don’t worry too much.
[A dog barks in the distance]
(Jun-ho) How long has it been since my brother came in?
(Goshiwon owner) Well,
I don’t check every day,
but the date he paid for the goshiwon was
a week ago.
Since then, I've come every day.
They don't come in, and they don't answer the phone.
Excuse me, but
the room fee...
Otherwise
you need to take your things out now.
After I look,
the room fee will be paid separately.
[Laughter of the guesthouse owner]
[The lock clicks open]
(Guesthouse owner) Go ahead and take a good look, then.
[Switching sounds]
[Significant music]
(Jun-ho) Is that a drunk?
It's just a crazy guy.
(Officer 1) I'm so
overwhelmed today, damn it.
(Sister) Hey, kids, come have some ice cream
[Children's laughter]
(Kid) Wow, it looks delicious
[Sae-bok rustles the bag]
(Sae-bok) Why?
You said you wanted to eat ice cream
Why does your face look like that?
Did you fight with your friends?
If you keep saying that
I'm just going to leave
Me
I don't want to be here
Mom said she would come back soon
[sniffling] If I wait for a month and Mom comes
We'll all live together, she said.
Cheol-ah
- (Saebyeok) That is…
- (Cheol) The kids say it’s all a lie
I can’t leave from here
They say my sister abandoned me here
[Cheol sniffles]
I will go
Mom and Dad will definitely come
Sister will make sure of it
- (Saebyeok) Next year, we will all gather together
And we will live in the same house
[Cheol sniffles]
Sister, you know?
Sister always keeps her promises
Ah, that 'Mugunghwa has bloomed'?
But why does Detective Hwang
want the name of that crazy guy?
Ah, that…
I caught a glimpse of it
yesterday, and thinking about
it
it seems like someone I knew before, right?
Really?
Ugh, what was it? (Officer 1) It’s
that guy from Sangmun-dong, uh, uh…
(Officer 2) Seong Gi-hoon,
from
Sangmun-dong
(Officer 1)
Oh, right, Seong Gi-hoon
You know him, right?
Uh, yes, I think so Ah, could
you get me that person’s address?
(Man 3) Ali, it’s been a while?
[Game sounds are heard]
Uh, Ali
‎(Ali) Why aren't you answering the phone?
‎Oh, you called? I didn’t know.
‎[Mouse click sound]
‎(Boss) Why, why, what’s going on?
‎Boss, please give me my overdue salary.
‎(Boss) Oh, come on.
‎How many times do I have to tell you that?
‎I don’t have any money right now.
‎[Mouse click sound]
‎(Boss) As you know,
‎the company’s situation is tough, buddy.
‎That finger treatment wasn’t done properly.
‎(Ali) I didn’t get my hospital bill covered properly.
‎Ha, I’m going back to my hometown now.
‎Please, give me money.
‎(Boss) Hey, damn it,
‎ask the kids outside.
‎Did they get their salaries?
‎We can't give money until we collect, you punk!
‎Hey, I also have a few places that hurt.
‎But I can't go to the hospital because I don’t have money.
‎Boss, you said you would give me money!
‎[Mouse click sound]
‎Please, give me money.
‎It’s been over six months!
‎Ah, you really...
‎(Boss) Hey, let's talk later
‎I'm a bit busy
‎(Ali) Boss, give me money
‎Boss, please give me money
‎(Boss) Where are you touching?
‎You son of a bitch, damn it, tsk
‎(Ali) Don't cuss at me!
‎(Boss) What a fucking bastard
‎(Ali) There's money here!
‎- (Boss) You bastard
‎- (Ali) Give me my money
‎[Boss's strained groan]
‎(Ali) Here it is
‎(Boss) Aren't you letting go, you bastard?
‎[Ali's Straining Moan]
‎(Ali) Give me my money
‎[Boss's Shout]
‎[Machine Error Sound]
‎[Ali's Urgent Breathing]
‎(Man 3) Hey, you can't go!
‎Hey!
‎(Employee) I know your circumstances
‎very well, but
‎Kojou, the thing is
‎There's no way to find the brokers who ran away
‎[Pouring water] The person who got hurt
‎isn't just you
‎Some people went directly to Dandong
‎because they caught those guys.
Instead, I almost got caught by the public security.
I almost got dragged back to the North.
[The employee puts down the teapot]
Is there no other way?
Then we have to hire another broker.
But as you know,
we have to start all over again.
How much is it?
First, we need to reassess your parents' whereabouts.
Again.
(Employee) Yeah, these days,
the border security has become fierce.
[Pouring coffee slowly] The cost across the river has also gone up...
So how much is it?
[The employee places the courage down]
At least
it has to be over 4,000...
[The employee clinks the cup]
4,000?
That's just the cost to China
and from there to South Korea again...
[The employee's scream]
(Employee) Ah, it's hot, ah, it's hot!
[The employee's frightened moan]
(Dawn) Last time as well,
I sent the money just believing your words.
I risked my life to save that money
‎[Employee's trembling breath]
‎(Employee) Hey
‎I didn’t know either, okay?
‎I really didn’t know those bastards would take the money and leave me
‎I swear
‎[Employee's scared breath]
‎(Dawn) Money
‎I’ll get it
‎If you trick me one more time
‎next time, I will definitely take your neck first
‎Got it?
‎[Employee responds]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[The door opens and closes with a clang]
‎Ah, it's hot…
(Sangwoo's mom) Are you eating well?
‎(Sangwoo) Yeah, I'm taking care of myself, so
‎don't worry.
‎(Sangwoo's mom) Oh, but you probably won't like
‎American food much.
‎What do you eat?
‎(Sangwoo) No, Mom.
‎There are a lot of Korean restaurants here.
‎Oh, really?
‎Ah, that's a relief.
‎[Laughter]
‎When are you coming back?
‎(Sangwoo) Hmm, my work is dragging on, so
‎I still don't know well.
‎I think it will take a while.
Oh, really
‎Our son must be having a hard time
‎[Sang-woo's mom sighs]
‎Mom
‎(Sang-woo's mom) Yeah, why?
‎(Customer) Ma'am
‎Please give me three boiled squid
‎Ah, yes, hold on a second
‎Sang-woo, there's a customer
‎(Sang-woo's mom) When you come back
‎don't bring anything, okay?
‎Mom doesn't need anything, got it?
‎Got it
‎(Sang-woo's mom) Yeah, don’t skip meals
‎Make sure to dress warmly
Our son, come in now, huh
I love you, son
[Sangwoo's mom smiles slightly]
Is it octopus?
[Call disconnect sound]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
(Sangwoo's mom) Oh my
This kid always says he’ll buy me something when he goes abroad
He keeps bringing things like this, tsk
It seems like your son is a devoted child
He graduated from Seoul National University
[Sangwoo's mom chops the squid]
(Sangwoo's mom) Business Administration
Oh my, Business Administration from Seoul National University?
‎(Customer) You have a good head on your shoulders and you look good too.
‎Are you married?
‎Not yet.
‎(Customer) How old are you this year?
‎Shall I set you up with someone?
‎Ah, but my son has high standards.
‎[Sangwoo's mom is skillfully preparing squid]
‎(Detective) Excuse me.
‎Are you by any chance the mother of Jo Sangwoo?
‎Yes, Jo Sangwoo is my son.
‎Where is Jo Sangwoo right now?
‎He went on a business trip to America.
‎What's going on?
Uh, this is the police.
(Detective) Uh, Mr. Jo Sang-woo
is wanted on charges of embezzlement and forgery of private documents
in violation of the Act on the Aggravated Punishment of Specific Economic Crimes.
A warrant has been issued for his arrest.
Yes?
Who are you arresting?
Oh, detectives
It seems there’s some kind of mistake
My son
is not the kind of person who would do anything wrong.
If you get in touch with your son,
please let him know to voluntarily come to the police station.
(Detective) If he continues to evade...
Later, it will be disadvantageous in court.
‎[The detectives flutter their umbrellas]
‎[Dark music]
‎[Sigh]
‎[The doorbell rings]
‎[The doorbell keeps ringing]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Tense music]
Who is it?
‎[A swishing sound is heard]
‎[Thunder rumbles]
‎(Ali's voice) [Urdu] Where did this money come from?
‎Ali, where did you get this money?
‎[Ali slams the window shut]
(Ally) Listen to me
carefully from now on.
Take this
and buy the fastest plane ticket possible
You and the kid go back home first
What about you?
(Ali) You two go ahead first
I'll head over as soon as I finish work
(Ali's wife) Is something wrong with you?
Right?
(Ali) Don't ask me anything right now
[Ali's wife is choking up]
Pack your things and get out of here today
I hope you understand my situation
[Ali's wife is sobbing]
I love you, and you too, kid.
(Gi-hun's friend) [Korean] Where's the money? (Gi-hun)
Can you lend me 3 million? I'll pay you back within two months.
(Gi-hun's friend) Friends
shouldn't talk about money.
You know the situation for
both of us clearly.
(Gi-hun) Ah, I get it.
Ah, how desperate do you
have to be to say this, huh?
If I can't manage,
I'll do deliveries here.
(Gi-hun's friend) Come on.
What kind of deliveries?
Take a look inside. It’s hard
to even pay the rent here.
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, then
‎I'll just use it for a month and give it back, okay?
‎Ah, if I run deliveries as a part-timer
‎I can pay it back in a month
‎Hey
‎My mom needs immediate surgery at the hospital
‎You're really…
‎[The entrance door chimes]
‎(Friend of Gi-hun) Babe
‎Can you stop coming in now?
‎(Gi-hun's friend) I’m going in
‎(Friend of Gi-hun) Ah, get in right now!
‎Put out the cigarette!
‎[Gi-hun's friend shakes off the ash]
‎Hello
‎(Friend of Gi-hun) Gi-hun ssi
‎Yes?
‎You can't smoke in front of other people's store
‎Ah, yes
‎[The entrance door chimes]
‎[Thunder rumbles]
‎[Footsteps approaching]
‎(Il-nam) Huh?
‎You…
‎Oh, old man
‎That's right?
‎Number 456
‎Ah, yes
‎Yeah, that's right
‎(Il-nam) No, but
‎How did you end up here?
‎Ah, I live around this neighborhood
[Il-nam responds]
[Il-nam's laughter]
Um…
Do you live in this neighborhood, sir?
No.
I have someone I know around here.
[laughter]
Right now, I have nowhere to go,
so I’m borrowing your hospitality for a bit.
[Il-nam's laughter]
(Il-nam) Oh dear.
(Gi-hun) Ah…
Would you like to sit for a moment?
(Il-nam) Sure.
[They laugh together]
(Gi-hun) It’s nice to see you all here, sir.
(Il-nam) That’s true.
It seems we have a connection.
‎[Il-nam's laughter]
‎Oh my.
‎Ah, would you like a drink?
‎(Il-nam) Oh, sure.
‎(Gi-hoon) Ah.
‎Ah, is this a good place? Is it okay to drink here?
‎Oh, it's fine.
‎[Laughter]
‎[Gi-hoon puts the bottle down with a thud]
‎[Il-nam puts the glass down with a thud]
‎Ah, this.
‎What should we do? There’s no snacks.
‎(Il-nam) Wait a minute.
‎[Il-nam rustles]
‎[Clears throat]
‎[Laughter]
[Gi-hun's urgent moan]
(Gi-hun) Ah, are you okay, sir?
But isn't this
too much to eat?
(Il-nam) Oh, come on
[Il-nam's laughter]
[The sky rumbles]
I
decided to go back
Where to?
[Il-nam's cleared throat]
To there?
Anyway
I won't live long anyway
(Il-nam) Like this
I don't want to just wait for the day I die and then go
Do you know?
There?
I wonder if I'll be first.
That 'Mugunghwa flower' back then
came in before you did.
Ah, but still…
When I came out,
those people's words
were all true.
This place
is more of hell.
[Laughter]
[The sky rumbles]
.[Calm music]
[Bright music starts playing]
[Sounds of footsteps running]
(Organization member 1) Deoksoo hyung
(Deoksoo) Why are you so late?
(Organization member 1) Ah, I just came out.
There was a fight between drunk
customers at the establishment.
You know.
Kid, every time it's Friday night
those bastards just come popping out (Deoksu)
Where's the money?
(Member 1) Ah…
I'm in a hurry, so this
is all I could get for now.
I'll give you more after the
weekend, once
the bills are settled.
Ah, but right now the
chairman is looking for
you, and he said he sent those guys out in
Incheon and Ilsan.
[Deoksu's half-hearted laugh]
Where have you been hiding all this time?
(Deoksu) Well, that's not something to
discuss here. You brought the car, right?
(Member 1) Yes, over this way.
(This is the one that says 'The
Mugunghwa Flower has bloomed')
Is that an invitation?
Okay.
They sent that yesterday.
It looks like they
will start again soon.
So
Gather as many kids
as you can by Tuesday.
I have secured a few guns.
Is it a gun?
They have guns.
But one guy comes
out for the pickup.
(Deoksu) Catch that masked
bastard and beat him up.
These bastards are breaking
into the place where the safe is.
(Staff 1) Oh, that’s...
Even if what you
say is all true...
Son of a bitch.
(Deoksu) I'm not saying to treat
it as a fact, I'm saying it is a fact.
I'm sorry.
(Duksu) Ha, those bastards.
They are kids who stack
hundreds of billions in a piggy bank.
If you hit these bastards in
the back of the head properly,
[smirks]
Drunk guys at the bar Living by
just dealing with the nonsense.
Goodbye.
Ah, but brother
The kids
Right now, you're hiding because
of a money issue with the chairman.
(Staff Member 1) The rumor
has spread all over Incheon.
Hey!
I'm not able to speak
up to the kids right now.
Hey, you son of a bitch.
I'll pay it all back
if I clean this up.
Hi, brother.
But how much did you
lose at the Philippine casino?
How did you know that?
Brother, so please be a little
more reasonable with that.
Is this bastard crazy, damn it?
Deoksu, hey.
- 'Deoksu'?
- (Member 1) [sneering] idiot
[Car horn]
[Tire friction noise]
‎[Tense music] ‎(Team member 1)
The kids doing junket in the Philippines
Instead of the
money you borrowed
You receive it with your
liver, kidneys, and eyes.
You've come this far now.
[Employee 1's laugh]
You're screwed, you idiot.
[Employee 1's laughter]
[The music intensifies]
[Employee 1's scream]
[Deoksoo's strained breathing]
[Employee 1's labored breathing]
[The groan of
Employee 1 in pain]
[Heavy Breathing]
(Duksu) [English] Hey!
Welcome to Korea.
You’ve come well!
Hang in there, Deok-soo.
Come in!
Come here, you fucking.
- (Employee 2) Grab Jang Deok-soo!
- (Employee 3) Run!
Catch it!
‎- (Staff 2) Jang Deok-soo!
‎- (Staff 4) Hey!
(Min-ji, Gi-hoon's
ex-wife) [Korean] Money?
(Gi-hun) Uh
(Gi-hun's ex-wife) How much?
(Han...
About 200?
(Geun's ex-wife) 2 million won?
(Gi-hun) Uh
(Ik-hun's ex-wife) Don't you
think you're being too much?
What about you?
Did you give me alimony?
Or have you ever
given child support?
So then, how can you reach
out your hand to me again?
(Ha, I'm sorry)
It's because of the
hospital bills, Mom.
[Gi-hoon's Sigh]
(Geun's ex-wife)
Where do you hurt?
(Gi-hun) Diabetes is severe.
They say I have
to undergo surgery.
[Gihoon's Sigh]
(Gi-hun's ex-wife)
I have no money.
We're living quite tightly.
(Gi-hun) Let's ask for a favor.
[Gi-hoon's trembling breath]
My mom still treated you well.
How desperate do you think I
must be to have come to you?
I'll definitely repay you.
(I don't have that
kind of money.)
I also get living expenses
from the kids' dad and use it.
Ah, then maybe to that person…
Is she crazy?
Hey
What should I say to ask
that person for money, huh?
[Gi-hun's Sigh]
Go, go
- (Gi-hun) Hey - The kids'
dad should be here soon, go, go
(Yah)
[Gihoon's ex-wife's sigh]
Why do you keep asking,
though? Is that person the kids' dad?
I'm Gayeong's dad!
(Former wife of
Gi-hun) What, Dad?
What did you do for her, huh?
Do you think you deserve that?
The day you gave birth to
Gayeong Were you even by my side?
(Ya, that day)
Ah, you know, I...
‎[Gi-hun's ex-wife's sigh]
‎Said they couldn't go.
A colleague collapsed...
(Former wife of
Gi-hun) I also collapsed!
That day, I went to the hospital
alone, waiting as if it were a chore.
If we were a little later,
Gayoung would have almost died!
‎(Gi-hun) That
bastard died that day!
In front of my eyes!
I heard they died without even
being able to go to the hospital!
[Door lock operation sound]
[Gi-hun's Ex-wife's Sigh]
[Door Lock Sound]
‎[The door swings open.]
Honey, we’re here.
The door slams shut.
(Gi-hun's ex-wife)
Oh, you came early?
[Door lock operating sound]
Dad
(Young sister) Mom!
I was passing by recently.
She said she stopped by
for a moment to see Gayoung.
‎(Gi-hun) Uh… ‎[Gi-hun's
awkward laugh]
Since Gayoung saw it
I’ll go.
Are you leaving?
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, yes ‎I
have an urgent meeting.
Ah, Gayoung, Dad is going.
- (Gi-hun) Dad, I'll come
again - (Ga-young) Okay
(This is how you
can do it, stepfather.)
[Door lock operational sound]
[Door lock operation sound]
Why did that person come again?
Why did you let me
come into the house?
‎(Gi-hun's ex-wife) I'm sorry.
I went to the mart.
I'm waiting in
front of the door.
‎[The rain pours down.]
‎[The automatic door closes
quietly] ‎[Footsteps running toward]
Excuse me.
What is it?
You said you need money?
[Sigh]
[Grabs the envelope]
Thank you
I will definitely repay it.
You don't have to pay it back.
Instead
I hope you never appear
before our family again.
Gayeong is having a hard time.
I have to leave for
the United States now.
You keep showing
up suddenly like this...
[Gi-hun's Angry Moans]
This bastard, Lee.
You think money can
buy everything! Damn!
[Gi-hun is grunting]
(Dad) Gayoung
[Heavy Music]
(Junho) Seong Gi-hoon?
Yes?
This is Hwang
Jun-ho from Dobong.
(Jun-ho) You came to the district office
to report something a while ago, right?
There is a place that kidnaps
people and makes them play games.
And from there
They said they killed people.
Ah, that's just a
story I made up.
I just made it up because
I was bored after drinking.
The business card
that Seong Gi-hoon had.
My brother also had it.
My brother is currently missing.
Ah, I just found it
lying on the street.
I just picked it up
and carried it around.
(Junho) Seong Gi-hoon 씨
Please help me.
[Dark music]
We need to find my brother.
I'm sorry.
I am not in a position
to help anyone right now.
The sky thunders.
[Meaningful Music]
[Sigh]
‎[Surprised breath]
‎[Approaching car engine sound]
[Anxious breath]
[Button operation sound]
[The gas is hissing out.]
[The Rough Breathing of Dawn]
[Dark Music]
Subtitles: Ahn Hyun-jeong