"Netflix series"
[Interesting music]
(Gi-hun) In our neighborhood,
we called that game 'squid'.
It was named after a drawing that resembled a squid.
The rules are simple.
The children gather into groups,
divided into attackers and defenders.
When the game starts,
the defender inside the line must move on both feet.
The attackers outside the line
must move like crabs.
Your mom
(Gi-hun) But if an attacker waits for the right moment
and crosses the waist of the squid,
they earn the right to move freely
on both feet.
Secret royal inspector
(Gi-hun) For reasons unknown,
we called that 'secret royal inspector'.
When they are ready for the final battle,
the attackers gather at the entrance of the squid drawing.
Go!
(Gi-hun) To win, the attacker must
step inside the small line above the squid's head
with their foot.
At that moment, pushed by the defender,
If you step on the line or go outside, you die.
Yeah, you die.
[Heavy sound effect]
[Children's cheers]
Hooray!
(Gi-hun) 'Hooray'
When you step on the finish line, you shout 'Hooray'.
In that moment, I
felt as if I owned the whole world
I was so happy.
[Gi-hun slurps the soup]
(Gi-hun's mom) Yeah.
[Refreshing sigh]
What is this? Are you giving it to me?
(Gi-hun's mom) You, you today
You know it's
Ga-young's birthday, right?
‎[Sigh]
‎Hey, you know ‎(Gi-hun’s mom) Don’t
forget ‎to go later
‎At least buy her
dinner ‎Ah, how much
are prices these days?
‎What can you buy her with this?
‎Doesn't Ga-young like chicken?
‎(Gi-hun’s mom) You ‎Just
buy a chicken and come
back ‎Are you just going
to feed her chicken?
‎It's her birthday, so you should at
least buy her a gift ‎Give me a
little more ‎(Gi-hun’s mom) I have no
money ‎(Gi-hun) Oh, why is there no money?
‎I gave you everything I
earned from my part-time job.
(Ai-gi, Gi-hun's mom) Oh my, that money
‎Hey, that's not even a month's interest on the loan
‎Oh my
‎(Gi-hun) Oh, that's
‎I can't pay it all back living like this!
‎So let's spend a little and live
‎(Gi-hun's mom) Oh my
‎Oh dear
‎[Sigh from Gi-hun's mom]
‎Ah, stop that, and!
‎(Gi-hun's mom) Ah, soak the dishes in water
‎[Sigh from Gi-hun's mom]
‎[The door closes with a click]
‎You always say your back hurts
‎How much do you even earn!
‎[Fading footsteps]
‎[Slams down the spoon]
‎[Strained groan]
‎[Gi-hun's excited breath]
‎[Gi-hun's exclamation]
‎[Laughter]
‎[ATM error sound]
‎(Gi-hun) Huh? Oh, it is my birthday, isn't it?
‎- You changed the password
‎- (Gi-hun) This is…
‎Your mom finally abandoned you, hey
‎[Laughter from Gi-hun's friend]
‎(Gi-hun) Damn…
‎[ATM operating sound]
‎[ATM error sound] ‎Huh?
‎Damn, what did this old man change it to?
‎(Gi-hoon's friend) Your mom ‎Try
something like your mom's
birthday?‎ Mom's birthday?
‎Mom's birthday…
‎[Gi-hoon's sigh]
‎(Gi-hoon's friend) I don't know, I don't
know ‎You don't know
your mom's birthday?
Damn, you idiot!‎ (Gi-hoon)
Damn, fuck, you dumbass, I know!
‎It's just that the old
man changes it every
year, with the lunar
calendar, that's why it
changes every year, you
idiot, fuck, you don't even…
‎(Gi-hoon's friend) Then
just check the lunar calendar.
‎(Gi-hun) Damn it
‎[ATM manipulation sound]
‎[ATM error sound]
‎Ah! I, damn it
‎Damn it
‎(Gi-hun's friend) Ah, hey, hey, hey
‎No, no
‎Hey, if you get it wrong just once more, your transaction will be stopped
‎[Gi-hun's sigh]
‎Think carefully, come on, is there nothing else?
‎[A guide voice starts to play]
‎[They laugh together]
‎(Gi-hun's friend) Hey, what did you do, what did you do?
‎(Gi-hun) Today is my daughter's birthday
‎Ah, these days, that old man
‎takes care of my granddaughter way more than I do
‎Oh my
‎(Caster in the video) In 2nd place
‎Horse number 9, Triple Line
‎[People are noisy]
‎In 3rd place is horse number 6, Dry Thunder
‎4th place is taken by horse number 3, Jack Prince…
‎[The commentary continues]
‎(Gi-hun) Oh, right, come in
‎More, more!
‎(Caster in the video) Horse number 3, Jack Prince
‎is gradually picking up speed
‎[Gi-hun shouts]
‎Catching up with horse number 9, Triple Line!
‎[The broadcast continues]
‎(Gi-hoon) More, more!
‎Run faster, run, number 9!
‎I said to run, damn it
‎[Sighs from Gi-hoon
and Gi-hoon's friends]
‎[Cheers from the crowd]
‎(Gi-hoon's friend) Number 9, what a
legend ‎Head is definitely solid, right?!
‎Ha, you idiot, damn it ‎Bringing good
words ‎Really making me shit
blood, really, damn it, oh my!
‎[Bright music plays]
‎(Announcer from the speaker) We
inform you that the betting for
race 10 will ‎soon
close, oh my, damn it.
‎[The announcement continues to play]
‎(Man 1) Ah, hurry up over there, come on
‎(Announcer from speaker) The ticket sales for Race 10
‎will close soon
‎[Sigh]
‎(Man 1) Hey
‎Ah, what are you doing…
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, please
‎just leave me alone!
‎Let me think!
‎[Gi-hun's heavy breathing]
‎Ah, damn
‎[Sigh]
‎Yeah
‎(Caster on video) After that,
‎number 9 Baegil Myth
‎is positioned in the middle ranks
‎[Gi-hun responds]
‎[The commentary continues]
‎(Gi-hun) That's right, come in
‎- (Gi-hun's friend) Run!
‎- (Gi-hun) Uh, uh, uh, yeah, turn
‎(Gi-hun) Uh, hurry and turn, turn, come on
‎- (Gi-hun) Stick together!
‎- Huh?
‎- (Gi-hun) Come out, come out, come out!
‎- Stick to the side, stick, stick…
‎[People are noisy]
‎(Gi-hun's friend) Ugh, ugh, ugh, no!
‎[Gi-hun's Urgent Moans] ‎(Caster in the
video) Number 6, Thunder ‎is still going!
‎[The commentary continues]
‎(Gi-hun) Got it, good, good, good, good!
‎Let's go, let's go, let's
go, let's go, let's go!
‎6, 8, 6, 8!
‎[Cheers from the crowd]
‎It's here, 6, 8 is here!
‎[Gi-hun's Laughter]
‎(Gi-hun's friend) Why did you pop
out in the middle? ‎[Gi-hun's Cheer]
‎(Gi-hun) What did I say?
Today is our daughter's birthday, that's why I said so.
June 8th, 6, 8!
Staff: It's 4,560,000 won.
Gi-hun: Yes, thank you.
Here, buy an Americano.
Gi-hun's friend: Aren't you buying for me?
Gi-hun's laughter
Gi-hun: Hey
We need to fill up my mom’s money first.
Where's the ATM around here?
Gi-hun: Dad will pick you up in front of the academy.
Gi-hun's laughter
What, chicken?
Hey, something more expensive is fine too.
Write down everything you want to eat, okay?
Yes, yes, yes.
During class time, just write what the teacher says.
Write it down during break, got it?
Gi-hun's laughter
Got it, 7 o’clock.
What could the birthday present be?
[Smiling] Stay tuned.
You're really going to be surprised…
Man 2: Hey, Gi-hun!
Man 3: Hey!
Hey, long time no see!
Oh, Ga-young, oh
Dad loves you too, okay?
‎[Interesting Music] ‎- (Gi-hun's friend) What is
it? ‎- (Man 3) Hey, hey, hey, catch him, catch him!
‎[Gi-hun's urgent groan]
‎(Gi-hun) Wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait…
‎[Gi-hun's urgent groan]
‎[Gi-hun's surprised groan]
‎[Painful groan]
‎Oh, ah, I'm sorry, um,
student, are you okay?
‎Ah…
‎[Gi-hun's urgent groan]
‎Ah, I'm sorry, huh?
‎(Man 2) Catch that bastard!
‎(Man 3) Hey, you bastard ‎Stop
right there! Aren't you stopping?
‎[Moan of pain]
‎Ah, just a moment
‎Just a moment, wait, I
‎I have money, I have money, I have money
‎[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
‎Really?
‎But why did you throw up?
‎Oh, that's because
‎Oh, I thought it might trouble you, teacher
‎I was going to collect it all at once
‎and give it to you
‎[Laughter]
‎(Man2) Oh, the kid's impressive
‎Ah, so how much is there?
‎[Gi-hun's painful moan]
‎400
‎First, take this
‎and I'll make sure to give you the rest by next month…
‎(Gi-hun) Huh?
‎[Gi-hun's shocked moan]
‎(Gi-hun) Oh, are you okay, student?
‎[Moan of pain]
‎Oh, look, ah, look, look
‎(Man2) Look, look
‎Oh my
‎[Man2's exclamation]
‎This is sweet
‎Well, oh, I guess you ate a lot of delicious things with my money
‎You had money.
Earlier, earlier 6, 8, 6, 8 came in
Money was really here
(Man 2) Hey
[Gi-hun's scared breath]
[Gi-hun's flustered moan]
[Moan of pain]
You
Do you know why nosebleeds happen so often?
[Scared breath]
It's because there are a lot of capillaries in the nose
[Urgent moan]
Please save me, pl, please save me
(Man 2) The taste of blood is nice though
I'll bring a bowl and
I should make some seonjiguk tonight.
[Sobbing] I will repay you.
I will repay you, really, I will.
(Man 2) Hey, you little brat.
Hey, don't let your heart get weak.
Why are you crying like this?
Ah, how did you know that I have a soft heart?
Hey.
Now, wipe your tears.
Here, put your thumbprint.
[Gi-hun coughs]
If I can't repay you by next month,
I'll give you one of my kidneys.
‎[Gi-hun's frightened moan]
Here’s an eyeball I'll
take it instead, okay?
Why, do you hate it?
[Gi-hun's desperate moan]
(Gi-hun) No, yes Got it, got
it [Gi-hun's rough breathing]
(Man 2) Hey (Gi-hun)
Yes, uh, this, In-joo…
[Pained moan]
[Man 2's laughter]
Oh, here it comes
(Man 2) Naturally
grown In-joo (Gi-hun) Yes?
Oh, yes [Gi-hun's
labored breathing]
(Man 2) Yeah, yeah, hold
it there [Man 2's laughter]
Well done, uh
[Man 2's laughter]
It's been a month, take good care of your health
Ah, excuse me, teacher
Ah, I'm sorry, but
Could you lend me just 10,000 won?
[Man 2's chuckle]
(Man 2) Oh, come on
Oh, you little brat
[Laughter of the men]
[Awkward sigh]
(Gi-hun) Excuse me
I'm sorry, but
The 10,000 won I gave you earlier…
[Gi-hun's awkward groan]
[Sounds of a gaming console are heard]
Damn it
[Gi-hun's sigh]
(Gi-hun) That's right
Okay, that's right, that's right
Good
[Gi-hun's sigh]
[Gi-hun's shout]
Oh, damn, damn it
(Kid) Mister
You can't just pick up anything thoughtlessly
Are you even trying?
[Rustling of a bag]
[Intriguing music]
[Gi-hun's exclamation]
(Gi-hun) Okay, that's right
Oh, this…
[Exclamations from Gi-hun and the kid]
[They laugh together]
[Gi-hun's laughter]
‎(Gi-hun) You did well!
‎You did well, you did well, you did well
‎[Gi-hun's laughter]
‎Oh, this?
‎This
‎I got bitten by a giant mosquito
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, these days mosquitoes are so vicious
‎Oh dear
‎(Ga-young) Dad
‎It's your choice to fight, but
‎don't get beaten up
‎(Gi-hun) Dad
‎I'm sorry
‎I was going to buy something tastier for Ga-young
‎but
‎It's okay
‎Yesterday, Mom and my stepdad
‎went to a steakhouse
Ah, steak
Ah, I see
But I think tteokbokki is much tastier
(Kayoung) Mom doesn't let me eat stuff like this, saying it's junk food
[Gihun and Kayoung's laughter]
(Gihun) Eat, eat
Oh, right
Dad brought a birthday present for Kayoung!
[Kayoung's surprised gasp]
[Gihun's laughter]
[Gihun's embarrassed groan]
[Gihun's awkward breath]
Hey, you know, right?
Girls are going to the military a lot these days.
[Awkward laughter]
The world you will live in from now on
is one where men and women
are equally treated.
Kayoung, you also
need to get a bit used to this.
[Flustered laughter]
Oh my, even fire is coming out.
[Laughter]
Hey, hey, it really feels like it, hey.
(Gihoon) Right, huh?
[Awkward laughter]
But
if mom sees this,
dad is going to get scolded again.
Ah, is that so?
Hey, then I guess I'll have to keep this until you grow up
Just don't smoke with it
Dad quit smoking
[sniffing]
[laughter]
I got it, I got it
(Gi-hoon) Dad will definitely quit smoking
Next year on your birthday
I'll get you a really nice gift
I promise, Kayoung
Next year?
Think about your birthday last year
Your birthday came around quickly this year too, right?
Next year's birthday will come soon.
Dad
Yes (Gi-hoon)
What?
No, yes
Okay, eat more, eat more
Eat more Tteokbokki
Excuse me, please give me just 1,000 won more here.
Mix in a lot of fish cakes.
[Sigh]
Why did you bring him so late?
The kid is wearing thin clothes.
Ah, I was carrying him because he said he was sleepy…
Oh, you’re 10 minutes late, 10 minutes.
Well, I said I would
come pick you up by car.
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, let's stop, it's the kid's birthday
‎[Gi-hun's discontented groan]
‎(Ga-young) Mom
‎[Gi-hun responds]
‎(Gi-hun's ex-wife) Oh, Ga-young, get down
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, I'll carry you
‎to the elevator
‎(Gi-hun's ex-wife) You're spoiled, get down
‎[Ga-young's sleepy groan]
‎- (Gi-hun's ex-wife) Ga-young, get down
‎- (Gi-hun) Ah, really
‎- (Gi-hun) Kid…
‎- (Gi-hun's ex-wife) Wake up, let's go
‎(Ga-young) Dad, hi
‎(Gi-hoon) Ah, go in, go in
‎[Sigh]
‎[Announcement voice] The entrance door is closing.
‎[Entrance door warning sound]
‎(Gi-hoon) Ah, ah, wait a minute!
‎Ah, wait, wait
‎Ah, just a second…
‎[Gi-hoon's heavy breathing]
‎[Strained breathing]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Approaching footsteps]
‎[Gi-hoon's sigh]
‎Teacher?
‎Could you wait just a moment…
‎(Gi-hoon) I don't believe in Jesus.
‎(Man 4) That's not it.
I wanted to give the teacher a good opportunity today...
Since my family believes in Buddhism,
don't bother me and go away.
Teacher
Would you like to play a game with me?
[Gi-Hoon's sigh]
What is it?
Are you a peddler?
Gi-Hoon: These days, the sales tactics are very diverse?
[Man 4 opens the bag with a click]
You look like you’re in a tough spot right now too,
But I'm currently...
[Interesting music]
(Man 4) Teacher
Have you ever played ddakji?
If you play ddakji with me,
I will give you 100,000 won each time you win.
[nervous laugh]
Oh, so if I hit your ddakji and flip it over,
you give me 100,000 won?
Conversely, if I win,
you just need to give me 100,000 won.
I will concede the first move.
I'm not feeling good today.
If you’re trying to trick me right now,
you’re really going to regret it today, huh?
‎(Gi-hoon) Am I really going first?
‎What color would you like to go with?
‎[Gi-hoon's strained moan]
‎[Sigh]
‎Don't you have any money?
‎Money...
‎Then you can compensate with your body
‎[Gi-hoon's sigh]
‎With my body?
‎[Gi-hoon's pained moan]
‎What the hell are you, you bastard?
‎I'll give you 100,000 won for a slap
‎[Frustrated breath]
‎[Gi-hoon slaps the token]
‎Let's play one more round.
‎[Entrance Door Warning Sound]
‎[Guide Voice] The entrance door is opening
‎[Interesting Music]
‎[Clap Sound]
‎(Gi-Hoon) One more round
‎[Gi-Hoon's Strained Moan]
‎[Guide Voice] The entrance door is closing
‎[Entrance Door Warning Sound]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Man 4's Shout]
‎[Pained Moan]
‎[Gi-Hoon's Strained Moan]
‎[Man 4's Shout]
‎[Pained Moan]
‎[Gi-Hoon's Strained Moan]
‎[Gi-Hoon's Angry Moan]
‎[Gi-hun's painful groans]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Gi-hun takes a deep breath]
‎[Gi-hun's strained groan]
‎[Nervous breathing]
‎[Heavy sound effect]
‎[Gi-hun's cheer]
‎Wow, did you see it, did you see it, did you see it?
‎(Gi-hun) [smiling] Did you see it?
‎Did you see? I won
‎You come here, you face this way, you bastard
‎Are you not letting go of this, you little shit?
It’s 100,000 won.
Congratulations.
Ah…
100,000 won.
[Spits]
(Man 4) Teacher.
If you do this for a few days,
you can make a lot of money.
Would you like to give it a try?
[Gi-hun’s snicker]
(Gi-hun) Uncle.
Isn’t this some kind of new pyramid scheme or something?
You’ve got the wrong person.
I’m not that gullible.
[Flipping through the bills] Tch…
(Man 4) Seong Gi-hun.
‎[Meaningful Music]
‎Did you write a waiver for physical abandonment today?
‎Name: Seong Gi-hoon, 47 years old
‎Highest Level of Education: Korea Industrial High School
‎Former employee of Dragon Motors Assembly Team 1
‎After taking voluntary retirement during the restructuring 10 years ago
‎I opened a chicken restaurant and a snack bar, but
‎they all failed
‎and currently I am working as a substitute driver
‎I have a ten-year-old daughter with my ex-wife, whom I divorced three years ago
‎Current debt: private loan 160 million
‎bank loan 255 million
‎Who are you?
What are you doing investigating me?
‎[The sound of an approaching subway engine]
‎There aren't many empty seats left
‎Please contact me
‎[A man grabs his bag]
‎[Door warning sound]
‎Tsk
‎Oh, right, damn
‎(Gi-hun) ♪ I'm thirsty in the middle of the night ♪
‎♪ Open the fridge... ♪
‎(Sang-woo's mom) Did you have another drink?
‎No.
‎[Sang-woo's mom chops the fish] ‎Hey, but I didn’t
even drink, yet ‎I feel like I’m really drunk?
‎[Gi-hun's laughter]
‎(Gi-hun) I made money
today, you know? ‎[laughter]
‎Gi-hun, are you
still gambling?
‎Hey, I’m not gambling, okay?
‎I really earned it with
my own effort, you know?
‎(Sang-woo's mom) But why
does your face look like that?
‎Are you fighting now?
‎(Gi-hun) Hey, that’s enough.
What’s Sang-woo up to these days?
‎Is he doing well at work?
‎He's busy every day.
(Sang-woo's mom) [Chopping fish]
I'm on a business trip abroad right now.
(Eun-gi) Hey, you little prick
When you come to Sang-woo’s house
just tell him to contact me
You know my mother?
The reason this punk got into Seoul National University
is all because of me
[snickers]
I've been taking him to school since we were kids
But now that the kid is going to college and getting a job
he hasn’t bought me a drink even once
Stop with the nonsense
You go home quickly with this
(Sang-woo's mom) Don’t go back to the bar again
Here, the change is fine.
‎(Gi-hun) ♪ I'm thirsty in the middle of the night ♪
‎[Half-laugh]
‎♪ When I opened the refrigerator ♪
‎It's 12,000 won, you rascal
‎[A dog barks from afar]
‎(Gi-hun) ♪ In one corner, there's mackerel ♪
‎♪ Pickled in salt… ♪
‎[Cat meow]
‎Hmm…
‎[Gi-hun's laughter]
‎Are you hungry? Huh?
‎Here
‎Eat this
‎You can't leave it, okay?
I bought this with the money I earned from getting slapped.
[Gi-hoon's laughter]
[The cat is purring]
[Laughter]
(Gi-hoon) ♪ I'm such a fool ♪
♪ Just looking at mom is
enough to make me happy ♪
[Smiling] Here, mom,
use this for your allowance.
[Gi-hoon's laughter]
(Gi-hoon) Ah, take it.
(Gi-hoon's mom) Oh my.
[Gi-hoon's confident grunt]
Did you gamble again?
(Gi-hoon) No.
(Gi-hoon's mom) Then
why does your face look like that?
Ah, you’re not going to say anything?
(Gi-hun) No, it’s not like that.
(Gi-hun's mom) You, you
Where did you steal this, someone else's money?
Oh, it’s not gambling or stealing
I earned it really
with my own hands, huh?
With my face and my body
I really worked to the bone
(Gi-hun) Ah, really
Did you
buy chicken for Ga-young?
And dinner too
And got her a gift and then came back
Did Ga-young not say anything to you?
What do you mean?
I heard Ga-young's mom and
her new husband
are all going to America next year
I'll get you a really nice gift
for Ga-young's birthday
Next year?
America?
(Gi-hun's mom) Yeah
That guy, well
is transferring his job to America
They’re all moving to America together
[Sigh]
Really?
Are you now
(Gi-hun's mom) Is food going down your throat? Huh?
You have to find what you know.
Ah, how can I find the kid?
At that time, when the stamp was put
it was already all over.
[Sigh]
Upstairs,
there's a young man who says he knows the law,
.[Gi-hun's sigh]
The kid's father,
just the economic part of raising a child, right?
If that's possible,
they say you can find the kid, right?
(Gi-hun's mom) goes to America
and just enters, and
forgets all the Korean.
You and I, we won't be able to communicate forever.
I'll wait for you to have nothing to do with others forever.
[Gi-hun's sigh]
Uh?
Do you really
have the confidence to live without seeing Ga-young?
[Heavy music]
[Gi-hun's sigh]
[A dog barks in the distance]
[Sigh]
[Gi-hun clicks his tongue]
[Gi-hun's sigh]
[Cell phone operation sound]
[Call connection sound]
(Man 5) Hello.
(Gi-hun) Ah, um
I'm the one who received the business card earlier.
‎(Man 5) Do you wish to participate in the game?
‎[Meaningful music]
‎If you wish to participate, please tell me your name and
‎date of birth.
‎[Nervous breathing]
‎[The sound of an approaching car engine]
‎(Man 6) Seong Gi-hoon?
‎Ah, yes.
‎(Man 6) What’s the password?
‎'The hibiscus flower'
‎'Has blossomed'
‎[The car door opens quietly]
‎[Gi-hoon's startled gasp]
‎[Gi-hoon's labored breath]
‎Seems like everyone is tired.
‎I…
It's here until the game starts.
‎[Gas is hissing out]
‎How long will it take?
‎[Gi-hun's puzzled groan]
‎[Gi-hun's weak breathing]
‎[Bright music is playing]
‎[Gi-hun's sleepy groan]
‎[Gi-hun's tired groan]
‎[Elevator arrival sound]
‎[Rebound]
‎(Il-nam) 50, 51…
‎55, 56
‎(Gi-hun) Sir
‎[Il-nam mutters]
‎What are you doing?
‎Ah, don’t talk to me, it confuses me.
‎(Il-nam) Sixty-seven
‎[Il-nam mutters]
‎(Gi-hun) Hey, can you count how many people have arrived?
‎Are you counting people?
‎Ah, right, so don't talk to me
‎[Il-nam mutters]
‎[Puzzled grunt]
‎Ah, this
‎How far did I count?
‎(Gi-hun) Sir, uh, 456 people have arrived
‎[Il-nam clears his throat]
‎Oh, wow, sir, you came in first?
‎I, huh?
‎Am I last?
‎[Snorts]
I know too. (Il-nam)
I'm just counting.
The doctor says that
counting numbers
is good for dementia.
(Gi-hoon) Ah, what
brings you here at an age to worry about dementia?
You should be eating the
food your daughter-in-law
prepared and warming
yourself by the floor while
watching your grandchildren perform, right?
(Il-nam) Come on, do your parents eat the kind of
food your daughter-in-law prepares? [Il-nam's sigh]
[Gi-hoon's cough]
I don't
have much time left.
Yes?
The doctor says that.
There’s a bump in my head
They say it’s a bump
A bump?
Brain tumor
[Laughter]
(Deoksu) You fucking bitch!
[A thud is heard]
[People's shocked gasps]
[Deoksu's laughter]
Hey!
[Deoksu's exclamation]
I see all of you here, huh?
Look at this bitch’s eyes, the temper's still the same, huh?
Well
What if you get hit a few times, you’re not exactly a scaredy-cat
A bitch with nowhere to go
You fed me, put me to sleep, and even taught me skills, and now
you stab me in the back?
You owe me less than
I have given to you.
[Laughing] Why
did such a confident woman run away?
It's not running away, it's
just independence. [Laughter]
Independence?
(Deoksu) Ha, damn it.
[Gasps of shock from the crowd]
[The crowd murmurs]
[The painful moans of dawn]
[Gasps of shock from the crowd]
[The crowd murmurs]
[The rough breathing of dawn]
(Duksu) Are you going
to gain independence?
What are you, Yu Gwan-sun?
Then go out and
wave the Taegeukgi.
Ah, right. You're a North
Korean, so you should
wave the red flag, right?
[People's stunned moans]
(Gi-hun) Hey, come here, huh?
[Strained moans
of the dawn] You...
Huh? Oh, a scar on your neck, huh?
It's you, pickpocket. You, give me my money, my
money! Where is my money? Give me my money! Ugh!
[Gi-hun's
pained
moans]
[People's stunned moans]
Ah, what the hell?
(Deok-soo) Who are you?
[Awkward moan]
What the hell are
you? You bastard.
Yes, I, I am
I'm Seong Gi-hoon
from Ssangmun-dong.
Hey, Ssangmun-dong, yes.
(Deok-soo) I'm still in the
middle of talking with this woman.
Ah, yes, I'm sorry, but I have
some urgent matters to discuss
with this sister as well.
(Deok-soo) What the hell is your relationship with this woman?
[Chuckling] Really, what kind
of relationship do you have?
Just looking at your face, you seem like a punk hiding
behind people like this, making a living off them. Did you send her?
Did you tell her to steal my money? You
bastard... [Gi-hoon's frightened whimper]
(Gihun) There are
gangsters killing people here!
‎[Gihun's urgent groan]
‎Oh, here ‎Please come out quickly!
Hurry up… ‎[The buzzer sounds]
‎Oh, they came out Oh, no ‎There are gangsters
and pickpockets here ‎[The door rattles open]
‎Gangsters and pickpockets, gangsters…
‎[Mysterious music]
‎[Gihun's heavy breathing]
‎[Flustered groan]
‎(Administrator) Welcome to everyone
who has come to this place.
You will participate
in a total of six games
over the next six days. A large prize
will be awarded to those
who win all six games.
(Younguk) How
can we believe that?
They suddenly anesthetized us, took our phones and wallets,
dragged us to a place we don’t even know, and suddenly they
show up and say if we play a few games, they’ll give us a large amount?
Are you saying we should believe that now?
‎(Administrator) The process of bringing you here
was a necessary measure
taken for security maintenance.
I will return everything
once the games are over.
‎(Mi-ok) But
‎Why are you wearing such a mask?
‎(Administrator) It is our principle
‎not to disclose the faces and personal information of the staff
‎to the participants.
‎This is a measure for the fair conduct of the game and
‎to maintain confidentiality.
‎Please understand.
‎I can't trust anything you're saying.
‎(Sang-woo) Abduction, kidnapping, and imprisonment
‎Even after all sorts of illegal acts,
‎they're coming up with various excuses
‎and not revealing who they are,
‎give me just one reason why we should trust you.
‎(Administrator) Participant number 218, Jang Sang-woo
‎[Remote control sound]
‎Age 46
‎Former team leader of the 2nd investment team at Joy Securities
‎Illegally siphoned off client deposits
‎and invested in stock derivatives and
‎futures options, resulting in failure.
‎Current loss amount: 650 million won
‎Participant number 107, Kim Mi-ok, debt of 540 million
‎Participant number 118, Oh Young-wook, debt of 1.02 billion won
‎Participant number 322, Jeong Min-tae, debt of 880 million
‎Participant number 119, Noh Sang-hoon, debt of 1.39 billion.
Number 369 Park Joo-woon, Debt 900 million
[The exciting cheers of
the people in the video]
All of you here right now are
people who are burdened with
debts you cannot bear and are
standing at the edge
of life's precipice.
When we first
approached you,
you did not believe us.
But as you can
see, we played a game and gave
you the promised money.
You trusted us and all willingly
volunteered for this
game without any coercion.
I will give you another
chance to choose now.
Go back and live
the rest of your life.
Will you live like garbage,
being chased by debt collectors?
Or will you take the
last opportunity we offer?
‎[People are murmuring]
‎(Ali) Us
‎What game are we playing?
‎(Administrator) For a fair game for everyone
‎Game details cannot be disclosed in advance
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, um…
‎How much is the prize roughly?
‎[Remote control sound]
‎[Tense music begins to play]
‎(Administrator) Each time a game ends
‎the prize money will be deposited into a piggy bank
‎The amount of the prize will be revealed after the first game ends.
I will make it public to everyone
If you do not wish to participate in the game
please let me know now
[Mysterious music]
[Miok's anxious moan]
Is this all?
[Il-nam crumples the paper]
[Sigh]
[Elegant music begins to play]
[Guidance voice] In a moment
the first game will begin
Participants, please move according to the guidance of the staff
(Man 7) Hey, what is this? This is no joke.
Wow, fuck, it's so big
‎[Voice guide] Please look at the camera
‎Smile
‎[Camera shutter sound]
‎Please look at the camera
‎Smile
‎[Camera shutter sound]
‎(Man 7) Damn
‎- Come here, you idiot
‎- (Man 7) Damn
‎[Voice guide] Please look at the camera
‎Smile
‎[Camera shutter sound]
‎[Machine operating sound]
‎[Voice guide] Confirmed
‎[People murmuring]
‎(Gi-hoon) Hey, Sang-woo!
Ah, it's Sangwoo!
Hey, what happened to you?
Why are you here?
Oh, I went to your shop a few days ago
Your mom said
you went on a business trip abroad.
Oh, and what was that talk earlier?
Do you have debt?
Oh, the Jeong Sangwoo living in Ssangmun-dong?
[Announcement Voice] Welcome to the first game,
everyone.
Hyung, let's talk later.
[Announcement Voice] To all participants
Please wait for a
moment at the playground.
I will say it again.
Participants,
please wait for a moment on the field.
[Elevator arrival sound]
[Phone rings]
[Elevator doors close quietly]
(Leader) [in English] I'm the front man.
The first game is ready.
Now we will begin.
[The receiver is set down with a clatter]
[People murmur]
[Seagull cries]
(Man 7) [in Korean] Hey
- (Man 8) Why?
- That, that
(Man 7) What's that?
Looks really weird
(Man 8) Ah, fuck, the head is so big
[Laughing from Man 7]
[Voice guidance] The first game is
'Mugunghwa Flower has bloomed.'
While the seeker shouts 'Mugunghwa Flower has bloomed'
you can move forward,
but if any movement is detected after that,
you will be eliminated
(Youngwook) Mugunghwa flower?
Is that what we used to
do when we were kids?
‎[Guide Voice] Let me say it
again ‎(Gi-hoon) Ah, it seems like it?
‎(Man 8) Mugunghwa, damn, are you
messing with me? ‎[Guide voice flows out]
‎Why are they making us do this?
‎(Man 7) Want to make a bet?
‎Whoever reaches the goal first
‎[Guide voice] If movement is
detected after that
‎you’re out
‎(Man 8) A million won, does that work?
‎[Man 7's chuckle]
‎(Man 7) Oh, damn,
does that work?
‎[Guide voice] Avoid the
seeker’s eyes within 5 minutes.
Those who are entering the finish line
It’s a pass
Then let's begin
[Machine voice] ♪ The Mugunghwa flower has
bloomed ♪
[Male 7's startled groan]
[Machine operation sound]
[Heavy breathing]
[Announcement voice] Number 324
Eliminated
You idiot, you’re caught
[Sound of a thud]
(Youngwook) Just now
What was that sound?
[Machine voice] ♪ The Mugunghwa flower has
bloomed ♪
(Male 8) Hey
You’re eliminated, you idiot
Don’t play around and get up
[Clears throat]
[Machine operation sound]
"Movement detected"
[Gunshot]
[Male 8's pained groan]
[Surprised gasps from people]
[People murmur]
[Scream]
[Gunshot]
[People's screams]
[Chaos]
[Gunshots echo continuously]
[Gi-hun's pained groan]
[People's pained groans]
[Loud chaotic sounds flow out]
[Dark music]
[Machine operating sound]
‎[Gunshot] ‎[Moans of pain]
[Guide voice] I will say it once again.
While the seeker shouts "The Mugunghwa flower has bloomed,"
‎you can move forward.
If movement is detected afterwards,
you will be disqualified.
It is a disqualification.
I will say it once again.
While the seeker shouts "The Mugunghwa flower has bloomed,"
‎you can move forward.
[Gi-hun's trembling breath]
If movement is detected afterwards,
it will be a disqualification.
Then we will begin.
[Mechanical voice] ♪ The Mugunghwa flower has bloomed ♪
‎[Mechanical voice] ♪ The hibiscus flower
‎has bloomed ♪
‎[Gunfire can be heard]
‎[Frightened groan]
‎[Mechanical voice] ♪ The hibiscus flower
‎has bloomed ♪
‎[Gunfire]
‎[People's painful groans]
‎[Gi-hun's frightened groan]
‎[Gunfire]
‎(Sang-woo) Hyung
‎Don't turn your head, listen
‎[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
‎If you stay like that, you’ll die anyway.
I think that doll is a motion detection device.
[Mechanical operating sound]
If you hide behind the person in front of you, you won't be detected.
[Mechanical voice] ♪ The rose of Sharon has bloomed ♪
[Gunshot]
[Man 9's painful groan]
[Man 10's painful groan]
[Shaky breathing]
[Gunfire continues to ring out]
There's no time.
[Trembling groan]
[Mechanical voice] ♪ The rose of Sharon has bloomed ♪
[Gasping breath]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Startled Groan]
‎[Rough Breathing]
‎[Mechanical Voice] ♪ The Rose of Sharon has
‎Bloomed ♪
‎[Gunshots Continue to Ring Out]
‎[Mechanical Voice] ♪ The Rose of Sharon has
‎Bloomed ♪
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Man 11's Scream]
‎(Deok-soo) Who is it, since earlier?
‎(Saebyeok) The one who hit you from behind.
‎(Deok-soo) You damned b*tch…
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Man 12's Scream]
‎(Saebyeok) Should I hit you one more time
‎on the back of your head?
Don't do it, please
‎[Gunfire keeps ringing out]
‎Please
‎Don’t tremble, you idiot
‎If you get caught like that, you'll die
‎[Mechanical voice] ♪ The rose of Sharon has bloomed ♪
‎[Gunfire keeps ringing out]
‎[Screams of people]
‎[Flustered moan]
‎[Shaky breath]
‎[Gunfire]
‎[Mechanical voice] ♪ The rose of Sharon has bloomed ♪
‎[Gi-hun's flustered moan]
‎[Strained moan]
‎Please save me, okay?
‎Let go of this
Please
Please...
[Young-wook is sobbing]
[Mechanical voice] ♪ The Rose of Sharon has bloomed ♪
[Gunshots are ringing out repeatedly]
[Ragged breathing]
[Mechanical voice] ♪ The Rose of Sharon has bloomed ♪
[Trembling breath]
[Gunfire]
[Young-wook's scream]
[Startled breath]
[Remote control sounds]
"Jazz"
[Soft music starts to play]
[Gunshots keep coming]
‎[Mechanical voice] ♪ The
Mugunghwa flower ‎has bloomed ♪
‎[Soft music]
‎[Surprised breath]
‎[Mechanical operating
sound] ‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Scream of man 13]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Tense groan]
‎[Anxious breath]
‎[Rhythmic music]
‎[Timer end sound]
‎[Mechanical operating sound]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Scream]
‎[Gunshots ring repeatedly]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Scream of man 14]
‎[People murmur]
‎[Rough breathing]
‎[A rattling sound]
‎[Heavy music]
‎[Seagull's cry]
‎[Rough breathing of dawn]
‎Subtitles: Ahn Hyun-jeong