"Netflix series"
[Elegant music flows out]
[Majestic music]
[Rough breathing]
[Trembling breath]
[Tension-filled music]
Why did you do that?
What do you want to talk about?
Why did you push that person?
[Scoff]
You got lucky and drew the very last seat
Your heart has become very generous, huh?
But if that guy had insisted like that gangster
[Gi-hun's incredulous breathing]
What would you have done then?
It was the last spot
That person was definitely trying to go
How can you be so sure?
That guy
He’s the one who, even though he knows how to differentiate glass,
Just watched everyone drop dead in front of him
Anyway, both you and I survived to the end of the bridge
Fuck, hyung
You might not know, but
The reason I'm still alive
Is not because of that bastard
The reason I am alive is
I did everything I could to survive
No matter how many reasons you come up with
You just killed an innocent person
Get a grip!
Either way, if we want to take that money
All the other guys have to die
If I kept your hands clean,
Shouldn't you be grateful instead?
Would you have pushed me too?
Ha, fuck, ah
Gi-hun hyung!
[Sigh]
Do you know why my life is in such a mess?
You're asking lame questions even in this situation
(Sangwoo) Your meddling is unnecessarily wide
but your head is fucking useless
Damn, you're the kind of person who has to eat shit to know whether it’s shit or soybean paste
Yeah
It's all my fault that I ended up like this
I'm not smart
I have no abilities
Living off my aging mother's back
and being a pathetic bastard with a big nose
But then
The pride of Ssangmun-dong, the genius Jang Sang-woo from Seoul National University,
why is he here doing this?
(Gi-hoon) A loser like me,
[Frustrated sigh]
Rolling around in a dung field,
Is that also my fault?
[The buzzer sounds]
[The door creaks open]
[Trembling breath]
(Administrator 1) To all of you who have completed
five games safely,
I sincerely congratulate and commend you.
Now, for you who have become finalists,
We have prepared a special gift
Before revealing the gift
Please change into the outfit we've prepared
[Nervous breathing]
[Water flows out]
[Dark music]
[Rough breathing of dawn]
[Suffering moans of dawn]
[Difficult moans of dawn]
[Rough breathing of dawn]
[Straining moans of dawn]
[Difficult moans]
‎[Ragged breathing]
‎[Tense music]
‎[Gasping breath]
‎(Captain) Bring him alive
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Startled breath]
‎[Tense breathing]
‎[Call connecting tone]
‎[Startled breath]
‎(Vice-Captain) Hwang Jun-ho!
‎- Vice-Captain
‎- (Vice-Captain) Where the hell are you right now?
‎Vice-Captain, can you hear me?
‎(Vice-Captain) You haven’t shown your face for days
‎and there’s been no contact
‎I’ll explain everything later.
‎(Captain) What the hell are you doing?
‎I'm currently ‎on an
island somewhere in the
southwestern sea
- (Captain) What?
‎- Please track my phone location
and quickly send a support team.
(Captain) What did
you say? Support?
‎(Junho) A support
team, at least the coast
guard ‎and more than one
company of the mobile unit.
(Captain) Hey, what are you
talking about? I can't hear you!
‎I'll send you photos and
‎videos, so please check them.
- (Captain) Hey, hey
‎- I'll contact you again.
(Captain) Please
speak a little slower...
‎[Urgent breathing]
‎[Elegant music flows out]
‎[The worker sets down
the knife with a thud]
‎(Manager 1) Today's dinner is a gift to thank all
of you finalists for the dedication and effort
you've shown until now, and to express our hope for
even more wonderful performances in the final game.
Please enjoy without any worries.  ‎[Nervous breathing]
‎[Cutlery clinks together]
‎[Meat is sliced briskly]
‎[Labored breathing]
‎[Cutlery clinks]
‎[Tense music]
‎[Tensed breathing]
‎(Manager 2) Over there!
‎[Elegant music flows out]
‎[Glass is placed down with a thud]
‎[Breath is exhaled]
‎[Meat is sliced quickly]
‎[Tense music]
‎[Jun-ho's rapid breathing]
‎[Surprised breathing]
‎[Running footsteps]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Jun-ho's surprised breathing]
‎[Jun-ho's tense breathing]
‎(Jun-ho) It's the police!
‎Everyone drop your weapons and surrender!
‎[Rough breathing]
‎Everything you've done has been sent to the police
‎and the coast guard will arrive here soon
‎(Captain) Well,
‎has the South Korean police ever been that diligent?
‎And here,
‎it's a place where phone calls don't even go through well
‎I don't know what you've sent,
‎but I have no idea if it actually got through
‎If you confess now,
‎you could receive leniency.
(Squad Leader) If you put down that
gun now and hand over your phone,
Your life can be spared
‎(Junho) Stop right there!
‎[Junho's heavy breathing]
‎(Captain) You can load
‎five rounds into that gun
‎But according to police regulations
‎you must leave one in the chamber empty
‎and load one blank shell
‎So there are three live rounds
‎[nervous breathing]
‎You shot one and killed one guy
‎and another shot broke the lock
‎So there should be
‎one round left in that gun.
With one step, I can kill you
‎[Elegant music flows]
‎[Rough breathing]
‎[The laborious breaths of dawn]
‎[Grand music]
‎[Elegant music]
‎[The trembling breaths of dawn]
‎[Rising music]
‎(Captain) Give up
‎(Junho) I warned you
‎If you come any closer…
‎[Gunshot]
‎[The captain's pained breaths]
‎(Captain) It's all over now
‎Come with me
‎[Flustered breathing]
Listen to me
You have to live
Who is it?
You
[Dark music]
Hyung
Let's go
[Flustered breaths]
Come with me
(Junho) Hyung
Why are you…
[Gunshot]
[Heavy sound effect]
[A splash is heard]
(Gihoon) Kang Saebyeok
[Trembling breaths]
Don't be scared
I didn't come to kill you
You've been dozing off since earlier
If I was going to kill you, I would have done it already
‎[Trembling Breaths of Dawn]
‎I brought this because of that guy
‎For self-defense
‎You don't look too good
‎No
‎I'm fine
‎But why did you leave so much food?
‎It just didn't taste good
‎Don't lie
‎If you're sick
‎Will the uncle fix it for you?
‎[Trembling Breaths]
‎Don't worry about me
‎Just take care of yourself in front of the uncle
‎Hey, Kang Saebyeok
‎Let's do it together
‎Next game
(gi-hun) Whatever it is
We're helping each
other like a team.
Then we can beat that guy.
We're taking that money
out together, splitting it in half.
What are you going to do with that money, uncle?
First, I’ll pay off my debts
Then, I’ll get my mom a store at the market
Quitting street vending and running a store
is my mom's dream.
And
I want to take on the role of a dad
properly for once.
How old are you?
Ten.
You’re the same age as my little brother.
Where’s your little brother now?
At the orphanage.
I promised to go pick him up once I make some money.
I’ll bring my mom too.
If we just prepare one house for the three of us to live together,
we decided to do that.
Even if we split the money in half,
that would be enough and more.
Hey, mister.
Make me one promise.
What promise?
Either you or I,
if one of us survives and gets out of here,
let's make sure to take care of our remaining family.
Don’t say such things.
We can just leave him behind and you and I can go.
But still, promise me.
[The trembling breath of dawn]
I will definitely take care of my little brother.
‎(Gi-hun) Shh
‎[Tense music]
‎[Nervous breathing]
‎(Dawn) Don't do that
‎Mister
‎You're not that kind of person
‎[Calm music]
‎[Shaky breathing]
‎[Dawn's labored breathing]
‎[Gi-hun's sigh]
‎[Dawn collapses heavily]
‎[Gi-hun's urgent breathing]
‎[Dawn's labored breathing]
‎(Gi-hun) Hey
‎Hey, what's wrong with you, huh? Hey
‎[Gi-hun's surprised groan]
‎Ah, you…
When did this start?
When did you get hurt?
[Gi-hun's urgent groan]
(Dawn) Sir
(Gi-hun) Yes
[In a strained voice] I want to go home
[With trembling breaths]
Hey
Hey, Kang Saebyeok, pull yourself together
(Gi-hun) You can't lose consciousness
Just hang in there for a moment
I'll call a doctor
[Gi-hun's labored breathing]
(Gi-hun) Over here, please help
I've lost a lot of blood
Please help me! ‎[Gi-hun's
desperate breathing]
‎A person is dying!
‎There's no one there!
‎Hey, you bastards!
‎A person is dying!
‎We have to save a person ‎Whether
it's playing a game or whatever!
‎Please respond!
‎[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
‎[Gi-hun's shocked breathing]
‎[The buzzer goes off]
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, please
call a doctor over
there, I’ve lost a lot
of blood, ah, hurry, okay?
‎[Gi-hun's desperate breathing]
‎There…
‎[Gi-hoon's panicked breath]
‎[Heavy music]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎Dawn
‎(Gi-hoon) Dawn, dawn
‎[Gasping] Hey
‎No, ah, dawn
‎[Choking back tears]
‎No, dawn, ah…
‎[Rough breath]
‎[Sobbing]
‎[Strained groan]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Surprised groan]
‎[Captain's trembling breath]
‎Why is hyung…
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Soft music starts playing]
‎[Trembling groan]
‎[Soft music]
‎[Flames are raging]