"Netflix series"
What are you watching?
[Button sound]
(Manager 1) How do we play the game?
(Captain) Proceed
Sir
[Gi-hun's focused breathing]
Thank you
[Laughter]
You look great
[Elegant music plays]
[Voice announcement] In a moment
the fourth game will start
Participants are advised to move
according to the instructions of the staff
Once again, we announce
the fourth game will start
Participants are advised to move
according to the instructions of the staff
[Nervous breathing]
[Surprised breathing]
(Manager 2) Right now
what you are witnessing is
the end for those who have broken
the rules of this world
for their own benefit
Furthermore, it is the end for those who have
corrupted the pure ideals of this world
In this world,
all of you are equal beings and
Everyone should be given equal
opportunities without any discrimination.
We promise that such an unfortunate incident will not happen again.
We sincerely apologize to all participants regarding this incident.
[Embarrassed breath]
[Sigh]
[Tense music]
"6th round winners list"
[Camera shutter sound]
[Phone ringing sound]
[Phone is ringing]
[Nervous breath]
[Elevator arriving sound]
[Phone keeps ringing]
(Leader) [English] This is the Frontman.
Yes, there is a small issue,
but we are handling it right now.
Don't worry.
It will be sorted out without any problems
before the VIPs arrive.
Yes, the game will start as scheduled,
and on time.
[Leader's sigh]
[Shaky breathing]
[Elegant music flows]
[Deok-soo's sigh]
(Beauty) [Korean] Your face is rotten.
Why?
Did the string break?
That’s really, oh my. [Guidance voice]
Welcome to the fourth game, participants.
This game will be
conducted in pairs of two.
Find someone you
wish to play the game
with, and if both agree, shake hands to
become partners. Once again, I would like
to remind you, this game will be conducted
in pairs of two. Find someone you wish to
play the game with, and if both agree,
shake hands to become partners. You have 10 minutes starting now.
Please form pairs of two.
‎[Tense music]
‎[Call waiting tone]
‎[Nervous breathing]
‎[Receiver operation sound]
‎[Call waiting tone]
‎[Sigh]
‎(Beauty) Oppa, oppa, oppa
‎Let's do it together, okay?
‎I'm better than you think
‎I'm stronger than most guys
‎And I've been caught 5 times before I bought it
‎It's just because I didn't study
‎My brain is no joke, okay?
‎If you do it with me
‎I'll do anything you tell me to do.
[Deep Breath]
I wonder if you’ll be surprised if you know what I can do for you?
Huh? Yes?
[Sangwoo's Deep Breath]
Everyone wants to hang out with me right now, but are just being cautious?
Why, are you worried?
Should I decide for you? Huh?
(Dawn) Stop being so annoying
Would that make you do it with the lady?
[Beauty's Deep Breath]
Just be honest
You just don’t want to team up with a woman and an old man, right?
(Man 1) Isn't it natural when lives are at stake?
We almost died during the tug of war.
That's right.
God had a purpose in making Eve from Adam's rib.
The roles and functions given by God
are different for men and women.
(Jiyoung) Idiots.
What is this, the Garden of Eden?
Hey, where are you going?
Why?
Wanna join me?
(Beauty) Idiot bastards.
You guys.
Not catching me is a big mistake
‎[Sigh]
‎Sangwoo, let’s…
‎(Sangwoo) Ali, let’s do it together
‎The games we play here
‎In the end, it’s either physical strength or mental skill
‎If it's just the two of us
‎We can win against most opponents
‎[Awkward smile]
‎Ah, no, no, no, no
‎(Gihun) Ah, it’s okay, it’s okay, it’s okay
‎Hey, you two would really get along well
I can just do it with
another person.
‎[Gi-hun's awkward smile]
‎(Man 2) Let's do our best
‎[sigh]
I...
‎Sir
‎Ah, I'm sorry but
‎if you go out in this outfit
‎without a jacket,
‎people will look down on you
‎[sigh]
‎Let's do our best
‎I look forward to your support, hyung
‎[they smile together]
‎[people are talking among themselves]
‎(Ji-young) Hey
‎Come with me
‎Why would I?
‎Then are you going to cling to those old farts?
Hmm, embarrassing?
Is being embarrassed the problem?
I have to win no matter what
Then do it with me
I’ll make sure you win
By what means?
By any means necessary
Why do you want to do it with me?
Why did you ask me to do it?
You were the only one
Someone who seemed like they would join me
I feel the same way right now
[reaches out his hand]
Ah, among the remaining guys
I’m the best one available.
I used to be a math teacher outside.
I also played early morning soccer, so I'm in good shape.
Oh, there are many people who want to do it, too.
But I'm just focusing on playing with you, uncle.
I think we'll get along well.
[awkward laugh]
But, you know,
I don't know what game to play.
(Man 3) Oh, don't hesitate.
Just play with me.
Ugh, at this rate,
I'll end up missing out on everyone
and become like a duck egg in Nakdong River.
You know, right?
The guy who cheated earlier was executed
and now there are thirty-nine of us left.
If we partner up in pairs,
one person will be left.
[panicked groan]
Oh, so what happens then?
What happens?
If someone is left, they’ll automatically be eliminated.
That old man over there will be the one left.
[sigh]
(Man 3) Stop stalling for time
Let’s do this, you and me.
(Gi-hun) Sir,
Would you like to team up with me?
‎[Guide Voice] The time for selecting team
members has ‎ended. ‎[Timer end sound]
‎(Beauty) You guys are really making a
mistake right now. ‎[The guide voice continues]
‎Do you really think
‎you can win without me?
‎I'm a beauty!
‎From Dongducheon to
Gangnam, ‎I've swallowed it all up!
‎[Beauty's urgent breathing]
‎What are you going to do if things like
air games or rubber bands ‎come out?
‎I'm a pro at that.
So, oppa, let's do it together.
Oppas can't do that
kind of stuff, right?
[The Displeased
Groan of Man 4] Brother!
[The Beautiful Woman's
Urgent Breathing]
Ah, unnie, let's do it [A
woman's embarrassed moan]
Fuck, those cock-sucking bastards Get the
hell out of here! [Woman's agonizing moan]
‎(Man 5 and Beauty) ‎- What’s
going on? ‎- Let’s all gather
together and give it a try
[sound of woman exerting
strength] ‎(Beauty) Unnie, I’m good with
girls too. Unnie, I’ll really do well, Unnie!
‎(Man 5) What’s going on!
‎[Beauty's urgent breathing]
‎(Beauty) Hey - (Beauty) Don’t trust
this bastard ‎- Oh, right, right
(Beauty) This bastard is trash.
This bastard will
ditch you in no time.
This bastard ‎Was in cahoots
with the dead doctor outside!
‎(Man 6) Yeah, that…
‎(Beauty) You didn't know?
This bastard hid everything from you guys
just to save himself. I’m
right, you son of a bitch.
This bastard is in on it too!
- (Man 6) Hey, hey, hey -
(Beauty) This bastard has to die!
- (Beauty) This bastard too…
- (Man 6) Hey, you fucking!
[Man 6 clicks his tongue]
[The door slams shut]
[The beauty's trembling breath]
[Significant music]
Where, where, where did everyone go?
(Beauty) Huh, why is no one here?
I still don’t have a partner.
Where has my partner gone, huh?
Who snuck her away?
Where is my partner, you bastards!?
Where is my partner!?
(Beauty) Give me my partner back, you motherfuckers!
[Beauty's scream]
(Deoksoo) Ugh, that annoying bitch
[Chuckling] Finally, that girl
Won't have to just look at me
(Man 6) But
What was that girl saying earlier?
About you and that doctor…
(Deoksoo) Mind your own business
That crazy woman was in a hurry
And was just rambling on as she pleased
[Announcement voice] Participants,
Please follow the instructions of the staff
And move to your respective positions
[Significant music]
(Sangwoo) Ali
Don't be nervous
If the two of us team up, we'll definitely win
(Ali) Since I'm with you, hyung
I think we can win
(Sangwoo) Yeah, let's win and get out together
We’re going back to our families with the money
(Ali) Yes, hyung
(Il-nam) Back in the day, I...
I've lived in a neighborhood like this.
‎(Gi-hun) [smiling] Me too.
‎I lived in a similar alley when I was a child.
‎[Gi-hun's laughter]
‎[Voice guidance] Now please take one pocket each.
‎Each pocket contains ten marbles.
‎Please check the quantity.
‎Sir, it seems we're playing marbles this time.
‎You've played marbles before, right?
‎Oh, of course.
‎When I was a kid in the neighborhood,
‎ah, I played a lot of marbles.
I was an athlete
‎[Gi-hun's laughter]
I can do it a little too
‎[Il-nam responds]
Ah, that's a relief
I was worried about what would happen if you made me do something hard again
Then we
Have to become partners
Partners?
I mean, since you said you play with marbles
Do you not know about partners?
‎(Il-nam) Friends in the neighborhood
Using marbles and tops
Together, you know
‎[responds]
Without yours or mine
Ah, my buddy, ah, I
remember [Il-nam agrees]
There was a guy in my
neighborhood too
The one
I was closest to, uh,
yeah, that buddy
[Clears throat]
[Thoughtful sigh]
(Il-nam) Is this how we make a bond?
[Laughs together]
(Gi-hun) Yes, that's right,
like this [Laughs together]
Sir, no, buddy
[Il-nam agrees]
Let's sweep all the beads from
this neighborhood [Laughs together]
[Sigh of relief]
‎[Guide Voice] This game is
‎each person using their own marbles
‎Now you will compete with the
‎partner next to you
‎The person who takes all ten of the
‎opponent's marbles wins
‎[Dark Music]
‎I will say it again
‎[Il-nam's thinking breath]
‎Each person using their own marbles
‎compete with the partner next to you
‎The person who takes all ten of the
‎opponent's marbles wins
‎Honey
‎[Slight Laugh]
‎Fuck
‎[A Sigh of Dawn]
‎Brother
‎So pretty
‎(Gi-hun) Sir
‎[Guide Voice] The time limit is 30 minutes
‎Let’s start
‎[Gi-hun's trembling breath]
‎Sir
‎Let's do it
‎Then one of us will die
‎Should we just sit here and
‎both die together?
‎(Sang-woo) Or are you going to
‎die in my place?
‎[Rattling out marbles]
‎Ali, you haven't done something like this, have you?
[Ji-young's Sigh]
It's the biggest tragedy since 6.25
Isn't it?
What game should we play?
You're so cold
(Ji-young) You're completely frozen
You
Are you really a spy who came down from the North?
Stop talking nonsense
Just tell me what game we're going to play
I don't really know either
(Ji-young) This is a game that the old-timers played when they were young
They said we can set the rules of the game however we want
I'll think about it
(Il-nam) Definitely
It should be around here, right?
‎(Gi-hun) Sir, we need to
‎play a game now
‎(Il-nam) That's strange
‎This alley
‎[Gi-hun's awkward breathing]
‎is right
‎But where did our house go?
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, Sir
‎All you have to do is guess
‎whether the number of marbles in my hand
‎is odd or even
‎Odd or even?
‎What's that?
‎Odd numbers are 1, 3, 5
‎Even numbers are 2, 4, 6
‎Do you understand?
Think carefully
Bet your gems on one of the two
[Interesting music]
(Man 6) Hall
[Deoksu's sigh]
[Man 6's excited gasp]
[Man 6's laughter]
How many did you open?
(Man 6) Ah, damn
Should I have opened one more?
[Laughter]
[Man 6 shakes the gems]
Don't laugh, you bastard
Hey, what the hell, why are you swearing?
‎(Man 6) 'Brother, brother' you call me,
‎do I really look like your subordinate?
‎You little bastard, do you want to die, huh?
‎(Man 6) Huh, kill you?
‎Oh my, how are you going to kill me?
‎You can't use violence, you idiot
‎[Sigh]
‎[Trembling breaths]
‎[Laughter of Man 6]
‎(Gi-hoon) Oh, come on, old man
‎We have to do it now
‎(Il-nam) Do what?
‎(Gi-hoon) Oh, uh, playing with marbles
‎Playing with marbles?
‎(Gi-hun) Hey, ah, look
‎Everyone is doing it right now
‎We have to do it too
‎No
‎What do you think I am, a kid?
‎[Il-nam's discontented groan]
‎Ah, old man
‎Let's
‎finish it with just one round
‎All in
‎Just one round
‎Do you want to spend the remaining time
‎with me like this?
‎[Man 1's exclamation]
‎- (Man 1) Awesome
‎- (Man 2) Damn
‎(Man 1) One, two, three, four
‎(Man 2) Come with me
‎I like it
‎What are you going to do?
‎Why are you in such a hurry?
‎Do you want to kill me like that?
‎[Sigh]
‎We're just going to play one round
‎There's still quite a bit of time left
‎Let's do it at the end
‎Then what will we do until then?
‎Talk
‎What kind of talk?
‎Talk we can't have with anyone else
‎One of us is going to die here anyway
‎Whatever we talk about
‎There won’t be an awkward situation when we see each other again
‎Right?
(Ally) Partner
[Interesting music]
How many did you bet?
‎(Ally) Two
[Sang-woo's sigh]
You fold
I don't want to play with that guy
‎(Ally) Teacher
I want to play with someone else
Don't say useless things and fold quickly
That old man has dementia
He's not in his right mind
If it goes on like this, that old man
‎is just forfeiting, isn't he?
We can't play the game, right?
‎(Gi-hun) Ah, damn it
‎[Urgent breathing sounds]
‎Um…
‎[Gi-hun's laughter]
‎Just try it once, this really…
‎This is really fun
‎(Il-nam) I want to go home
‎My home is definitely in this alley
‎(Gi-hun) Oh, damn, seriously
‎Please, get a grip
‎[Il-nam's bewildered groan]
‎If we stay like this, we’re both going to die
‎You have a lump here
‎So you might not care since you're going to die anyway, but
I have to live and get out of here
I have to live and get out, Lee
[Il-nam's painful groan]
[Gi-hun's ragged breathing]
Don't scream
You just need to play with me
[Gi-hun's embarrassed breathing]
(Man 6) Twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen
Fuck, okay
[Man 6 shakes the beads]
(Deok-su) Fuck, change the game
(Man 6) Why should I? It's going well.
(Duksu) So far,
I’ve been going along with what you wanted,
Now let’s do it my way,
I don’t want to?
[Laughter]
Fuck
(Duksu) Let me change the game
That’s the only way it’s fair,
You guys said this was an equal place, right?
(Byeongjeong) I admit it
What is it? What do you want to do?
Pair
[Significant music]
What are you doing? Open your hand
[Sigh]
You bastard, you
You’re using tricks, right?
Hyung
Why, why, why is this happening?
How can you keep winning?
The odds in this game are fifty-fifty, (Sang-woo) hey, you
bastard This doesn't make any sense, this situation right now!
No, I didn't do anything
[Ali's flustered moan]
You bastard, you pretended to know
nothing And fooled me, didn't you?
You said you’ve never
done this kind of thing before!
How did you trick me?
Tell me! Damn [The
gun clicks as it's loaded]
[Sang-woo's trembling breath]
‎(Ji-young) Why did you
come down from the North?
I thought this place was better.
So
Is this place better?
What about the family?
Did they come down with you?
Just my younger sibling.
What about your parents?
My father crossed the river
and was shot, drifting away in the river.
My mother
was captured by the public security in China
and was dragged back to the north.
Where is your younger sibling?
In an orphanage.
(Il-nam) Pair
[Gi-hoon’s sigh]
(Il-nam) Odd-even
Odd-even
[Il-nam’s laughter]
Did I win?
How many did you get?
‎[Meaningful sound effect]
‎(Gi-hun) Ha, damn
‎[The marbles jingle]
‎(Deok-soo) We take turns until one person puts it in
‎Each of us throws one marble
‎into that hole
‎What if someone puts it in?
‎The person who put it in gets to take all the
‎marbles that have been thrown on the ground up until then
‎(Man 6) Ah…
‎You’re aiming for a big comeback?
‎Why?
‎Are you scared?
‎Ah, damn, I am scared
‎I can put them in the hole a bit too, huh?
(Man 6) Do you think it's okay? Huh?
[Man 6's laughter]
Are you going to earn money here and then leave
What will you do with it?
I need to find a house to live with my younger sibling
And I need to bring my mom from the North
[Half-hearted laughter]
Hey
With 40 billion won, you could do that and still have leftover
Is there nothing else?
What, like a place you want to go?
Jeju Island
Jeju Island?
(Dawn) I saw it on TV
It doesn't look like Korean land, it feels like a foreign country.
[Smirks]
Hey
What kind of scale is Jeju Island?
Well, it should at least be on the level of Hawaii, no
At least Maldives
(Jiyoung) Let's have a mojito
Mojito?
Haven't you seen the movie?
With Lee Byung-hun
'Let's go to Mojito and have a drink in Maldives'
[Smiling] Don't you know?
Oh, hey, you really won't make it
When you get out of here
You should learn from me how to spend money stylishly in South Korea
[Laughter]
Ah
Both of us can't go out.
[Awkward laugh]
[Sangwoo's sigh]
[Sniffling]
I was wrong, Ali.
I misunderstood you.
(Sangwoo) But I can't die like this.
[Sniffling]
If I die here,
my whole family dies.
[Sangwoo sobs]
I'm sorry.
Hyung.
(Ali) [Sniffling] I'm sorry.
I also have family.
(Sangwoo) Hey, Ali, hey.
Hey, if you just help me
there's a way for both of us to survive
You came this far because of me, right?
I even gave you money for the bus
And the tug-of-war was thanks to my plan
We stood watch together all night
Until just a moment ago
We promised to leave this place together,
didn't we?
[Sobbing]
So please
please just trust me once and help me
Huh?
What are you going to do?
‎(Il-nam) Is this a single?
‎It seems like a pair?
‎It's a pair, right?
‎Ah, please hurry up!
‎Single
‎Shit…
‎[Sigh]
‎[Il-nam's laugh]
‎I won again
‎Ha, how many did you put down?
‎[Laugh]
‎[Meaningful sound effect]
‎[Surprised gasp]
‎Ah, shit
‎[Sigh]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Interesting music]
‎[Frightened moan]
‎Ha, one left.
There's still one left
‎[Deoksoo's displeased sigh]
‎[A sigh]
‎[Deoksoo's annoyed sigh]
‎[Man 6 blows air through his lips]
‎[Man 6's sigh]
‎[Deoksoo blows air through his lips]
‎[Exhilarated gasp]
‎[Man 6's displeased sigh]
‎[Deoksoo's laughter]
‎(Man 6) Damn it
‎I think
‎that in the end, a few teams here
‎won't get a clear outcome
‎Why?
What were the rules of this game?
One person has to get all the other people's marbles in 30 minutes to pass.
(Sangwoo) But think about it.
There's no way for one side to definitely get all the marbles in 30 minutes.
As we go back and forth winning and losing,
there will definitely be a team that doesn't reach a decision in time.
So what will you do?
Will you eliminate all those people?
That doesn't make sense.
There hasn't been a decision, right?
Yeah
Then what about then?
We will have a team competition.
One team will combine their marbles,
and bet twenty against the other team
to win.
[Sangwoo grabs Ali tightly]
(Sangwoo) Just like our original plan,
you and I can compete as a team again.
Both of us can go out together.
[Gunshot]
[Both are startled]
[Screams of Male 7]
[Announcement] Number 414 eliminated.
Hey, do you want me to end up like that by your hand?
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Man 8's scream]
‎[Guidance voice] Eliminated number 2
‎Have you ever seen dead people
‎before coming here?
‎When I was young, there was an epidemic in our village
‎At that time, the villagers
‎were dying every day
‎The soldiers gathered the bodies
‎and burned them all together
‎(Dawn) At that time, our
‎grandfather, grandmother, and even my brother
‎were all burnt
‎You have too deep of a story
‎[Laughs softly]
‎Have you
‎ever seen it?
[Gunfire]
[Announcement Voice]
Number 130 eliminated
The first time I saw it
It was my mom.
When I came home from school,
my mom was lying on the floor, dead.
Next to her
was that man, my father,
holding a knife.
The next thing I saw
was the corpse of my father.
The one standing next to me with a knife
was me.
[Dark music]
That man was a pastor by occupation.
He would hit my mom
and after doing that to me,
always prayed
to forgive our sins.
But on the day mom was killed,
didn't you pray?
Did you know you wouldn't be forgiven?
[Shaky breath]
[Approaching footsteps]
[Gunshot]
[Surprised breath]
[Voice prompt] 40th elimination
[Nervous breath]
Clap
(Gi-hun) No, no, kid
Kid, wait a sec
Wait a sec, I
Hall
[Significant sound effect]
[Il-nam's thinking breath]
[Dark music]
‎(Il-nam) What did you say?
‎Yeah?
‎Just now
‎What did you say?
‎Clap
‎Clap, right?
‎Then
‎I lost, huh?
‎(Il-nam) Huh?
‎(Ali) Really
‎Can we win together?
‎(Sang-woo) Yes
‎Really?
‎(Sang-woo) Listen to my plan
‎And if you don't like it, you can reject it
‎Then I’ll just
‎give you the last remaining marble
‎So you won’t feel guilty about killing me
‎Plan
What is it?
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Quickly inserts the bead]
‎[Voice Guide] Number 68 eliminated
‎That depends on who the opponent is
‎First, we need to figure out which team will remain
‎We don’t have time right now, so let’s quickly scatter
‎and check the situation of the other teams
‎Among the teams that haven’t decided the outcome yet
‎look for the younger teams
‎and the older teams
‎Age?
‎(Sangwoo) Yeah
‎That’s important
‎Whether they’re young people like you
Or are they people over 50
[Tapping Ali] You
‎ go to the alley across
I’ll check out the teams on the other side
Yeah, hyung
(Sangwoo) Ali
(Ali) Yes?
(Sangwoo) That pocket
It’s dangerous to be holding it like that
Everyone is going to turn into crazy people at the last minute
‎ You never know what's going to happen
If we lose this, it’s over
You know?
I’ll make it safe for you to carry it
What are you going to do if
you take the money out of here?
I have never thought about it.
The day of release
Someone was waiting
in front of the prison.
(Jiyoung) I thought he was just a debt collector
because of the debt that person left behind.
It's giving a business card.
That strange business card.
Just
I'm here because I
have nowhere to go.
What will I do when
I get out of here?
Didn't think about it?
Do you want to go to
Jeju Island together?
Sorry
Another mistake [Gunshot]
[ tense music ] [ announcement
voice ] 229th eliminated
(Duksu) Damn it
[Displeased breath of Man 6]
[Man 6's sigh]
[Blowing air through the mouth]
[Deoksu's tense breathing]
[Man 6's sigh of relief]
(I thought you were
in, you son of a bitch.)
[Man 6's sigh]
Did you throw everything?
[Man 6's tense breathing]
I’m still
There's one left.
[Man 6's laughter]
[Breath of tension]
Duk-soo.
I had a good time
during this period.
[Meaningful sound effect]
[Deoksu's Cheer]
‎[Tense music]
‎(Deok-soo) I’m in, it’s mine
My blue bead!
[Smiling] Ha, damn.
I've had a good time,
you son of a bitch!
[Deoksoo's Laughter] [Man
6's Embarrassed Groan]
[The urgent breathing of Man 6]
[Urgent music]
Ah, shit.
‎[The urgent moan of man 6]
[Man 6's rough breathing]
You sons of bitches!
[Gunshot]
[Announcement Voice]
Number 278 disqualified.
(Sangwoo) Here we go.
How about this, it should
be much safer, right?
[There is a creaking sound.]
Yes.
Then let's meet here again when
there are 3 minutes left on the timer.
I'll tell you the plan then.
(One man) hall
One, two, three.
One, two, three
Both have three, huh?
But just now
What did you say?
Huh?
I
What did I say?
You said it's a match.
I
Is that so?
Yes
[Embarrassed breath]
That's right.
I lost again?
[Gunshot]
[Announcement Voice]
Number 43 is eliminated.
[Everyone has their own words]
(Ally) [Urdu] Older team
‎[The terrified moan
of man 9] ‎[Gunshot]
‎[Announcement Voice] [Korean]
85th Elimination ‎[Ali's Surprised Moan]
Hey, hurry up, hurry.
(Ally) [Urdu] three children
- (Man 11) Ah, this doesn’t work.
- (Man 12) Move aside.
(Ally) [Urdu] Two old men
A sound of clattering
can be heard.
[Gunshot]
[Announcement Voice]
[Korean] Disqualified number 276
[Il-nam's powerful breath]
[Il-nam's Sigh]
[One sigh]
It's your turn to fold.
(Han 남) Huh?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
[Sigh]
Hole
(One man) uh
Ah
What date is it today?
This month the 24th is
It's our son's birthday.
I decided to buy a
robot toy as a gift.
I completely forgot and couldn't do
anything for your birthday last year.
This time, you
really have to do it.
[The Breathing
Thoughts of Il-nam]
Ah
That's right.
Um, well, what, what did I say?
It's a hall.
Huh?
(One Man) Uh
(Sangwoo) It's twenty beads.
The rules you mentioned are
No matter what game you
play, do not use violence.
You just had to take all
of the opponent's beads.
I have never used any violence.
[People say, each
in their own way]
[Guidance Voice] 3
minutes until game ends.
3 minutes left.
[Sigh]
[The Sigh of Dawn]
[Gunshot]
[Voice guidance]
Disqualified number 158
Let's do it now.
Throw the bead from here
The side that stops
close to that wall wins.
How is it?
It's dawn.
What?
My name.
The dawn of a strong river.
Dawn
Good.
You?
Jiyoung
(Fore dawn) Is there a surname?
No, nothing like that.
(At dawn) Who will do it first?
You go first.
Your number is fast too.
Did all the beads disappear?
[Il-nam's awkward breathing]
What should I do?
I want to play more.
Would you mind lending
me just one bead?
I'm sorry.
[Gunshot]
[Guide voice]
Disqualification number 70
(A man) Ah
Here this is
There was one
bead, wasn't there?
[Smiling] One is
I'm left.
[Il-nam's smile]
[Gi-hun's urgent breathing]
(Gi-hun) Two,
four, six, eight, ten
Two, four, six, eight, nineteen
[Meaningful sound effect]
[Awkward breath]
Hey, sir, just a moment.
Inspiration!
[The Sigh of Dawn]
[Calm music]
What are you doing?
(I lost, right?)
What the hell are you doing?
Ah, I just dropped the bead.
Is this it?
Is it that you'll make
me win no matter what?
Do you think I'll be
grateful for you doing this?
Throw it again.
I can throw again,
but you can't win.
Ah, just make it
a bit cooler for me.
Don't just act cool by
yourself, throw it again!
[The Rough Moans of Dawn]
I'm not here.
(What?)
You have a reason
to leave here, but
I'm not here.
(Jiyeong) What should I
do when I get out of here?
Since you asked, I've been
thinking about it continuously.
No matter how
much I think about it
I can't think of it.
[sniffling]
It's only right for someone
with a reason to leave.
That's right.
You are
Make sure to survive and
get out ‎[The dawn is breaking]
So
Meet mom too.
I’m also looking for
my younger sibling.
[Laughter mixed with tears]
You must go to Jeju Island.
(Big) Hyung
Hyung
Bro, where are you?
Bro
Sangwoo hyung!
I just saw you.
Hyung!
Sang-woo hyung!
[Heavy sound effect]
[Surprised breath]
[Shivering breath]
[Gunfire]
[Announcement Voice]
eliminated number 199
(Kyung-Sae Byeok)!
[The trembling breath of dawn]
Thank you
Thank you for doing it with me
[Laughter]
[Gunshot]
[Announcement Voice]
Disqualified number 240
[Choking up]
‎[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
(Yeong-gam) Sir
I'll do it just one
more time, okay?
Please just once.
‎(Il-nam) Ah
[Gi-hun's urgent breathing]
This is the house.
[The Elasticity of One Man]
I used to
With my wife and son
I lived in this house.
I, in the yard
There was also a small pond.
‎- (Gi-hun) Old man
‎- (Il-nam) Oh my
(Gi-hoon) There's one bead left.
I have to do that with you.
[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
When I get off work
and come home,
My son was having a
blast playing with his friends.
I didn't even know Dad was here.
Get a grip.
Pull yourself together and
listen to what I'm saying!
Then I will hide
behind that utility pole.
I secretly watched
my son playing.
‎[Sobbing] ‎(Il-nam) We were
having so much fun playing.
‎[Il-nam's Laugh] ‎Please
Get a grip.
Ah, I'll ask you like this.
We all bet everything.
Shall we have a match?
Yes?
I'll stake everything I have.
Your thing is all in too.
What do you mean by that?
All that you have.
I'm betting everything
I have on this.
That's fair, isn't it?
Are you saying to hang all
of this with that one bead?
Ah, where is such nonsense?
That's nonsensical!
Then
You deceived me.
You took my bead.
Does it make sense?
[Heavy sound effect]
[Calm music]
[Trembling Moan]
[Gi-hun's trembling breath]
Take (Il-nam)
It's yours.
We are
You're just a freeloader.
Don't you remember?
We made a pact by
linking our fingers.
Among close friends
There’s no yours or mine.
[Weeping]
(Il-nam) During that time
Thank you.
Thanks to you.
Take care.
Gane
It's okay.
All
It will be alright.
(Il-nam) Yeah
‎[Gi-hoon keeps sobbing]
[Timer End Sound]
(Ilnam) Me
I remembered the name.
My name is
It's a boy.
Oil Man
[Weeping]
[Gunshot]
[Surprised Moan]
[Announcement Voice]
Number 1 eliminated
[Gihun is sobbing]
Subtitle: Ahn Hyun-jeong