"Netflix series"
‎[Meaningful music]
‎[Crying all night]
‎[Insect sounds]
‎[Unbuckling the seatbelt]
‎[Junho's trembling breath]
‎(Administrator 1) Start
‎(Administrator 2) Personnel check
‎[Junho's nervous breath]
‎[Car door opens with a click]
‎[Surprised breath]
‎[Scanner operating sound]
‎[Scanner error sound]
‎[Tense music]
‎[Worker's painful moan]
‎[Junho and the worker's straining groan]
‎[Junho's straining groan]
‎[Worker's labored groan]
‎[Scanner operating sounds echo everywhere]
‎[Junho's straining groan]
‎[Junho's rough breathing]
‎[A splash sound occurs]
‎(Soldier 1) There
‎(Junho) Over there
‎Due to motion sickness…
(Manager 3) Have you forgotten the rules?
'Don't speak first without the superior's permission'
Go up to the cabin and wait.
[Seagull crying]
[Significant music]
[Bright music flows out]
(Gi-hun) Sir
Sir
[Patting Il-nam] Sir
(Il-nam) Huh?
[Sigh of relief]
(Gi-hun) Are you back to your senses?
You
[Il-nam's pleased breathing]
(Il-nam) 456
(Gi-hun) Yes.
Oh, I thought you were gone forever
[Il-nam's laughter]
Me
I'm not that easy to kill
Ah, of course
[Il-nam's laughter]
Thanks to you, I went out
and because of you, I came back
You can't go first
[Il-nam chuckles lightly]
(Il-nam) Many have returned
[Il-nam's laughter]
(Gi-hoon) That's right
It seems everyone had a tough time
[Gi-hoon's exclamation]
[Il-nam's perplexed groan]
Hey, that girl who couldn't even
name the kid has come in, ah.
(일남) I see.
Did you come up with a name for the baby?
- Huh?
- (기훈) Oh my.
‎(상우) Hyung Gi-hun.
‎(기훈) Oh, Sang-woo.
Did you come?
I didn't think you would.
‎(기훈) Tsk, oh my.
It turned out like this.
What about you?
Did you come after seeing your mom?
‎(알리) Bosses.
‎(기훈) Oh? Ah.
My lifesaver.
‎(알리) Bosses.
Glad to see you again.
‎[Gi-hoon's laughter]
‎Thank you so much for the transportation fee that day.
‎You gave this friend a transportation fee?
‎I heard you walked from Yeouido to Ansan.
‎(Gi-hoon) [smiling] Hey, that’s warm-hearted.
‎Is this like, our training camp buddies?
‎Is that the vibe?
‎[Gi-hoon's laughter]
‎What's a training camp?
‎Do you know about the military, the military?
‎A place where you shoot guns and train and stuff.
‎(Ali) Ah!
‎A place where soldiers live?
‎(Gi-hoon) That's right.
‎Oh, wait a minute.
Speaking of which,
How about we all come together like in the military?
That's right.
We never know what games we might play in the future,
so it would be advantageous to form a group to prepare for various scenarios.
Ah, let's do it together.
(Gi-hun) Ah, the strength is no joke.
Did you see it?
This guy completely lifted me with one hand?
Really, can I join too?
Ah, yes, uh
You're just a private.
This guy is a good soldier.
I'm just a veteran private.
‎[Gi-hoon's laughter]
‎(Ali) Thank you, boss.
‎[laughter]
‎Let's skip the 'boss' part.
‎(Il-nam) Hey.
‎If it's okay,
‎can I join in a bit?
‎Oh, of course.
‎Sir, you can be the chief master sergeant who has been in the army for a lifetime.
‎[Il-nam's overwhelming breath]
‎[Gi-hoon's laughter]
‎Thank you.
‎(Gi-hoon) Hey, this is
Our team composition
fits perfectly, doesn’t it?
[Gi-hun's laughter]
I’ll forget everything that happened
and take you in.
Come under me.
Originally, we were quite good as a team, right?
Are you still posturing?
The kids outside (at dawn) were all out looking for you,
spread out everywhere?
(Deok-soo) Don’t mess around.
No matter how tough you are,
acting all lone wolf here
won't give you any advantage.
Can’t you see this?
Those guys with masks
The beds of the dead have been completely taken away.
If you're not careful, your bed will be out soon too.
[Laughter]
Worry about your bed instead.
[People's ridicule]
[Deoksoo's sigh]
(In the early morning) Hey, guys.
Don't stick to this bastard.
This bastard is outside,
stealing from his little followers' pockets,
just fattening his own belly.
Eventually, he got so bold that
he even tried to dip into his own crew's pockets,
and got caught, ending up like this.
Do you know what we call these kinds of people in our hometown?
'Revolutionary son of a bitch'
[Laughter]
This red bastard, dammit
‎[Approaching footsteps]
Older brothers and sisters
Sorry for interrupting
What is it?
Oh my
This guy is good-looking
[Nervous laughter]
Hey
Let me join too
Join where?
With your team
[Laughter]
Auntie, what are you good at?
I’m good at everything except for the things I can’t do.
‎(Beauty) Isn't she much more worth it than that skinny sister?
‎In many ways
‎[People's gasps]
‎Can you do it that well, ma'am?
‎[Deok-su chuckles]
‎Shall we give it a try?
‎(Deok-su) The bed is empty anyway
‎[People laugh]
‎[Elegant music begins to play]
‎[Announcement voice] It is now meal time
‎Participants are requested to line up in the center of the accommodation
‎Let's eat before we do anything
‎[Announcement voice] I will repeat once more
It's mealtime from now on.
‎[Laughter of the people]
‎Participants, please line up in the center of the accommodation
‎[Sigh]
‎Damn punk
‎[Button pressing sound]
‎(Administrator 4) Out of 201 participants,
‎187 have returned
‎The re-participation rate is 93%
‎(Leader) Those who have not returned
‎will continue to be monitored
‎and we'll report the situation
‎(Administrator 4) Yes
‎[Gi-hun's sigh]
‎[Il-nam's sigh]
‎(Il-nam) It reminds me of old times, huh
Did you also have this
kind of lunchbox, sir?
[Smiling] Then
My wife is with my
stuff and the kids' stuff.
Every morning, I was always busy packing lunch boxes.
‎[Il-nam's laughter]
‎Oh, is this hot? The rice? Ahhh
‎Hey, if there was just
‎a stove in the middle
‎(Gi-hun) it would be perfect to warm it up and eat
‎Sang-woo, do you remember?
‎We had a charcoal stove in our elementary school classroom
‎If you placed the lunch box on it
‎it would get really hot
‎and burn the bottom, right?
‎[Il-nam agrees]
‎Hyung
‎(Gi-hun) Yeah
If you have time to think about the past
Think about what game to play next
[Il-nam's cough]
Hey
Do you think about that?
You only know if you shut up
(Il-nam) Well, from what we've done so far
In the past
Isn't it one of the games
That kids used to play?
Well, it's like that
It's not just one or two
(Gi-hun) Ddakji, touch-and-go, dantta-meokgi
Tic-tac-toe, tag, tonkatsu, freeze tag
Girls play hopscotch, rubber bands, string games
[Thinking breath]
What else is there?
(Ali) I don't know how to do those things
Don't those kids play these games?
Don't worry
The kids' game rules are simple
If you don't know, we'll help you
[Laughter]
Thank you
[Significant music]
[Guidance voice] Today's schedule
has all ended.
All workers are requested to
return to their accommodations.
I will say it once again.
Today’s work is all finished.
All workers, please return to your accommodations.
(Beauty) [Bang, bang, banging on the door]
Hey, hey, hey, open the door, you bastards!
Ugh, I feel like my bladder is going to burst!
Don’t you guys even need to pee?
Just let me go to the bathroom!
I’m only asking to be allowed to go to the bathroom for a moment, what’s so hard about that?
Oh, come on, there are tons of guys here, are you really going to piss on the floor?
[Slamming the door] Hey,
you… Hey, you bastards!
If you want to make me play a game, at
least treat me like a human and let me play!
Hey, triangle, call your
superior above you.
Call that square
guy, you bastard!
(Manager 5) You cannot go outside the
accommodation except during the
designated times. Fuck, so am I
supposed to only need to pee at the times you set, huh?
(Beauty) How dare you,
you motherfuckers.
You think I can't do it?
[The beauty is huffing]
Hey, it's cheap!
Hey, it’s coming out continuously!
[The beauty is huffing]
(Soldier 2) Come this way
Anyway, those Joseon folks
have to act up just because their ear holes are open
Oh, damn
I’ll go too
What’s up?
[Significant music]
[The beauty's chuckle]
Since someone is desperately cleaning the toilet
you just sit right down?
Hey
You’re a bit annoying, you know?
That rude girl
Hey
[A clattering sound]
[A relieved sigh]
[Mechanical operating sounds]
[The beauty's straining moan]
[Straining moan]
[A relieved sigh]
[Laughter]
[The beauty's laughter]
[Inhales]
[Exhales]
[Laughter]
It's sweet, damn it
[The door slams open]
Oh, that surprised me, damn
(Beauty) Why?
[Surprised breath]
[Clears throat]
Do you want a sip too?
Don't move, just quietly suck on the cigarette.
[Flustered moan]
(Beauty) What are you doing?
[Interesting music]
You...
Are you going in there right now?
(Dawn) Let me see what's in there.
Buy me some time.
If you find out something, I'll let you know too.
Okay, step here.
[Beauty's painful moan]
[Dawn's straining moan]
[Beauty's struggling moan]
[Dawn's ragged breathing]
[The Beautiful Woman's Strained Moan]
[Sniffing]
[The Dawn's Strained Moan]
(Beautiful Woman) Oh!
Constipation is killing me!
[The Beautiful Woman Pretends to Strain]
I might as well give birth to a baby!
Someone help!
[Pretends to Struggle]
[The Beautiful Woman
Pretends to Be in Pain]
(Beautiful Woman)
Ugh, I'm dying.
Why isn't it coming out?
[Significant Sound Effect]
[Soldier 2 Bangs on the Door]
(Soldier 2) It's time to go back.
(Beautiful Woman) Wait a minute!
It's almost all out now.
Ah, I need to come out quickly.
I need to come out quickly! I really need to come out quickly?
(Soldier 2) It's time to go back.
If you don't come out, I'm going to go in.
(Beauty) Wait a minute, wait a minute!
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
There's no toilet paper here, there's no toilet paper!
Ah, damn it.
I'm going to wash with water and come out.
Don't come in.
Stay right there.
Am I washing?
I'm not wearing anything down below right now.
[Breathless sound]
Damn it!
Ah, it's being cleaned well.
[Mouse squeaking]
[Trembling breath]
[Disgusted groan]
[Surprised breath]
[Mouse squeaking]
(Manager 6) What are you doing?
Keep stirring.
[Trembling breath]
[Soldier 2 bangs on the door]
(Soldier 2) Please come out now.
(Beauty) I told you I don't have any toilet paper right now!
(Soldier 2 and Beauty)
- If you don't come out, I'll drag you out.
- You can't go out until you clean up, huh?
(Beauty) Hey, isn't it basic to check for toilet paper at every stall?
Call that square little bastard!
I need to make a complaint, damn it.
What are you looking at, you bastard?
Wow, damn.
[The toilet flushes]
Fuck, bastard.
Hey, you bastard.
Didn’t I tell you not to come in?
This is sexual harassment!
Hey, when I go out,
I'm gonna sue you, you bastard, damn.
[The beauty lightly hits Soldier 2]
Ha, damn.
‎[Bell Alert]
‎[Guidance Voice] It’s now
‎time to go to bed
‎You’ve worked hard today
‎[Joon-ho's Sigh]
‎[Significant Music]
‎(Joon-ho) A deserted island
‎Kidnapping, surveillance
‎And masks
‎[A cough is heard]
‎[Cell phone operation sound]
‎[Sigh]
‎(Beauty) [In a small voice] Hey
‎What did you see, huh?
‎Ah, what did you see?
‎(Dawn) Let’s talk about it tomorrow
‎(Beauty) Ah, what are you going to talk about tomorrow?
‎Talk about it now, damn it
‎Hey, what did you see?
‎If you were up there for that long earlier
‎you must have seen something!
‎Huh?
‎[Bell ringing notification]
‎[Guidance voice] A new morning has arrived
‎Everyone, please get out of your seats
‎We will start the headcount in 10 minutes
‎[Timer activation sound]
‎[Elegant music starts playing]
‎[Guidance voice] It is now time for a meal.
Participants are requested to line up
in the center of the accommodation.
‎(Beauty) Hey
‎What did you see?
‎I said what did you see?
‎You said you'd tell me in the morning?
‎If you were there for that long
‎you must have seen something
‎The guys in masks
‎were melting something in a big cauldron
‎What were they melting?
‎I don't really know
‎(Beauty) Oh, fuck
‎I went through all that trouble yesterday to save you
‎And you don't know?
‎It smelled
‎(Beauty) What kind of smell?
‎It smelled like sugar
‎Sugar smell?
So they were just melting sugar like that?
Seems like it
Is that really all there is?
[A beauty's sigh]
(Beauty) You
If there's something you see but don't say
‎I'll put a cigarette burn in your eye, damn it
[Awkward breath]
I'm really hungry
I'm craving something sweet?
Ah, damn
Are they at least giving us some sweet potatoes today?
[ Junho's sigh]
[The buzzer goes off]
[Meaningful music]
[Voice Guidance] We are checking the number of people
Please wait at the door
It is completed
Everyone, please move
[Interesting Music]
[Gi-hun takes a deep breath]
Ah, um…
Isn't there any chocolate milk?
I can't drink white milk
When I was young, if I drank this white milk
I couldn't digest it
I also didn't have milk served at school
[Il-nam's laughter]
(Gi-hun) Damn
(Il-nam) You
You must have been hit a lot by your father when you were young.
‎(Gi-hoon) How do you know?
‎(Il-nam) My son was just like you.
‎[Il-nam's laughter]
‎(Ali) Boss
‎Why aren't you eating that?
‎You eat it.
‎(Ali) Really?
‎I usually don’t eat breakfast.
‎(Ali) Thank you, boss.
‎(Gi-hoon) Usually, kids who study well
‎have a small appetite.
‎Drink this too.
‎(Ali) Thank you, boss.
‎[Gi-hoon chuckles]
[Elegant music flows out]
[Guide voice] In a moment
the second game will begin
Participants, please move according to the guidance of the staff
Once again, we announce
In a moment, the second game will begin
[Significant music]
Participants, please move according to the guidance of the staff
[Forklift warning sound]
[Tense music]
(Sangwoo) You saw something, right?
Last night
I heard you talking to some woman
Tell me, what did you see
(Saeob) Why should I?
(Sangwoo) You said you were a defector
Games like sticker slapping, hibiscus flower
These games they make you play
are all games I used to play when I was young
The next game too
likely has a high probability of being something like that
If you tell me what you saw
I might be able to figure it out
[Intriguing music]
‎(Gi-hun) Why is the playground so big?
‎What are they trying to make us do?
‎[Announcement voice] Welcome everyone to the second game
‎(Gi-hun) Hey, what do you think it is, huh?
‎Lasting a long time on the spinning wheel?
‎Dropping someone from the jungle gym?
‎Huh?
‎[Announcement voice] Before we start the second game
‎please choose one of the four shapes in front of you
‎and stand in front of it
‎(Alli) What is that?
‎(Gi-hun) Circle, triangle
‎Star, umbrella
‎(Il-nam) It feels like I've seen this somewhere before?
‎[Significant music]
‎(Sang-woo) If you tell me what you've seen
‎I might be able to figure out what it is
‎I was melting sugar
‎[Significant sound effect]
‎[Sang-woo's startled breath]
‎(Gi-hun) Sang-woo
‎(Sang-woo) Huh?
‎What should we do?
‎(Sang-woo) Well
‎[Guidance voice] Please choose one immediately
‎and proceed.
[People are buzzing]
Please select one immediately
and move to it.
Should our team all move together?
That could be dangerous.
We don't even know what to order yet.
If we all go to one place,
it might be unfavorable for everyone.
Really?
(Sangwoo) There's a saying in investment
'Don't put all your eggs in one basket'
[Gihun's laughter]
(Gihun) Sir
[Il-nam responds]
This guy got into Seoul National University Business School as the top student.
He was a famous prodigy in our neighborhood since childhood.
(Il-nam) Really?
Wow, that's amazing, right?
(Gi-hoon) [smiling] Oh, of course!
Then, as Sang-woo said, let's split up for now
and see who's the best, okay?
Who will go where?
I'll go to the triangle.
(Gi-hoon) Then what about that place?
(Ali) [in Urdu] Circle.
[Gi-hoon's puzzled grunt]
Circle.
(Gi-hoon) Ah, a circle?
Yes, it looks like the
moon from our hometown.
[Gi-hoon's troubled breathing]
(Gi-hoon) Then there are
a star and an umbrella left.
[Il-nam's thoughtful breathing]
You choose first.
(Gi-hoon) Ah, should
I? [Il-nam responds]
Ah, then I'll take the umbrella,
I guess. [Il-nam responds]
Umbrella?
Why?
Since I was a kid, I
used to get scolded a
lot by my mom for
losing umbrellas.
So later on, my mom just
gave me broken umbrellas.
I’m like other kids too.
Carrying around a decent umbrella was my wish.
[Il-nam responds]
- (Gi-hun) Do you really dislike it?
- (Il-nam) Huh?
Shall we switch then?
(Il-nam) No, I actually like it.
[Il-nam laughs]
These days
isn't it hard to see stars?
(Gi-hun) Alright, let's all get moving.
Once we find out what kind of game it is,
we'll gather again and come up with a strategy.
[Il-nam responds]
Gi-hun hyung
(Gi-hun) Uh
[sigh]
No
[Laughter]
[Voice guidance] The time for choices has ended
I will now reveal the game
[Interesting music]
[Voice guidance] Participants, please take one case from in front of you
Participants, please take one case from in front of you
[Voice guidance] Now, please open the case
and check what's inside
[Strained groan]
[Puzzled groan]
Circle?
[Quivering breath]
[Heavy breathing]
[Announcement voice] The second game is
the sugar-drawing game.
The shape you chose is
the shape you have to draw.
(Gi-hun) I'm screwed.
[Announcement voice] The time limit is 10 minutes.
If you cleanly cut out the given shape
within 10 minutes, you pass.
Then, let's begin.
[Timer start sound]
[Timer ticking]
[Sigh of relief]
[Il-nam's cough]
[Gi-hun's anguished groan]
‎[Gi-hun's trembling breath]
‎[Picks the dalgona swiftly]
‎[Nervous moan]
‎[Machine operating sound]
‎[There’s a rustling sound]
‎[Joo-un's surprised breath]
‎[Joo-un's trembling breath]
‎[Frightened breath]
‎(Joo-un) I
‎Just this once
‎Please, just one more time…
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Screams of people]
‎[Joo-un slides quietly]
‎[Frightened breath]
‎[Surprised moan]
‎[Approaching footsteps]
‎[Surprised breath] ‎[Tense music]
‎Ah, I, no, I made a mistake, ah,
please save me
‎[Soldier 3 cocks the gun]
‎(Woman) Please
save me... ‎[Gunfire]
‎[People's startled groans]
‎[Frightened groans]
‎[Gunfire continues to ring
out] ‎[People's painful groans]
out] ‎[People's startled groans]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Gunfire echoes out]
‎[Machine operating sound]
‎[Gunshots]
‎[People's astonished moans]
‎[Trembling breaths]
‎[Gunshots]
‎[People's astonished moans]
‎[Gunshots continue echoing]
‎[People's pained moans]
‎[Gunshots]
‎[Relieved breaths]
‎[Guidance voice] 111 success
‎[Gunshots]
‎67 success
‎[Ali's tense breaths]
‎[Gunshots]
‎(Ali) Do, do, do, circle
‎[Relieved breaths]
‎Circle
‎[Guidance voice] 199 success
‎[Trembling breaths]
‎210 success
‎[Gunshots]
‎[People's astonished moans]
‎224 success
‎246 success
‎[Gunshots]
‎[People's astonished moans]
‎73 success
‎[Scanner operating sound]
‎(Administrator 7) 29
‎[Guidance voice] 72 success
‎(Junho) Yes
‎(Administrator 7) What is today's mission?
‎[Guidance voice] 34 success
(Junho and Manager 7) - My mission is...
- Mission 29 is transporting the eliminated.
‎(Admin7) Why are you already in?
‎(Jun-ho) I'm sorry
‎[Guidance voice] Success 44
‎(Jun-ho) I was mistaken
‎(Admin7) Wait here until the game is over
Listen to what you were mistaken about then
‎[Guidance voice] Success 32
‎[Elegant music plays]
‎(Soldier4) Left
‎[Significant music]
‎[Guidance voice] Success 122
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Shaky breathing]
‎Success 29
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Gi-hun's tense breathing]
Success 218 ‎[Gi-hun's
flustered breathing]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Gi-hun's tense breathing]
‎[People's startled gasps]
‎[Tense music]
‎[Gi-hun's trembling breathing]
‎[Announcement voice] Success
357 ‎[Scraping the Dalgona]
‎[Gunshot] Success 83 ‎[Tense
music] ‎[Elegant music starts to play]
‎[Sigh]
‎[Trembling breaths]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Heartbeat sound effect]
‎(Gi-hun) It's melted
‎[Interesting music]
‎(Gi-hun) This is it
‎You can melt it from behind
‎The boundary line is thinner, so it will melt first
‎[The lighter clicks off]
‎[Voice guidance] 212 successful
‎196 successful
‎[Deoksu's tense breathing]
‎244 successful
‎69 successful
‎[Interesting music]
‎70 successful
‎[Sigh]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Gi-hun's trembling breath]
‎[People's startled gasps]
‎[Gunshot]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Laughter]
‎[The ticking sound resonates]
‎[Gi-hun's rough breathing]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Choked breath]
‎[Timer ending sound]
‎[Voice guidance] 456
‎Successful
‎[Sniffles]
‎[Elegant music plays]
‎[Trembling breath]
‎[Voice guidance] The second game has
‎ended
‎Participants who have succeeded
‎please leave the playground immediately
(Soldier 5) Move your hands
away [Sang-hoon's startled groan]
[Trembling breath]
[Tense music]
[Sang-hoon's angry groan]
[Gunshot]
[Soldier 5's scream]
[Sang-hoon's straining groan]
[Sang-hoon's shout]
[Gunshot]
[Sang-hoon's straining groan]
Hey, you fucking bastards!
(Sang-hoon) What the fuck is this?
What kind of shitty game is this?
Why does someone get something good
while someone else has
to get something bad?
(Sang-hoon in the video) Don't
come closer You fucking bastards.
This bastard
I'm going to kill him
I'm really going to kill him
[Sang-hoon is panting]
[People's shocked groans]
[Gunshots can be heard]
[Tense music]
[Sang-hoon's trembling breath]
Take, take, take off your mask
Hurry, take it off, damn it
[Sang-hoon's trembling breath]
[Manager 7 tosses the mask]
Turn, turn, turn around
[Sang-hoon's shocked breath]
(Sang-hoon) Why has this happened
to a kid like you?
[Trembling breath]
[Gunshot]
[Sang-hoon collapses]
[Dark music]
[Gunshot]
(Captain) Remember
If you find out who we are, you will die
(Manager 7) Number 29
Stay here until it's over
You’ll see what you were mistaken about
[Tense music]
Subtitle: Ahn Hyun-jung